<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><jobs><item><id>1695548377</id><date_posted>2025-05-26T10:00:44.976</date_posted><date_created>2025-05-26T10:25:09.255668</date_created><title>Software Engineer III, Infrastructure, Core</title><organization>Google</organization><organization_url>https://www.google.com</organization_url><date_validthrough></date_validthrough><locations_raw><item><key name="@type">Place</key><address><key name="@type">PostalAddress</key><addressCountry>MX</addressCountry><addressLocality>Mexico City</addressLocality><addressRegion>CDMX</addressRegion></address></item></locations_raw><locations_alt_raw></locations_alt_raw><location_type></location_type><location_requirements_raw></location_requirements_raw><salary_raw></salary_raw><employment_type></employment_type><url>https://www.google.com/about/careers/applications/jobs/results/85470199116899014</url><source_type>ats</source_type><source>in-house</source><source_domain>google.com</source_domain><organization_logo></organization_logo><cities_derived><item>Mexico City</item></cities_derived><regions_derived><item>Ciudad de México</item></regions_derived><countries_derived><item>Mexico</item></countries_derived><locations_derived><item>Mexico City, Ciudad de México, Mexico</item></locations_derived><timezones_derived><item>America/Mexico_City</item></timezones_derived><lats_derived><item>19.4333</item></lats_derived><lngs_derived><item>-99.1333</item></lngs_derived><remote_derived>false</remote_derived><description_text>MINIMUM QUALIFICATIONS:

 * Bachelor’s degree or equivalent practical experience.
 * 2 years of experience with software development in one or more programming
   languages, or 1 year of experience with an advanced degree in an industry
   setting.
 * 2 years of experience with data structures or algorithms in either an
   academic or industry setting.
 * 2 years of experience with developing large-scale infrastructure, distributed
   systems or networks, or experience with compute technologies, storage or
   hardware architecture.



PREFERRED QUALIFICATIONS:

 * Master&apos;s degree or PhD in Computer Science or related technical fields.
 * 2 years of experience with performance, large-scale systems data analysis,
   visualization tools, or debugging.
 * Experience in coding and system health, diagnosis and resolution, and
   software test engineering.
 * Experience developing accessible technologies.
 * Experience in backend coding languages such as C++, Python or Java.


ABOUT THE JOB:

Google&apos;s software engineers develop the next-generation technologies that change
how billions of users connect, explore, and interact with information and one
another. Our products need to handle information at massive scale, and extend
well beyond web search. We&apos;re looking for engineers who bring fresh ideas from
all areas, including information retrieval, distributed computing, large-scale
system design, networking and data storage, security, artificial intelligence,
natural language processing, UI design and mobile; the list goes on and is
growing every day. As a software engineer, you will work on a specific project
critical to Google’s needs with opportunities to switch teams and projects as
you and our fast-paced business grow and evolve. We need our engineers to be
versatile, display leadership qualities and be enthusiastic to take on new
problems across the full-stack as we continue to push technology forward.

As a Software Engineer, you will provide the infrastructure and application
programming interfaces (APIs) that enable distributed debugging and development
across Google, at a scale unmatched anywhere else. You will build the next
generation of debugging services that will transform debugging at Google and
make it easy to root cause events at large-scale, distributed systems in a
privacy-safe way. You will also build services that scale well and handle large
workloads, and will add minimum latency to clients and will be inexpensive to
operate.

The Core team builds the technical foundation behind Google’s flagship products.
We are owners and advocates for the underlying design elements, developer
platforms, product components, and infrastructure at Google. These are the
essential building blocks for excellent, safe, and coherent experiences for our
users and drive the pace of innovation for every developer. We look across
Google’s products to build central solutions, break down technical barriers and
strengthen existing systems. As the Core team, we have a mandate and a unique
opportunity to impact important technical decisions across the company.


RESPONSIBILITIES:

 * Solve problems around query latency, data freshness, index correctness and
   serving at scale.
 * Automate and improve efficiency in operational and user support.
 * Support users with system integrations and resolve client issues.
 * Participate in weekly onduty rotation to address user and operational
   tickets.
 * Collaborate with privacy to explore options for quick access to debug data
   while protecting users&apos; data.</description_text></item><item><id>1694652817</id><date_posted>2025-05-25T22:50:03.365</date_posted><date_created>2025-05-25T22:53:04.021738</date_created><title>Software Engineer - REF137F</title><organization>Jobs for Humanity</organization><organization_url></organization_url><date_validthrough></date_validthrough><locations_raw><item><address><addressLocality>Mexico City</addressLocality><addressRegion>Mexico City</addressRegion><addressCountry>Mexico</addressCountry></address></item></locations_raw><locations_alt_raw><item>Mexico City, CDMX, Mexico</item></locations_alt_raw><location_type></location_type><location_requirements_raw></location_requirements_raw><salary_raw></salary_raw><employment_type><item>Full-time</item></employment_type><url>https://jobs.smartrecruiters.com/JobsForHumanity/744000061388755-software-engineer-ref137f</url><source_type>ats</source_type><source>smartrecruiters</source><source_domain>jobs.smartrecruiters.com</source_domain><organization_logo></organization_logo><cities_derived><item>Mexico City</item></cities_derived><regions_derived><item>Ciudad de México</item></regions_derived><countries_derived><item>Mexico</item></countries_derived><locations_derived><item>Mexico City, Ciudad de México, Mexico</item></locations_derived><timezones_derived><item>America/Mexico_City</item></timezones_derived><lats_derived><item>19.4333</item></lats_derived><lngs_derived><item>-99.1333</item></lngs_derived><remote_derived>false</remote_derived><description_text>Company DescriptionJobs for Humanity is collaborating with The RRS Group Inc to build an inclusive and just employment ecosystem. We support individuals coming from all walks of life. 

Company Name: The RRS Group IncThe RRS Company and its affiliated entities, the RRS, have offered real estate development-related services to investment grade clients for decades. These services are focused on providing site acquisition, architectural services and development management for commercial offices and industrial properties. Our customers receive innovative integrated enterprise solutions for all building services. As part of this integrated process, our company can provide impactful consultation services on the marketing and financial aspects of a real estate development project and Facility Solutions.But that’s not all…we also provide a full range of benefits to help our employees achieve financial, emotional, mental, and physical well-being including supporting their own communities through Making Lives Better with RRS,Inc (MLBA). MLBA is our award-winning, in-house non-profit charity that’s focused on empowering people through mission-focused work. Our Core ValuesIntegrity | doing the right thing when no one is watching and acting with uncompromising honesty. We believe in maintaining lasting relationships based on honesty, consistency and the highest ethical standards. This creates credibility in our personal and professional relationships.Caring | showing concern, empathy and compassion for others, ourselves, and our environment. Our care shows itself in our commitment to “safety first” in all we do. We encourage each other to be the best and hold each other accountable. We help those in need, contribute to the communities in which we work and develop creative ways to be responsible with our resources.Integration | working unselfishly toward common goals across disciplines, teams, departments and regions. Our collective contributions are greater than our skills. We will be transparent and understand each other’s expertise to provide the most value when delivering our services to one another and our clients.Innovation | developing new ideas and applying the solutions that differentiate us in valuable ways. We are not comfortable with the status quo. We remain accountable for continuous improvements in our results because we do not consider innovation an end in itself. We maintain an environment where we foster new ideas and encourage changes that help us improve.               If you share these core values, we have the right opportunity for you! We anticipate the application window for this opening will close on: 06/05/2025We encourage you to apply directly through our RRS Group Careers site:https://careers.smartrecruiters.com/RRSGroupIncJob DescriptionWe are seeking a talented and innovative Software Engineer to join our dynamic team in Mexico City. As a Software Engineer, you will play a crucial role in designing, developing, and maintaining high-quality software solutions that drive our company&apos;s success.Collaborate with cross-functional teams to design, develop, and implement software applications and systemsWrite clean, efficient, and maintainable code using languages such as Java, Python, or C++Participate in the full software development lifecycle, from concept and design to testing and deploymentConduct code reviews and provide constructive feedback to team membersTroubleshoot, debug, and optimize software to ensure high performance and reliabilityImplement and maintain software documentationStay up-to-date with emerging trends and technologies in software engineeringContribute innovative ideas and solutions to technical challengesParticipate in agile development processes, including sprint planning and retrospectivesMentor junior developers and share knowledge within the teamQualificationsBachelor&apos;s or Master&apos;s degree in Computer Science, Software Engineering, or a related fieldStrong proficiency in one or more programming languages, particularly Java, Python, or C++Solid understanding of data structures, algorithms, and software design principlesExperience with version control systems, preferably GitFamiliarity with web development frameworks and database management systemsKnowledge of agile development methodologiesExcellent problem-solving and analytical skillsStrong attention to detail and commitment to producing high-quality codeEffective communication skills, both verbal and writtenAbility to work collaboratively in a team environmentDemonstrated commitment to continuous learning and staying abreast of emerging technologiesPrevious internships or substantial personal projects in software development are a plusAdditional Information RRS Group is an Equal Opportunity Employer who is committed to building strength and delivering long-term sustainability through diversity and inclusion. Respecting all backgrounds, differences and perspectives enables us to improve the lives of our people, customers, suppliers, contractors, and the communities in which we live and work. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to sex, sexual orientation, gender, gender identity and/or expression, race, national origin, ethnicity, age, religion, marital status, physical or mental disability, pregnancy, childbirth, or related medical condition, military or veteran status, or any other characteristic protected under applicable law. </description_text></item><item><id>1690841316</id><date_posted>2025-05-23T21:05:27</date_posted><date_created>2025-05-24T01:44:08.058788</date_created><title>Software Engineer (Java/Oracle SQL/Linux)</title><organization>Amdocs</organization><organization_url>amdocs.com</organization_url><date_validthrough>2025-06-22T21:05:27</date_validthrough><locations_raw><item><key name="@type">Place</key><address><key name="@type">PostalAddress</key><addressLocality>Guadalajara</addressLocality><addressRegion>Jal.,MX</addressRegion><addressCountry><key name="@type">Country</key><name>MX</name></addressCountry></address></item></locations_raw><locations_alt_raw></locations_alt_raw><location_type></location_type><location_requirements_raw></location_requirements_raw><salary_raw></salary_raw><employment_type><item>FULL_TIME</item></employment_type><url>https://jobs.amdocs.com/careers/job/563431002871520-software-engineer-java-oracle-sql-linux--mexico-guadalajara-am-</url><source_type>ats</source_type><source>eightfold</source><source_domain>jobs.amdocs.com</source_domain><organization_logo></organization_logo><cities_derived><item>Guadalajara</item></cities_derived><regions_derived><item>Jalisco</item></regions_derived><countries_derived><item>Mexico</item></countries_derived><locations_derived><item>Guadalajara, Jalisco, Mexico</item></locations_derived><timezones_derived><item>America/Mexico_City</item></timezones_derived><lats_derived><item>20.6767</item></lats_derived><lngs_derived><item>-103.3475</item></lngs_derived><remote_derived>false</remote_derived><description_text>Job ID: 199526 
Required Travel :Minimal 
Managerial - No 
Location: :Mexico-Guadalajara (AM) 
Who are we?
Amdocs helps those who build the future to make it amazing. With our market-leading portfolio of software products and services, we unlock our customers’ innovative potential, empowering them to provide next-generation communication and media experiences for both the individual end user and enterprise customers. Our employees around the globe are here to accelerate service providers’ migration to the cloud, enable them to differentiate in the 5G era, and digitalize and automate their operations. Listed on the NASDAQ Global Select Market, Amdocs had revenue of $5.00 billion in fiscal 2024. For more information, visit www.amdocs.com
In one sentence
Responsible for design, development, modification, debug and/or maintenance of software systems
What will your job look like?
• You will design, develop, modify, debug and/or maintain software code according to functional, non-functional and technical design specifications.
• You will follow Amdocs software engineering standards, applicable software development methodology and release processes, to ensure code is maintainable, scalable, and supportable, and demo the software products to stakeholders.
• You will investigate issues by reviewing/debugging code, provide fixes and workarounds, and review changes for operability to maintain existing software solutions.
• You will work within a team, collaborate and add value through participation in peer code reviews, provide comments and suggestions, and work with cross functional teams to achieve goals.
• You will assume technical accountability for your specific work products within an application and provide technical support during solution design for new requirements.
• You will be encouraged to actively look for innovation, continuous improvement, and efficiency in all assigned tasks.
All you need is...
Participate in Agile development cycles, including sprint planning, stand-ups, and retrospectives.
Prior experience of Work on telecom-related applications, particularly in BSS (Business Support Systems).
Code development and code review of new functionalities per the agile methodology
Troubleshoot issues and identify optimizations of the system
Provide support to UAT and ETQA/Testing Team.
Support and monitor the production environment
Hands on knowledge of Java, Spring Boot, Linux, Oracle SQL, Python

Why you will love this job:
• You will be challenged to design and develop new software applications.
• You will have the opportunity to work in a growing organization, with ever growing opportunities for personal growth.
Amdocs is an equal opportunity employer. We welcome applicants from all backgrounds and are committed to fostering a diverse and inclusive workforce</description_text></item><item><id>1690841319</id><date_posted>2025-05-23T21:04:35</date_posted><date_created>2025-05-24T01:44:08.075945</date_created><title>Software Engineer (Java/Oracle SQL/Linux)</title><organization>Amdocs</organization><organization_url>amdocs.com</organization_url><date_validthrough>2025-06-22T21:04:35</date_validthrough><locations_raw><item><key name="@type">Place</key><address><key name="@type">PostalAddress</key><addressLocality>Guadalajara</addressLocality><addressRegion>Jal.,MX</addressRegion><addressCountry><key name="@type">Country</key><name>MX</name></addressCountry></address></item></locations_raw><locations_alt_raw></locations_alt_raw><location_type></location_type><location_requirements_raw></location_requirements_raw><salary_raw></salary_raw><employment_type><item>FULL_TIME</item></employment_type><url>https://jobs.amdocs.com/careers/job/563431002870278-software-engineer-java-oracle-sql-linux--mexico-guadalajara-am-</url><source_type>ats</source_type><source>eightfold</source><source_domain>jobs.amdocs.com</source_domain><organization_logo></organization_logo><cities_derived><item>Guadalajara</item></cities_derived><regions_derived><item>Jalisco</item></regions_derived><countries_derived><item>Mexico</item></countries_derived><locations_derived><item>Guadalajara, Jalisco, Mexico</item></locations_derived><timezones_derived><item>America/Mexico_City</item></timezones_derived><lats_derived><item>20.6767</item></lats_derived><lngs_derived><item>-103.3475</item></lngs_derived><remote_derived>false</remote_derived><description_text>Job ID: 199423 
Required Travel :No Travel 
Managerial - No
Location: Mexico-Guadalajara (AM) 
Who are we?
Amdocs helps those who build the future to make it amazing. With our market-leading portfolio of software products and services, we unlock our customers’ innovative potential, empowering them to provide next-generation communication and media experiences for both the individual end user and enterprise customers. Our employees around the globe are here to accelerate service providers’ migration to the cloud, enable them to differentiate in the 5G era, and digitalize and automate their operations. Listed on the NASDAQ Global Select Market, Amdocs had revenue of $5.00 billion in fiscal 2024. For more information, visit www.amdocs.com
In one sentence
Responsible for design, development, modification, debug and/or maintenance of software systems
What will your job look like?
• You will design, develop, modify, debug and/or maintain software code according to functional, non-functional and technical design specifications.
• You will follow Amdocs software engineering standards, applicable software development methodology and release processes, to ensure code is maintainable, scalable, and supportable, and demo the software products to stakeholders.
• You will investigate issues by reviewing/debugging code, provide fixes and workarounds, and review changes for operability to maintain existing software solutions.
• You will work within a team, collaborate and add value through participation in peer code reviews, provide comments and suggestions, and work with cross functional teams to achieve goals.
• You will assume technical accountability for your specific work products within an application and provide technical support during solution design for new requirements.
• You will be encouraged to actively look for innovation, continuous improvement, and efficiency in all assigned tasks.
All you need is...
• Bachelor&apos;s degree in Science/IT/Computer Science or equivalent
• Participate in Agile development cycles, including sprint planning, stand-ups, and retrospectives.
• Prior experience of Work on telecom-related applications, particularly in BSS (Business Support Systems).
• Code development and code review of new functionalities per the agile methodology
• Troubleshoot issues and identify optimizations of the system
• Provide support to UAT and ETQA/Testing Team.
• Support and monitor the production environment
Main Skills: Java, Spring Boot, Linux, Oracle SQL, Python
Why you will love this job:
• You will be challenged to design and develop new software applications.
• You will have the opportunity to work in a growing organization, with ever growing opportunities for personal growth.
Amdocs is an equal opportunity employer. We welcome applicants from all backgrounds and are committed to fostering a diverse and inclusive workforce</description_text></item><item><id>1690260664</id><date_posted>2025-05-23T19:20:56</date_posted><date_created>2025-05-23T19:24:16.022978</date_created><title>Staff Software Engineer - PaaS</title><organization>Qualtrics</organization><organization_url></organization_url><date_validthrough></date_validthrough><locations_raw><item><key name="@type">Place</key><name>Mexico City, Mexico</name><address><key name="@type">PostalAddress</key><name>Mexico City, Mexico</name><addressCountry></addressCountry><addressLocality>Mexico City, Mexico</addressLocality></address></item></locations_raw><locations_alt_raw></locations_alt_raw><location_type></location_type><location_requirements_raw></location_requirements_raw><salary_raw></salary_raw><employment_type></employment_type><url>https://www.qualtrics.com/careers/us/en/job/6900525?gh_jid=6900525</url><source_type>ats</source_type><source>greenhouse</source><source_domain>www.qualtrics.com</source_domain><organization_logo></organization_logo><cities_derived><item>Mexico City</item></cities_derived><regions_derived><item>Ciudad de México</item></regions_derived><countries_derived><item>Mexico</item></countries_derived><locations_derived><item>Mexico City, Ciudad de México, Mexico</item></locations_derived><timezones_derived><item>America/Mexico_City</item></timezones_derived><lats_derived><item>19.4333</item></lats_derived><lngs_derived><item>-99.1333</item></lngs_derived><remote_derived>false</remote_derived><description_text>At Qualtrics, we create software the world’s best brands use to deliver exceptional frontline experiences, build high-performing teams, and design products people love. But we are more than a platform—we are the creators and stewards of the Experience Management category serving over 18K clients globally. Building a category takes grit, determination, and a disdain for convention—but most of all it requires close-knit, high-functioning teams with an unwavering dedication to serving our customers. 

When you join one of our teams, you’ll be part of a nimble group that’s empowered to set aggressive goals and move fast to achieve them. Strategic risks are encouraged and complex problems are solved together, by passing the mic and iterating until the best solution comes to light. You won’t have to look to find growth opportunities—ready or not, they’ll find you. From retail to government to healthcare, we’re on a mission to bring humanity, connection, and empathy back to business. Join over 5,000 people across the globe who think that’s work worth doing.
Staff Software Engineer - PaaS 
Why We Have This Role
We are looking for a staff software engineer who is comfortable with high degrees of ambiguity and is proficient at designing scalable systems, mentoring junior engineers, and acting as a technical leader as our team pushes the Qualtrics PaaS product to the next level. You should love data visualization, using AI to accelerate customer value, and building simple solutions to solve hard customer problems. Designing systems in an agile environment to withstand growth and owning quality from end to end are rewarding challenges and part of why Qualtrics is such an exciting place to work!
How You’ll Find Success
Designing and implementing well-crafted, scalable, and maintainable code
Working through ambiguity; taking business goals and product ideas and turning them into working products for real customers
Using metrics to measure success and leveraging data to make decisions
Partnering with product managers, UX designers, and other engineers to deliver solutions for our customers
Taking initiative and demonstrating persistence in getting things done
Strong level of curiosity
Showing a desire to learn new skills and grow in the role
How You’ll Grow
Enhance your ability to build scalable, fast, robust, and simple SaaS solutions
Expand your experience with full-stack development using the latest technologies
Benefit from working with other great engineers, UX designers, and product managers
Learn how the world&apos;s leading companies use data and analytics to improve their customer experience
Through mentoring, teaching, and reviewing, help the engineers on your team make sound architectural decisions and improve their code craftsman skills
Opportunities to lead teammates on challenging technical projects
Things You’ll Do
Develop scalable, fast, robust, and simple web-based solutions to solve complex business problems
Execute while business/technical requirements are not well defined, and proactively drive deliverables while anticipating and mitigating risk
Make decisions independently, in collaboration with the team, but keep stakeholders informed of impactful changes
Drive operational perfection by driving investigation of production issues, root cause analysis and follow-up actions for mitigation
Implement new features and optimize existing ones to drive maximum performance
Attend daily stand-up meetings, collaborate with your peers, prioritize features, and work with a sense of urgency to deliver value to your customers.
Contribute to technical standards for our engineering organization
What We’re Looking For On Your Resume
Has worked with design and product teams to understand needs, propose features, create early prototypes, and transform them into exciting end-user features
Has developed scalable, fast, robust, and rich web-based solutions to solve complex business problems, using the latest frontend and backend technologies
Experience working in a full-stack team, building advanced frontend applications, large-scale backends and maintaining high-volume datastores
Experience working with AWS technologies
Experience working in NodeJS is a plus
Experience with machine learning and generative AI is a plus
Experience with continuous delivery, git, test automation, and build/deploy systems
Strong algorithms, data structures, and coding background
Bachelor’s or Master&apos;s degree in Computer Science or equivalent
8+ years working in a full-stack engineering position (preferably for a SaaS company)
What You Should Know About This Team
The Ecosystem Engineering organization is committed to providing world-class developer tooling that enables the creation of business-critical solutions and extensions on the Qualtrics platform
We are a group of talented and passionate engineers dedicated to developing the Qualtrics Ecosystem, focusing on enhancing the developer experience for our partners and customers.
Our engineers collaborate closely with platform teams to ensure our products are tightly integrated and consistent with Qualtrics platform behavior, while having the flexibility to choose our own architecture and the independence to quickly deliver on our business vision.
The team’s broad suite of product ownership and true mandate for full-stack development offers an amazing opportunity to drive your career development and build a strong foundational understanding across Qualtrics systems.
Our Team’s Favorite Perks and Benefits
We take pride in our office&apos;s design aiming at cultivating creativity from our rooftop views to an open and collaborative work space
On top of a great benefits package (medical, dental, vision, life insurance, etc), we provide snacks, drinks, and free lunches in our office
Full time employees receive an annual experience bonus after their first year of employment; Qualtrics Experience Bonus is a program designed to provide experiences to our employees they might not otherwise have
QED program – Qualtrics Engineer Development (QED) allows engineers to spend up to 10% of our time each quarter on individual engineering projects and learning activities
Personalized career planning – you will work with your manager to design a plan based on your experiences, values, and career aspirations (inside and outside Qualtrics) that helps you achieve your career goals at Qualtrics
We believe in sharing Qualtrics success which is part of the compensation for all employees
The Qualtrics Hybrid Work Model: Our hybrid work model is elegantly simple: we all gather in the office three days a week; Mondays and Thursdays, plus one day selected by your organizational leader. These purposeful in-person days in thoughtfully designed offices help us do our best work and harness the power of collaboration and innovation. For the rest of the week, work where you want, owning the integration of work and life.
Qualtrics is an equal opportunity employer meaning that all qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, national origin, disability, status as a protected veteran, or any other protected characteristic.
​​​​​​​Applicants in the United States of America have rights under Federal Employment Laws:Family &amp; Medical Leave Act,Equal Opportunity Employment,Employee Polygraph Protection Act
Qualtrics is committed to the inclusion of all qualified individuals. As part of this commitment, Qualtrics will ensure that persons with disabilities are provided with reasonable accommodations. If reasonable accommodation is needed to participate in the job application or interview process, to perform essential job functions, and/or to receive other benefits and privileges of employment, please let your Qualtrics contact/recruiter know.
Not finding a role that’s the right fit for now? Qualtrics Insiders is the one-stop shop for all things Qualtrics Life. Sign up for exclusive access to content created with you in mind and get the scoop on what we have going on at Qualtrics - upcoming events, behind the scenes stories from the team, interview tips, hot jobs, and more. No spam - we promise! You&apos;ll hear from us two times a month max with fresh, totally tailored info - so be sure to stay connected as you explore your best role and company fit.</description_text></item><item><id>1689101107</id><date_posted>2025-05-23T07:31:09.58</date_posted><date_created>2025-05-23T08:25:29.020271</date_created><title>Software Engineer III, Chrome</title><organization>Google</organization><organization_url>https://www.google.com</organization_url><date_validthrough></date_validthrough><locations_raw><item><key name="@type">Place</key><address><key name="@type">PostalAddress</key><addressCountry>MX</addressCountry><addressLocality>Mexico City</addressLocality><addressRegion>CDMX</addressRegion></address></item></locations_raw><locations_alt_raw></locations_alt_raw><location_type></location_type><location_requirements_raw></location_requirements_raw><salary_raw></salary_raw><employment_type></employment_type><url>https://www.google.com/about/careers/applications/jobs/results/139898173249200838</url><source_type>ats</source_type><source>in-house</source><source_domain>google.com</source_domain><organization_logo></organization_logo><cities_derived><item>Mexico City</item></cities_derived><regions_derived><item>Ciudad de México</item></regions_derived><countries_derived><item>Mexico</item></countries_derived><locations_derived><item>Mexico City, Ciudad de México, Mexico</item></locations_derived><timezones_derived><item>America/Mexico_City</item></timezones_derived><lats_derived><item>19.4333</item></lats_derived><lngs_derived><item>-99.1333</item></lngs_derived><remote_derived>false</remote_derived><description_text>MINIMUM QUALIFICATIONS:

 * Bachelor’s degree or equivalent practical experience.
 * 2 years of experience with software development in one or more programming
   languages, or 1 year of experience with an advanced degree in an industry
   setting.
 * 2 years of experience with data structures or algorithms in either an
   academic or industry setting.



PREFERRED QUALIFICATIONS:

 * Experience with open source software and infrastructure development.
 * Experience in software development in one or more of the following languages:
   Python, C/C++, Java, Rust.
 * Experience with fuzzing and vulnerability research.
 * Knowledge of security engineering (e.g., memory safety issues).


ABOUT THE JOB:

Google&apos;s software engineers develop the next-generation technologies that change
how billions of users connect, explore, and interact with information and one
another. Our products need to handle information at massive scale, and extend
well beyond web search. We&apos;re looking for engineers who bring fresh ideas from
all areas, including information retrieval, distributed computing, large-scale
system design, networking and data storage, security, artificial intelligence,
natural language processing, UI design and mobile; the list goes on and is
growing every day. As a software engineer, you will work on a specific project
critical to Google’s needs with opportunities to switch teams and projects as
you and our fast-paced business grow and evolve. We need our engineers to be
versatile, display leadership qualities and be enthusiastic to take on new
problems across the full-stack as we continue to push technology forward.

In this role, with your technical expertise, you will manage project priorities,
deadlines, and deliverables. You will design, develop, test, deploy, maintain,
and enhance software solutions.Chrome is dedicated to building a better, more
open web. We’re focused on making a better browser (on both desktop and mobile)
to help users take advantage of all the web has to offer in a safe and secure
way.Chrome is available across all major platforms — iOS, Android, Windows, Mac,
Linux and Chrome OS. We also built Chrome as an open source project so the
entire web ecosystem could benefit from the latest innovations in speed,
simplicity and security.


RESPONSIBILITIES:

 * Write product or system development code.
 * Participate in, or lead design reviews with peers and stakeholders to decide
   amongst available technologies.
 * Review code developed by other developers and provide feedback to ensure best
   practices (e.g., style guidelines, checking code in, accuracy, testability,
   and efficiency).
 * Contribute to existing documentation or educational content and adapt content
   based on product/program updates and user feedback.
 * Triage product or system issues and debug/track/resolve by analyzing the
   sources of issues and the impact on hardware, network, or service operations
   and quality.</description_text></item><item><id>1690375229</id><date_posted>2025-05-23T00:00:00</date_posted><date_created>2025-05-23T20:52:36.657127</date_created><title>Senior Software Engineer, PeopleGraph</title><organization>People.ai</organization><organization_url></organization_url><date_validthrough></date_validthrough><locations_raw><item><key name="@type">Place</key><address><key name="@type">PostalAddress</key><addressLocality>Mexico City</addressLocality><addressRegion></addressRegion><addressCountry></addressCountry><postalCode></postalCode></address></item></locations_raw><locations_alt_raw></locations_alt_raw><location_type></location_type><location_requirements_raw></location_requirements_raw><salary_raw></salary_raw><employment_type><item>Contract</item></employment_type><url>https://jobs.lever.co/people-ai/8e6c2e57-153e-474f-acad-b93dad3361da</url><source_type>ats</source_type><source>lever.co</source><source_domain>jobs.lever.co</source_domain><organization_logo>https://lever-client-logos.s3.amazonaws.com/8454713f-116a-4252-acb9-04ea1e2c21f1-1579636243012.png</organization_logo><cities_derived><item>Mexico City</item></cities_derived><regions_derived><item>Ciudad de México</item></regions_derived><countries_derived><item>Mexico</item></countries_derived><locations_derived><item>Mexico City, Ciudad de México, Mexico</item></locations_derived><timezones_derived><item>America/Mexico_City</item></timezones_derived><lats_derived><item>19.4333</item></lats_derived><lngs_derived><item>-99.1333</item></lngs_derived><remote_derived>false</remote_derived><description_text>People.ai is an AI-powered foundational data platform that helps customers unlock go-to-market success &amp; growth by providing teams with solutions built specifically for their needs. Providing enhanced pipeline visibility, more actionable insights, and a single source of truth for all sales activities. People.ai’s unique dataset, consisting of trillions of sales activities, millions of deals, 160 million business contacts, and 69 approved patents related to AI-based business insights, sets the company apart. Companies such as Verizon, Red Hat, and Palo Alto Networks rely on their enterprise-ready, patented AI technology.

At People.ai, we believe that people enrich the world around them in countless ways. We believe that the more time they spend applying their creativity, resourcefulness, and critical thinking to activities that matter most in their professional life, the more effective a professional they become. Our team is a diverse, outspoken group of creatives and critical thinkers, hyper-focused on driving change and growth. We embrace “different”. We applaud non-traditional career paths. We&apos;re inspired by people who have made processes their own.

As a Senior Software Engineer on the PeopleGraph team, you will lead the development and optimization of our people data intelligence platform that gathers, cleanses, and analyzes information from diverse sources. You&apos;ll architect scalable solutions for our real-time API services and Databricks processing jobs while advancing our LLM-powered intelligence layer. You&apos;ll work autonomously to transform complex data challenges into elegant solutions, collaborate closely with Product teams to shape technical direction, and elevate our engineering excellence while delivering actionable people insights at scale.
\n

Responsibilities:
Design, develop, and maintain highly scalable microservices that power our real-time API for people data delivery.
Architect and implement LLM-based intelligence features for data analysis, classification, and information extraction.
Collaborate closely with Product teams to translate business requirements into technical solutions.
Work autonomously to identify technical gaps and opportunities for improvement in our architecture.
Implement monitoring, alerting, and observability systems to ensure reliability of critical services.
Mentor mid-level engineers and promote engineering excellence through code reviews and best practices.
Drive technical decision-making with a focus on maintainability, scalability, and performance.
Continuously refine our data cleaning and ranking algorithms to improve data quality.

Requirements:
Excellent problem-solving skills with focus on elegant and practical solutions.
5+ years of professional software engineering experience with demonstrated ability to write clean, maintainable code.
Strong proficiency in at least one programming language (Python preferred).
Experience with real-time data processing systems using technologies like Kafka.
Experience with big data processing using Spark or similar technologies in environments like Databricks.
Experience using Large Language Models (LLMs), familiarity with prompting techniques (chain-of-thought, RAG), and knowledge of common market models.
Ability to work independently, set technical direction, and collaborate closely with Product teams.
Strong communications skills and ability to thrive in a remote-first environment.
Bachelor’s Degree in Computer Science, Computer Engineering, or closely related discipline.


Nice to Have:
Experience with fine-tuning or advanced inference techniques for LLMs.
Background in data analysis and ability to derive insights from large datasets.


\n
$4,000 - $6,000 a month
\n
Headquartered in San Francisco, CA, People.ai is backed by Y Combinator and Silicon Valley’s top investors, including ICONIQ Capital, Andreessen Horowitz, Lightspeed Venture Partners, Akkadian Ventures, and Mubadala Capital. People.ai is listed in the top 20 percent of Inc 5000 companies, is a regular leader in our key categories on G2, and is on the Forbes list of America’s Best Startup Employers. For more information, please visit www.people.ai.</description_text></item><item><id>1690375228</id><date_posted>2025-05-23T00:00:00</date_posted><date_created>2025-05-23T20:52:36.589817</date_created><title>Senior Software Engineer, Data Modeling</title><organization>People.ai</organization><organization_url></organization_url><date_validthrough></date_validthrough><locations_raw><item><key name="@type">Place</key><address><key name="@type">PostalAddress</key><addressLocality>Mexico City</addressLocality><addressRegion></addressRegion><addressCountry></addressCountry><postalCode></postalCode></address></item></locations_raw><locations_alt_raw></locations_alt_raw><location_type></location_type><location_requirements_raw></location_requirements_raw><salary_raw></salary_raw><employment_type><item>Contract</item></employment_type><url>https://jobs.lever.co/people-ai/8c9c9785-35d6-4f4a-b374-b3e70eccfd09</url><source_type>ats</source_type><source>lever.co</source><source_domain>jobs.lever.co</source_domain><organization_logo>https://lever-client-logos.s3.amazonaws.com/8454713f-116a-4252-acb9-04ea1e2c21f1-1579636243012.png</organization_logo><cities_derived><item>Mexico City</item></cities_derived><regions_derived><item>Ciudad de México</item></regions_derived><countries_derived><item>Mexico</item></countries_derived><locations_derived><item>Mexico City, Ciudad de México, Mexico</item></locations_derived><timezones_derived><item>America/Mexico_City</item></timezones_derived><lats_derived><item>19.4333</item></lats_derived><lngs_derived><item>-99.1333</item></lngs_derived><remote_derived>false</remote_derived><description_text>People.ai is an AI-powered foundational data platform that helps customers unlock go-to-market success &amp; growth by providing teams with solutions built specifically for their needs. Providing enhanced pipeline visibility, more actionable insights, and a single source of truth for all sales activities. People.ai’s unique dataset, consisting of trillions of sales activities, millions of deals, 160 million business contacts, and 69 approved patents related to AI-based business insights, sets the company apart. They have a comprehensive list of top Fortune 500 companies that rely on their enterprise-ready, patented AI technology.

At People.ai, we believe that people enrich the world around them in countless ways. We believe that the more time they spend applying their creativity, resourcefulness, and critical thinking to activities that matter most in their professional life, the more effective a professional they become. Our team is a diverse, outspoken group of creatives and critical thinkers, hyper-focused on driving change and growth. We embrace different. We applaud non-traditional career paths. We&apos;re inspired by people who have made processes their own. 

As a Senior Software Engineer on the Data Modeling team, you will build and maintain a scalable and real-time architecture for processing vast amounts of data to power the next-generation of our LLM-based query engine (SalesAI) that will answer questions of various complexities and unlock rich insights for People.ai’s customers. You will also maintain and enhance our batch processing pipelines. You will collaborate across R&amp;D, leverage customer feedback, perform extensive data analysis, design and develop algorithms, storage formats, and APIs to unlock high performance and low latencies.

We value ownership highly — the ability to take an idea through all the stages from conception to shipping a product. This reflects throughout our company, but is especially true in engineering. As an engineer at People.ai, you&apos;ll be a part of a highly independent and autonomous team. Since we&apos;re building out a robust data layer that needs to be presented elegantly to the end-user, you&apos;ll be working with a large array of different technologies and fields. Expect lots of interesting challenges.
\n

Responsibilities:
Design and implement core backend services and data pipelines.
Ensure high data quality and accuracy of generated insights
Document design choices and operational knowledge to successfully deploy and run services.
Provide appropriate test coverage, unit and integration testing, with focus on performance and cost efficiency for your feature ownership areas.
Ensure robust alerting, dashboards, and runbooks for production services are in place.
Collaborate within the team and with other engineering teams to build new features and products according to business needs.
Follow software design and development best practices and promote such practices in the team.

Requirements:
5+ years of professional experience working on backend systems in an enterprise environment.
2+ years experience programming in Python 2.x/3.x or Scala or Java.
Professional experience with data analysis / data science tasks.
Experience with LLMs is a plus.
Understanding of SOA, microservices, and event-driven architecture.
Experience with an enterprise-grade stack for scalable web apps including messaging broker, in-memory storages, NoSQL, and key-value databases.
Strong knowledge of TDD, Unit, and automated test paradigms.
Experience with SQL and RDBMS solutions.
Experience with large-scale data processing (Spark).
Experience with Elasticsearch and/or Kafka is preferred.
Experience with containerized applications, Docker, and Kubernetes.
Possess a DevOps mindset, AWS experience is a plus.
Bachelor’s Degree in Computer Science, Computer Engineering, or in a closely related discipline.


\n
$4,000 - $6,000 a month
\n
Headquartered in San Francisco, CA, People.ai is backed by Y Combinator and Silicon Valley’s top investors, including ICONIQ Capital, Andreessen Horowitz, Lightspeed Venture Partners, Akkadian Ventures, and Mubadala Capital. People.ai is listed in the top 20 percent of Inc 5000 companies, is a regular leader in our key categories on G2, and is on the Forbes list of America’s Best Startup Employers. For more information, please visit www.people.ai.</description_text></item><item><id>1690375219</id><date_posted>2025-05-23T00:00:00</date_posted><date_created>2025-05-23T20:52:36.496461</date_created><title>Senior Software Engineer, Admin Experience</title><organization>People.ai</organization><organization_url></organization_url><date_validthrough></date_validthrough><locations_raw><item><key name="@type">Place</key><address><key name="@type">PostalAddress</key><addressLocality>Mexico City</addressLocality><addressRegion></addressRegion><addressCountry></addressCountry><postalCode></postalCode></address></item></locations_raw><locations_alt_raw></locations_alt_raw><location_type></location_type><location_requirements_raw></location_requirements_raw><salary_raw></salary_raw><employment_type><item>Contract</item></employment_type><url>https://jobs.lever.co/people-ai/3bcfdb1d-f0a5-45e5-a071-575045518b21</url><source_type>ats</source_type><source>lever.co</source><source_domain>jobs.lever.co</source_domain><organization_logo>https://lever-client-logos.s3.amazonaws.com/8454713f-116a-4252-acb9-04ea1e2c21f1-1579636243012.png</organization_logo><cities_derived><item>Mexico City</item></cities_derived><regions_derived><item>Ciudad de México</item></regions_derived><countries_derived><item>Mexico</item></countries_derived><locations_derived><item>Mexico City, Ciudad de México, Mexico</item></locations_derived><timezones_derived><item>America/Mexico_City</item></timezones_derived><lats_derived><item>19.4333</item></lats_derived><lngs_derived><item>-99.1333</item></lngs_derived><remote_derived>false</remote_derived><description_text>People.ai is an AI-powered foundational data platform that helps customers unlock go-to-market success &amp; growth by providing teams with solutions built specifically for their needs. Providing enhanced pipeline visibility, more actionable insights, and a single source of truth for all sales activities. People.ai’s unique dataset, consisting of trillions of sales activities, millions of deals, 160 million business contacts, and 69 approved patents related to AI-based business insights, sets the company apart. Companies such as Verizon, IBM Red Hat, Snowflake, Zoom, and Palo Alto Networks rely on their enterprise-ready, patented AI technology. 

At People.ai, we believe that people enrich the world around them in countless ways. We believe that the more time they spend applying their creativity, resourcefulness, and critical thinking to activities that matter most in their professional life, the more effective a professional they become. Our team is a diverse, outspoken group of creatives and critical thinkers, hyper-focused on driving change and growth. We embrace different. We applaud non-traditional career paths. We&apos;re inspired by people who have made processes their own. 

As an engineer within People.AI’s Application group you will be tasked with bringing People.AI custom-captured data to life through views and workflows that give reps, managers, and sales leaders superpowers. Our goal is to surface insights for these personas when and where they need them so they can take action and improve their sales outcomes. Amongst other media, you will help build first class web applications, embeddable experiences that work seamless in other partner environments, Chrome extensions, and more. 

We value ownership highly — the ability to take an idea through all the stages from conception to shipping a product. This reflects throughout our company, but is especially true in engineering. As an engineer atPeople.ai, you&apos;ll be a part of a highly independent and autonomous team. You will work with a modern web stack and a wide variety of technologies and user experiences that push the boundaries of what traditional sales personnel can do with their sales data. 
\n

Responsibilities:
Collaborate within the team and with other engineering teams to build new features and products according to business needs.
Document design choices and operational knowledge to successfully deploy and run workflows (and any supporting services)
Provide appropriate test coverage, unit and integration testing, with focus on performance, readability and maintainability for your feature ownership areas.
Follow software design and development best practices and promote such practices in the team.

Requirements:
5+ years of professional experience working with modern web stack (Typescript, React, etc)
Experience with data analysis is a plus
Experience with LLMs is a plus
Bachelor’s Degree in Computer Science, Computer Engineering, or in a closely related discipline


\n
$4,000 - $6,000 a month
\n
Headquartered in San Francisco, CA, People.ai is backed by Y Combinator and Silicon Valley’s top investors, including ICONIQ Capital, Andreessen Horowitz, Lightspeed Venture Partners, Akkadian Ventures, and Mubadala Capital. People.ai is listed in the top 20 percent of Inc 5000 companies, is a regular leader in our key categories on G2, and is on the Forbes list of America’s Best Startup Employers. For more information, please visit www.people.ai.</description_text></item><item><id>1690199552</id><date_posted>2025-05-23T00:00:00</date_posted><date_created>2025-05-23T18:42:51.355581</date_created><title>Software Engineer (Full stack)</title><organization>Takeda</organization><organization_url></organization_url><date_validthrough></date_validthrough><locations_raw><item><key name="@type">Place</key><address><key name="@type">PostalAddress</key><addressCountry>Mexico</addressCountry><addressLocality>MEX - Santa Fe</addressLocality></address></item></locations_raw><locations_alt_raw><item>MEX - Santa Fe</item></locations_alt_raw><location_type></location_type><location_requirements_raw></location_requirements_raw><salary_raw></salary_raw><employment_type><item>FULL_TIME</item></employment_type><url>https://takeda.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/External/job/MEX---Santa-Fe/Software-Engineer--Full-stack-_R0152660</url><source_type>ats</source_type><source>workday</source><source_domain>takeda.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com</source_domain><organization_logo></organization_logo><cities_derived></cities_derived><regions_derived></regions_derived><countries_derived><item>Mexico</item></countries_derived><locations_derived><item>Mexico</item></locations_derived><timezones_derived><item>America/Mexico_City</item></timezones_derived><lats_derived><item>19.4333</item></lats_derived><lngs_derived><item>-99.1333</item></lngs_derived><remote_derived>false</remote_derived><description_text>By clicking the “Apply” button, I understand that my employment application process with Takeda will commence and that the information I provide in my application will be processed in line with Takeda’s Privacy Notice and Terms of Use. I further attest that all information I submit in my employment application is true to the best of my knowledge. Job Description Software Engineer The Future Begins Here At Takeda, we are leading digital evolution and global transformation. By building innovative solutions and future-driven capabilities, we are improving the lives of millions of patients around the world. Mexico City has been selected to be home to Takeda’s recently launched Innovation Capability Center thanks to its international recognition in qualified and experienced talent in the data, digital and technology fields. We invite you to join our digital transformation journey. In this role, you will have the opportunity to boost your skills and become the heart of an innovative engine that is contributing to global impact and improvement. At Takeda’s ICC we Unite in Diversity Takeda is committed to creating an inclusive and collaborative workplace, where individuals are recognized for their backgrounds and abilities they bring to our company. We are continuously improving our collaborators journey in Takeda, and we welcome applications from all qualified candidates. Here, you will feel welcomed, respected, and valued as an important contributor to our diverse team. The Opportunity As a Software Engineer you will be responsible for transforming design and vision into working product and you will develop, customize, and enhance functionalities of diverse set of digital products. You will contribute to development of a cutting-edge platform that empowers our organization&apos;s digital capabilities. Responsibilities Deliver high-quality modern user experiences built in modern Front-End and Back-End (React, TypeScript, Node.js, Python) frameworks and libraries . Leverage best practices, Object Oriented JavaScript programming, Python and TypeScript frameworks. Develop and maintain scalable integrations using native AWS technologies to support continuing increases in data source, volume, and complexity. Builds systems of medium-to-high complexity with minimal guidance and supervision. Build interfaces for modern internet applications using the latest front-end technologies. Implement reusable libraries across applications. Ensure responsive design works across computing platforms. Develop application code and automated tests (unit and integration) in selected framework and/or library. Ensure high performance for global users through performance tests and tuning. Partner with the design team around usability and UI/UX concerns. Works closely with enterprise teams including Enterprise Architecture, Security, and Enterprise Data Backbone Engineering to design and develop data integration patterns/solutions along with proper data models supporting different data and analytics use cases. Collaborate with more senior team members to implement feedback on pull request reviews. Collaborate with agile team members to craft clear user stories and continuously deliver product increments. Continuously collaborate with Product Owner to demo developed functionality and validate against specified requirements. Estimate work based on user stories and functional requirements or wireframes. Contribute to Takeda’s mission by leading the development and adoption of solutions that deliver business outcomes and drive innovation. Leverage GitHub for CI/CD for all application development. Skills and Qualifications Bachelor’s degree in computer science, computer engineering, systems analysis or a related study. 4+ years relevant software development experience. Strong hands-on experience as a front-end and back-end engineer with following tech stack: JavaScript/TypeScript, React, Node.js, Python and HTML/CSS. Solid hands-on experience with SASS, CSS, HTML, and writing cross-browser compatible code. Hands-on experience with relational and non-relational databases (SQL, NoSQL). Hands-on experience or aptitude to learn workflow automation frameworks such as Power Automate. Experience with building and using APIs in codebase for data exchange, enabling custom workflows, and for event triggering between applications. Hands-on experience developing cloud native solutions on AWS (fundamentals such as Lambda, storage buckets, access management, and compute resources). Ability to communicate complex technical concepts. Self-starter with a passion for taking ownership of your work and delivering outcomes. Solid communication skills, a team player with a &apos;winning as a team&apos; attitude. Ability to continuously enhances own skills. Ability to write and speak in the English language. Practice efficient time management and coordinates tasks, working in an international environment. What Takeda’s ICC Can Offer You At Takeda, you take the lead on building and shaping your own career. Joining the ICC in Mexico City will give you access to high-end technology, continuous training and a diverse and inclusive network of colleagues who will support your career growth. It is our priority to provide competitive compensation and a benefit package that bridges your personal life with your professional career. Amongst our benefits are: Competitive Salary + Performance Annual Bonus Monthly Supermarket and Food Vouchers Flexible Working Schemes Comprehensive Healthcare Insurance Plans: Life, Medical, Dental &amp; Vision Additional Time Off Diversity, Equity, and Inclusion Programs If you have further inquiries on the ICC Mexico City or this role, follow us on LinkedIn, and look up for our upcoming online events where we will elaborate on open roles and host Q&amp;A sessions. Locations MEX - Santa Fe Worker Type Employee Worker Sub-Type Regular Time Type Full time Takeda is an industry-leading, global pharmaceutical company with an unwavering dedication to putting patients at the center of everything we do. We live our values of Takeda-ism – Integrity, Fairness, Honesty, and Perseverance – and are united by our mission to strive towards Better Health and a Brighter Future for people worldwide through leading innovation in medicine. Here, everyone matters and you will be a vital contributor to our inspiring, bold mission. At Takeda, you will make an impact on people’s lives – including your own. Takeda is an equal opportunity employer. For applicants of U.S and Puerto Rico positions: Click here to learn about our commitment to Equal Employment Opportunity (EEO). If you are limited in the ability to use our job application tool, or otherwise require a reasonable accommodation for a disability please click here.</description_text></item><item><id>1690014651</id><date_posted>2025-05-23T00:00:00</date_posted><date_created>2025-05-23T16:48:55.387382</date_created><title>Lead Software Engineer</title><organization>Petco</organization><organization_url></organization_url><date_validthrough></date_validthrough><locations_raw><item><key name="@type">Place</key><address><key name="@type">PostalAddress</key><addressCountry>Mexico</addressCountry><addressLocality>MSC</addressLocality></address></item></locations_raw><locations_alt_raw><item>MSC</item></locations_alt_raw><location_type></location_type><location_requirements_raw></location_requirements_raw><salary_raw></salary_raw><employment_type><item>FULL_TIME</item></employment_type><url>https://petco.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/External/job/MSC/Lead-Software-Engineer_R307035</url><source_type>ats</source_type><source>workday</source><source_domain>petco.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com</source_domain><organization_logo></organization_logo><cities_derived></cities_derived><regions_derived></regions_derived><countries_derived><item>Mexico</item></countries_derived><locations_derived><item>Mexico</item></locations_derived><timezones_derived><item>America/Mexico_City</item></timezones_derived><lats_derived><item>19.4333</item></lats_derived><lngs_derived><item>-99.1333</item></lngs_derived><remote_derived>false</remote_derived><description_text>Create a healthier, brighter future for pets, pet parents and people! If you want to make a real difference, create an exciting career path, feel welcome to be your whole self and nurture your wellbeing, Petco is the place for you. Our core values capture that spirit as we work to improve lives by doing what’s right for pets, people and our planet. We love all pets like our own We’re the future of the pet industry We’re here to improve lives We drive outstanding results together We’re welcome as we are Petco is a category-defining health and wellness company focused on improving the lives of pets, pet parents and Petco partners. We are 29,000 strong and operate 1,500+ pet care centers in the U.S., Mexico and Puerto Rico, including 250+ Vetco Total Care hospitals, hundreds of preventive care clinics and eight distribution centers. We’re focused on purpose-driven work, and strongly believe what’s good for pets, people and our planet is good for Petco. Technical Provide technical guidance and foster a collaborative and innovative environment. Drive the technical vision and strategy, ensure alignment with business goals. System Architecture: Contribute significantly to the design and evolution of the overall system architecture. Ensure that software solutions are scalable, maintainable, and aligned with best practices. Coding and Development: Participate actively in coding and development activities, setting high standards for code quality, efficiency, and innovation. Collaborate with cross-functional teams to define and implement robust software solutions. Code Review and Quality Assurance: Conduct thorough code reviews, providing constructive feedback to ensure code quality and adherence to coding standards. Oversee testing strategies to identify and address software defects. Project Leadership: Take ownership of projects, managing end-to-end development processes, timelines, and resources. Collaborate closely with product managers and stakeholders to understand requirements and deliver solutions. Documentation: Create and maintain comprehensive technical documentation related to software design, architecture, and development. Provide documentation for both technical and non-technical stakeholders. Collaboration and Communication: Foster a collaborative team culture, encouraging open communication and knowledge sharing. Communicate effectively with team members, stakeholders, and management on project status, technical decisions, and challenges. Continuous Learning: Stay updated on emerging technologies, industry trends, and best practices. Lead initiatives for continuous learning within the team and contribute to the enhancement of development processes. Qualifications: Bachelor&apos;s or Master&apos;s degree in Computer Science, Software Engineering, or a related field. 8+ years of proven experience as a software engineer or in a similar leadership role. Expertise in one or more programming languages (e.g., Java, C++, Python). Strong understanding of software architecture, design patterns, and best practices. Experience with version control systems (e.g., Git) and collaborative development workflows. Excellent problem-solving and analytical skills. Effective communication, leadership, and mentorship abilities. Preferred Qualifications: Experience with web development frameworks (e.g., React, Angular, Django). Knowledge of cloud computing platforms (e.g., AWS, Azure). Familiarity with containerization and orchestration tools (e.g., Docker, Kubernetes). Previous experience in developing and maintaining scalable and distributed systems. Proven experience in mentoring junior software developers Petco Animal Supplies, Inc. is an Equal Opportunity Employer. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, national origin, disability, age, protected veteran status, or any other protected classification. To translate this webpage to Spanish or other languages on your internet browser click the translate button to the right of your browser address bar. Additional instruction can be found here: https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/173424?hl=en-GB&amp;co=GENIE.Platform%3DDesktop Para traducir esta página web al español u otros idiomas en su navegador de Internet, haga clic en el botón de traducción a la derecha de la barra de direcciones de su navegador. Puede encontrar instrucciones adicionales aquí: https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/173424?hl=en-GB&amp;co=GENIE.Platform%3DDesktop Our vision at Petco is Healthier Pets. Happier People. Better World. We’re making things better for pets, people and the planet through our Think Adoption First philosophy, the Petco Foundation and other important initiatives that focus on putting animals first, educating pet parents and reducing our carbon footprint. The journey starts with knowledgeable, passionately engaged associates who are proud to recommend Petco as a place to work, who believe in our Vision and who are committed to delivering a superior customer experience. From our retail stores and our network of Distribution Centers to our Corporate offices, you&apos;ll work with others who share your values and commitment. We seek individuals who are passionate about animal welfare, have great people skills and are driven to grow and advance in their careers with us. Our ongoing growth is creating exceptional opportunities for professional development and personal enrichment throughout our organization.</description_text></item><item><id>1688227055</id><date_posted>2025-05-22T23:24:27</date_posted><date_created>2025-05-23T00:25:54.089573</date_created><title>Platform Software Engineer (Full Stack) - Contract</title><organization>Tech Holding</organization><organization_url></organization_url><date_validthrough></date_validthrough><locations_raw><item><key name="@type">Place</key><name>Mexico, Remote</name><address><key name="@type">PostalAddress</key><name>Mexico, Remote</name><addressCountry></addressCountry><addressLocality>Mexico, Remote</addressLocality></address></item></locations_raw><locations_alt_raw></locations_alt_raw><location_type></location_type><location_requirements_raw></location_requirements_raw><salary_raw></salary_raw><employment_type></employment_type><url>https://job-boards.greenhouse.io/techholding/jobs/4568690005</url><source_type>ats</source_type><source>greenhouse</source><source_domain>job-boards.greenhouse.io</source_domain><organization_logo></organization_logo><cities_derived></cities_derived><regions_derived></regions_derived><countries_derived><item>Mexico</item></countries_derived><locations_derived><item>Mexico</item></locations_derived><timezones_derived><item>America/Mexico_City</item></timezones_derived><lats_derived><item>19.4333</item></lats_derived><lngs_derived><item>-99.1333</item></lngs_derived><remote_derived>true</remote_derived><description_text>About us:
Working at Tech Holding isn&apos;t just a job, it&apos;s an opportunity to be a part of something bigger. We are a full-service consulting firm that was founded on the premise of delivering predictable outcomes and high-quality solutions to our clients. Our founders and team members have industry experience and have held senior positions in a wide variety of companies – from emerging startups to large Fortune 50 firms – and we have taken our combined experiences and developed a unique approach that is supported by the principles of deep expertise, integrity, transparency, and dependability.
The Role
As a Platform Software Engineer, you will work with a team of talented software developers to expand and mature a kitchen automation system and cloud-connected infrastructure. You will perform hard-core coding, debugging, testing, and troubleshooting throughout the development process. You will use your expertise in software engineering to own the design, prototype, and commercialization of core software. You will collaborate closely with robotics specialists in controls, machine learning, and computer vision.
What You’ll Do
Code, debug, test and troubleshoot software throughout the development process.
Develop sophisticated state machines that efficiently manage and optimize various cooking 
workflows.
Engineer streamlined, user-friendly procedures for robotic system installations ensuring a smooth 
user experience.
Design and implement robust monitoring solutions to continuously track and ensure the health of 
our robotic systems in various environments.
Use best engineering judgment to iterate on code and refactoring repeatedly to improve our 
software generality and quality.
Read our code and documentation to understand our existing architecture and practices.
Adhere to and help improve our software development lifecycle (SDLC) processes.
Take ownership when developing, maintaining, improving, testing and releasing software.
Create unit tests and system-level tests to verify code functionality.
Create architectural diagrams that demonstrate flow of data through the system.
Requirements
BS or higher in Computer Science (or related field) and 2+ years of relevant industry experience
Experience in system software, network stacks, state machines, and SQL databases for robotic 
systems
Python programming expertise and familiarity with C++
Proficiency in developing applications in the Robot Operating System (ROS)
Proficiency with working in development environments that comprise of Linux, Docker, and Git
Self-motivated, responsible, and excellent written and verbal interpersonal skills
Ability to collaborate effectively as a remote team member
Strong attention to detail, analytical skills, and ability to learn quickly
Collaborative team player with a drive to take initiative and ownership
Must be available to work in Pacific Time (PT) zone
Preferred Qualifications
Experience with cloud and edge computing
Experience developing platforms that serve multiple robotic products
What We Offer
Remote opportunity with collaborative team culture
Exposure to cloud-first environments and modern DevOps tooling
Opportunities for growth and cross-functional impact
Dynamic and fast-paced engineering environment
Tech Holding is proud to be an Equal Opportunity Employer and is committed to fostering a diverse and inclusive workplace. We welcome applicants from all backgrounds and experiences, and we consider qualified applicants without regard to race, color, religion, gender, sexual orientation, gender identity, national origin, disability, veteran status, or any other legally protected characteristic. If you require accommodation in the application process, please contact our HR</description_text></item><item><id>1687606707</id><date_posted>2025-05-22T19:09:03</date_posted><date_created>2025-05-22T19:17:33.769764</date_created><title>Senior Data &amp; Software Engineer</title><organization>Kunai</organization><organization_url></organization_url><date_validthrough></date_validthrough><locations_raw><item><key name="@type">Place</key><name>Remote - Mexico</name><address><key name="@type">PostalAddress</key><name>Remote - Mexico</name><addressCountry></addressCountry><addressLocality>Remote - Mexico</addressLocality></address></item></locations_raw><locations_alt_raw></locations_alt_raw><location_type></location_type><location_requirements_raw></location_requirements_raw><salary_raw></salary_raw><employment_type></employment_type><url>https://job-boards.greenhouse.io/kunai/jobs/4742672007</url><source_type>ats</source_type><source>greenhouse</source><source_domain>job-boards.greenhouse.io</source_domain><organization_logo></organization_logo><cities_derived></cities_derived><regions_derived></regions_derived><countries_derived><item>Mexico</item></countries_derived><locations_derived><item>Mexico</item></locations_derived><timezones_derived><item>America/Mexico_City</item></timezones_derived><lats_derived><item>19.4333</item></lats_derived><lngs_derived><item>-99.1333</item></lngs_derived><remote_derived>true</remote_derived><description_text>Kunai builds full-stack technology solutions for banks, credit and payment networks, infrastructure providers, and their customers. Together, we are changing the world’s relationship with financial services. At Kunai, we help our clients modernize, capitalize on emerging trends, and evolve their business for the coming decades by remaining tech-agnostic and human-centered.
Kunai is working with a major credit card organization in Mexico City, to build the platform that companies use to manage their corporate card program. This includes everything from applying for a card, to upgrades, payments, statements, reward points - the whole thing end to end. We will build on a modern tech stack, pushing to the cloud, and have a lot of fun while we get there.
In this role, you will oversee all technical aspects of the databases for a Global Corporate Client Platform, that powers not only the global work suite of applications, but over 75 mission critical applications. This role requires a deep understanding of database architectures and hands-on experience with database technologies, preferably PostgreSQL as that is our target technology in the modernization initiatives. Successful candidates will ensure strong control management, proactive risk management, optimal database performance, security, resiliency, integrity, and availability, along with implementing innovative solutions such as the Point of Arrival (POA) system for the data layer.
Experience
6+ years of software development experience in a professional environment and/or comparable experience including: 
A wide breadth of engineering experience
Proven experience working with teams of engineers
Hands-on expertise with application design, software development, and automated testing
Experience with distributed (multi-tiered) systems, algorithms, and relational databases
Experience in database development, tuning, and administration
Qualifications
Bachelor’s degree in computer science, computer science engineering, or related experience required; advanced degree preferred
3+ years of hands-on Java development
3+ years working with PostgreSQL
Experience in API design and Architecture, SOAP and REST
Experience in Database modernization or Migration
Nice to have
Hands-on knowledge of Spark
Experience in Scala development
Experience with Systems of Record (SOR)
Prior experience migrating from legacy (the current environment is DB2) data environments 
This is a primarily a remote role, but will require going a couple of days a month to the CDMX office
Our success over the past 20 years is rooted in our exceptional team, which thrives in a culture of collaboration, creativity, and continuous learning. 

We are proud to offer our employees a range of benefits, including competitive compensation, professional development opportunities, and flexible work arrangements, all designed to help them thrive. As we continue to expand, we remain committed to cultivating an environment where people feel valued, have a voice, and are given the tools to grow—both personally and professionally—while pushing the boundaries of innovation in the fintech industry.</description_text></item><item><id>1687477088</id><date_posted>2025-05-22T17:31:01.15</date_posted><date_created>2025-05-22T18:25:30.426983</date_created><title>Software Engineer, Chrome Accessibility</title><organization>Google</organization><organization_url>https://www.google.com</organization_url><date_validthrough></date_validthrough><locations_raw><item><key name="@type">Place</key><address><key name="@type">PostalAddress</key><addressCountry>MX</addressCountry><addressLocality>Mexico City</addressLocality><addressRegion>CDMX</addressRegion></address></item></locations_raw><locations_alt_raw></locations_alt_raw><location_type></location_type><location_requirements_raw></location_requirements_raw><salary_raw></salary_raw><employment_type></employment_type><url>https://www.google.com/about/careers/applications/jobs/results/109029229680566982</url><source_type>ats</source_type><source>in-house</source><source_domain>google.com</source_domain><organization_logo></organization_logo><cities_derived><item>Mexico City</item></cities_derived><regions_derived><item>Ciudad de México</item></regions_derived><countries_derived><item>Mexico</item></countries_derived><locations_derived><item>Mexico City, Ciudad de México, Mexico</item></locations_derived><timezones_derived><item>America/Mexico_City</item></timezones_derived><lats_derived><item>19.4333</item></lats_derived><lngs_derived><item>-99.1333</item></lngs_derived><remote_derived>false</remote_derived><description_text>MINIMUM QUALIFICATIONS:

 * Bachelor’s degree or equivalent practical experience.
 * 2 years of experience with data structures/algorithms and software
   development in one or more programming languages.



PREFERRED QUALIFICATIONS:

 * Master&apos;s degree or PhD in Computer Science or related technical fields.
 * Experience developing accessible technologies.
 * Experience with C++, JavaScript and Web Applications.
 * Experience with Chrome and Chrome OS.


ABOUT THE JOB:

Google&apos;s software engineers develop the next-generation technologies that change
how billions of users connect, explore, and interact with information and one
another. Our products need to handle information at massive scale, and extend
well beyond web search. We&apos;re looking for engineers who bring fresh ideas from
all areas, including information retrieval, distributed computing, large-scale
system design, networking and data storage, security, artificial intelligence,
natural language processing, UI design and mobile; the list goes on and is
growing every day. As a software engineer, you will work on a specific project
critical to Google’s needs with opportunities to switch teams and projects as
you and our fast-paced business grow and evolve. We need our engineers to be
versatile, display leadership qualities and be enthusiastic to take on new
problems across the full-stack as we continue to push technology forward.

As a Software Engineer working with the Chrome Accessibility team, you will help
us make Chrome universally accessible and useful. Without the things we build,
some users wouldn’t be able to use Chrome at all. We are focused on opening new
possibilities for these users and making new experiences possible for them.
Going beyond just enabling people to use our products and services, we want to
find new ways to become a companion in people’s lives. Your projects will have
crucial impact on these users as you address hard technical problems and
coordinate with many teams at Google to find solutions that make Chrome an
amazing platform for everyone.

Chrome is dedicated to building a better, more open web. We’re focused on making
a better browser (on both desktop and mobile) to help users take advantage of
all the web has to offer in a safe and secure way.Chrome is available across all
major platforms — iOS, Android, Windows, Mac, Linux and Chrome OS. We also built
Chrome as an open source project so the entire web ecosystem could benefit from
the latest innovations in speed, simplicity and security.


RESPONSIBILITIES:

 * Work closely with UX designers, Product Managers, and other engineers to
   define, design, and implement accessibility and immersive reading features.
 * Work on Chrome browser features to improve the experience for users with
   disabilities, including those who rely on third-party assistive technology.
 * Build and improve Chrome OS platform features for users with disabilities,
   including screen reading, braille support, magnification, color enhancement,
   and more.
 * Improve the web platform with tools and APIs to help developers make their
   web apps accessible to everyone.
 * Stay up-to-date with the latest accessibility standards and best practices.</description_text></item><item><id>1687120227</id><date_posted>2025-05-22T15:21:18.685</date_posted><date_created>2025-05-22T15:25:06.825038</date_created><title>Software Engineer II - Android</title><organization>McDonald&apos;s Corporation</organization><organization_url></organization_url><date_validthrough></date_validthrough><locations_raw><item><address><streetAddress>Calz. Gral. Mariano Escobedo 595 Rincón del Bosque, Bosque de Chapultepec I Secc, Miguel Hidalgo</streetAddress><addressLocality>Ciudad de México</addressLocality><postalCode>11580</postalCode><addressCountry>Mexico</addressCountry></address></item></locations_raw><locations_alt_raw><item>Calz. Gral. Mariano Escobedo 595 Rincón del Bosque, Bosque de Chapultepec I Secc, Miguel Hidalgo, Ciudad de México, Mexico</item></locations_alt_raw><location_type></location_type><location_requirements_raw></location_requirements_raw><salary_raw></salary_raw><employment_type><item>Full-time</item></employment_type><url>https://jobs.smartrecruiters.com/McDonaldsCorporation/744000061017575-software-engineer-ii-android</url><source_type>ats</source_type><source>smartrecruiters</source><source_domain>jobs.smartrecruiters.com</source_domain><organization_logo></organization_logo><cities_derived><item>Mexico City</item></cities_derived><regions_derived><item>Ciudad de México</item></regions_derived><countries_derived><item>Mexico</item></countries_derived><locations_derived><item>Mexico City, Ciudad de México, Mexico</item></locations_derived><timezones_derived><item>America/Mexico_City</item></timezones_derived><lats_derived><item>19.4333</item></lats_derived><lngs_derived><item>-99.1333</item></lngs_derived><remote_derived>false</remote_derived><description_text>Company DescriptionMcDonald’s growth strategy, Accelerating the Arches, encompasses all aspects of our business as the leading global omni-channel restaurant brand. As the consumer landscape shifts we are using our competitive advantages to further strengthen our brand. One of our core growth strategies is to Double Down on the 3Ds (Delivery, Digital and Drive Thru). McDonald’s will accelerate technology innovation so 65M+ customers a day will experience a fast, easy experience, whether at one of our 25,000 and growing Drive Thrus, through McDelivery, dine-in or takeaway.  McDonald’s Global Technology is here to power tomorrow’s feel-good moments.  That’s why you’ll find us at the forefront of transformative technology, exploring new and innovative ways to serve our millions of customers and spread happiness one delicious Hot Fudge Sundae-dipped fry at a time. Using AI, robotics and emerging tech, we’re digitizing the Golden Arches. Combine that with our unparalleled global scale, and we’re reshaping all areas of the business, industry and every community that is home to a McDonald’s restaurant. We face complex tech challenges every day. But that’s where our diverse and talented teams come in. They’re made up of the best and brightest from all over the globe, and they thrive in the space where feel-good meets fast-paced.  We’re recruiting engineers to join our Global Technology team in Mexico City as we open our McDonald&apos;s in Mexico office. Our Mexico City office will be a hub for technology innovation and operational support to help us build the solutions that will improve our customer, crew and employee experience each and every day. Check out the McDonald’s  Global Technology Technical Blog to learn how technology and our global team are directly enabling the Accelerating the Arches strategy. Job DescriptionContribute to all aspects of the agile development life cycle including design, development, documentation, testing and operations.As a software development engineer on a team, you will play a pivotal role in shaping the definition, vision, design, road map and development of product features from beginning to end.Design, implement, test, deploy and maintain innovative software solutions to transform service performance, durability, cost, and security.Use software engineering best practices to ensure a high standard of quality for all team deliverables.Work in an agile, startup-like development environment, where you are always working on the most important priorities.Qualifications2+ years of non-internship professional software development experience.Extensive programming experience with Kotlin, Java, and Android platform technologies and APIs.Bachelor’s Degree in Computer Science or related field or equivalent years of experience.Solid knowledge of Computer Science fundamentals (object-oriented design, data structures and algorithm.Strong verbal and written communication skills.Solution-oriented attitude and ability to solve tough problems in a collaborative, cross-functional, and fast-paced environment.Demonstrated leadership abilities in an engineering environment in driving operational excellence and best practices.Highly quantitative with great judgment and passion for building a great customer experience.Uncompromising attention to detail and drive to continuously improve the product.Ability to take a project from scoping requirements to launch to delivery.#LI-Hybrid</description_text></item><item><id>1687809345</id><date_posted>2025-05-22T00:00:00</date_posted><date_created>2025-05-22T20:49:31.6896</date_created><title>Senior Software Engineer</title><organization>TigerConnect</organization><organization_url></organization_url><date_validthrough></date_validthrough><locations_raw><item><key name="@type">Place</key><address><key name="@type">PostalAddress</key><addressCountry>Mexico</addressCountry><addressLocality>Mexico City</addressLocality></address></item></locations_raw><locations_alt_raw><item>Hybrid - Mexico City, Mexico</item></locations_alt_raw><location_type></location_type><location_requirements_raw></location_requirements_raw><salary_raw></salary_raw><employment_type><item>FULL_TIME</item></employment_type><url>https://tigerconnect.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/TC/job/Hybrid---Mexico-City-Mexico/Senior-Software-Engineer_R003053</url><source_type>ats</source_type><source>workday</source><source_domain>tigerconnect.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com</source_domain><organization_logo></organization_logo><cities_derived><item>Mexico City</item></cities_derived><regions_derived><item>Ciudad de México</item></regions_derived><countries_derived><item>Mexico</item></countries_derived><locations_derived><item>Mexico City, Ciudad de México, Mexico</item></locations_derived><timezones_derived><item>America/Mexico_City</item></timezones_derived><lats_derived><item>19.4333</item></lats_derived><lngs_derived><item>-99.1333</item></lngs_derived><remote_derived>false</remote_derived><description_text>TigerConnect transforms healthcare with the industry’s most widely adopted clinical collaboration platform – uniquely modernizing the way doctors, nurses, care teams, patients, and data connect. With solutions spanning care team communication, scheduling automation, alarm management and event notifications, nurse call, patient engagement and more, we accelerate productivity, reduce costs, and improve patient outcomes, safely and securely. More than 8,000 healthcare organizations trust us to deliver enterprise-ready solutions, making this possible with the right group of dedicated, thoughtful trailblazers. Today, private practice doctor’s offices, small and large hospice centers, and some of the largest healthcare organizations in the United States rely on TigerConnect. We’re a fun, hungry, smart, innovative group of eclectic people who are passionate about transforming the way clinical care teams work and communicate. TigerConnect transforms healthcare with the industry’s most widely adopted clinical collaboration platform – uniquely modernizing the way doctors, nurses, care teams, patients, and data connect. With solutions spanning care team communication, scheduling automation, alarm management and event notifications, nurse call, patient engagement and more, we accelerate productivity, reduce costs, and improve patient outcomes, safely and securely. More than 8,000 healthcare organizations trust us to deliver enterprise-ready solutions, making this possible with the right group of dedicated, thoughtful trailblazers. Today, private practice doctor’s offices, small and large hospice centers, and some of the largest healthcare organizations in the United States rely on TigerConnect. We’re a fun, hungry, smart, innovative group of eclectic people who are passionate about transforming the way clinical care teams work and communicate. TigerConnect is looking for an experienced Senior JavaScript Engineer to join our team and help build a platform used by thousands of first responders, nurses, and doctors. You will play a leading role in all aspects of our platform development including REST API, MongoDB configuration, AWS DevOps, Android and iOS development. Above all, your work will impact the way hospitals save lives during an emergency. What You’ll Be Doing: Lead the design and development of scalable backend services using Node.js and TypeScript Architect and implement RESTful APIs to support mobile and web applications Configure and manage MongoDB databases, ensuring optimal performance and data integrity Collaborate with cross-functional teams to integrate cloud infrastructure solutions, particularly within AWS environments Develop and maintain front-end components using modern JavaScript frameworks such as Vue or React Participate in test-driven development practices, including pair programming and mobbing sessions Utilize AI tools to enhance development workflows and code quality Mentor team members, fostering a culture of continuous learning and knowledge sharing What You Bring: 8+ years professional experience with JavaScript and Typescript, with minimum of 4 years professional experience with enterprise scale platform development using Node.js Experience configuring and maintaining cloud infrastructure (preferably with AWS) Experience with front end JavaScript development in any of the following JS frameworks (Vue, React) Experience with App development in any of the following JS frameworks (iOS, Android, Flutter) All development is done with pairing and mobbing with TDD. You MUST have experience in this type of environment Experience using AI to augment development and coding You&apos;re a team player who actively teaches the team in areas where you are skilled while showing an eagerness to step out of your comfort zone and learn completely unfamiliar things by engaging with the team and asking for help in the areas where you&apos;re not as skilled Perks &amp; Benefits We Offer: Join us in our prime office space in the heart of Mexico City&apos;s Reforma area; Our hybrid teams unite top talent from Mexico, the US, and beyond, offering flexibility and collaboration Enjoy our comprehensive benefits with excellent private medical, dental, vision, and life insurance coverage for you and your family Focus on your well-being through our wellness reimbursement program and company-wide wellness days (extra days off to rest and recharge) Take advantage of extra perks and benefits, including a savings fund, monthly teleworking allowance, grocery vouchers, and travel insurance In addition to the minimum days off required by law, our Flexible Time Off program gives you extra time to enjoy the things you love Join a mission-driven team committed to making a real impact in the world of healthcare Our mission is to provide a healthcare communication solution that radically improves the way care is delivered. We’ve been recognized as one of the Best Places to Work in Los Angeles (2022), as well as on the list of Best Paying Companies (2022) with the Best Perks &amp; Benefits (2022). We were also honored to be named to Inc. 5000’s list of Fastest Growing Companies. TigerConnect is an equal opportunity employer and values diversity at our company! We do not discriminate on the basis of race, religion, color, national origin, sex, gender, gender expression, sexual orientation, age, marital status, veteran status, or disability status. We will ensure that individuals with disabilities are provided reasonable accommodation to participate in the job application or interview process, to perform essential job functions, and to receive other benefits and privileges of employment. Please contact us to request accommodation. TigerConnect is on a mission to transform and improve communication and workflows in hospitals and the healthcare industry overall. This is without a doubt a tall task, but one that we’ve been solving since 2010 and will continue to tackle with the right group of dedicated, thoughtful trailblazers. Headquartered in Santa Monica, California, and with team members across seven countries, TigerConnect believes that the people building and supporting our products are the core to our success. From our outstanding benefits package to our focus on mental health &amp; wellbeing to our life-saving products — working at TigerConnect allows you to build partnerships and truly make an impact on how healthcare communication is delivered.</description_text></item><item><id>1687687973</id><date_posted>2025-05-22T00:00:00</date_posted><date_created>2025-05-22T19:54:37.972119</date_created><title>Senior Software Engineer - Java, Fullstack</title><organization>3Pillar</organization><organization_url></organization_url><date_validthrough></date_validthrough><locations_raw><item><key name="@type">Place</key><address><key name="@type">PostalAddress</key><addressLocality>Mexico</addressLocality><addressRegion></addressRegion><addressCountry></addressCountry><postalCode></postalCode></address></item></locations_raw><locations_alt_raw></locations_alt_raw><location_type></location_type><location_requirements_raw></location_requirements_raw><salary_raw></salary_raw><employment_type><item>Full-time</item></employment_type><url>https://jobs.lever.co/3pillarglobal/7e92a873-7052-4958-9e0c-dcb3fead285c</url><source_type>ats</source_type><source>lever.co</source><source_domain>jobs.lever.co</source_domain><organization_logo>https://lever-client-logos.s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/ac642534-49c7-4e52-9580-2c59423836cb-1723212200858.png</organization_logo><cities_derived></cities_derived><regions_derived></regions_derived><countries_derived><item>Mexico</item></countries_derived><locations_derived><item>Mexico</item></locations_derived><timezones_derived><item>America/Mexico_City</item></timezones_derived><lats_derived><item>19.4333</item></lats_derived><lngs_derived><item>-99.1333</item></lngs_derived><remote_derived>false</remote_derived><description_text>👋 Greetings, future tech savant: 

Embark on an exciting journey into the realm of software development with 3Pillar! We extend an invitation for you to join our team and gear up for a thrilling adventure. At 3Pillar, our focus is on crafting cutting-edge technologies that revolutionize industries. As a DevOps Engineer, you&apos;ll play a vital role in our dynamic team, contributing to exciting projects that redefine urban living, establish new media channels for enterprise companies, or drive innovation in healthcare. This opportunity goes beyond code – it&apos;s about creating epic solutions that leave a lasting impression in the market. If your passion for programming fuels your drive to make a real-world impact, consider this your pass to the captivating world of Product Development! 🚀💻

WE ARE 3PILLAR GLOBAL

At 3Pillar, culture is more than a buzzword. The power of culture, teamwork, and open collaboration drives our commitment to building breakthrough software solutions that power digital businesses. Our passion for software development has gained us recognition in some of the industry’s most innovative spaces, including a spot on the Inc. 5000 list ten years in a row, a three time winner of the Washington Post Top Workplaces Award, and notable features in Forbes, Fortune, and the Washington Business Journal. 

We are an innovative software development partner whose solutions drive rapid revenue, market share, customer growth and employee efficiency for industry leaders in Media and Publishing, Information Services, Banking and Financial Services, Insurance and Healthcare.
Our key differentiator is our Product Mindset. Our development teams focus on building for outcomes and all of our team members around the globe are trained on the Product Mindset’s core values – Minimize Time to Value, Solve For Need, and Excel at Change. Our business-minded approach to agile development ensures that we align to client goals from the earliest conceptual stages through launch and beyond. 

WHAT WE BELIEVE

At 3Pillar, our core values – Intrinsic Dignity, Outsized Impact, Open Collaboration, and Continuous Improvement – drive our commitment to providing best-in-class software development services to high-growth businesses across the globe. We’ve spent more than fifteen years building innovative software solutions. Our executive team has always held our values to the highest standard which has led to active participation on the Forbes Tech Council, a winner of the Ernst &amp; Young Entrepreneur of the Year Award, and a spot on the Washington Business Journal’s Women Who Mean Business list.
\n

Key Responsibilities:
Craft client code that is not just efficient but also performant, testable, scalable, secure, and of the highest quality.
Provide accurate status tracking, reporting, and estimation using project methods and tools.
Gather requirements, validate their understanding amongst the team, and create and maintain relevant documentation.
Execute activities within the current methodology and uphold the highest quality standards.
Foster collaboration with fellow engineers, designers, and managers to comprehend user pain points and iterate on solutions that drive client success.
Take ownership of projects, from technical design to a successful launch.


Key Responsibilities:
Demonstrated expertise with a minimum of 2+ years of experience in at least one of the specified technologies.
Java 17+
Spring boot, JPA
AWS
DB2
Aurora
Azure
Microservices
Reactive Programming
Ideally with knowledge of mobile development (Mobile First / Flutter)
Beginner- to intermediate-level design proficiency following UML/C4/ArchiMate.
Experience in engineering software systems of medium-to-large scope and complexity.
Familiarity with Agile software development methodologies.
Proficiency with relational databases and SQL.
Experience in building frontend/backend applications at scale.
Proficiency in the English language.


Benefits:
Medical Insurance benefits as per company policy. 
Life Insurance as per company policy
15 days of paid vacation plus additional days based on tenure
Vacation bonus as per local law
Sick leave and paid holidays as per local law
Profit sharing as per local law
Paternity and maternity leave as per as per local law
Marriage, bereavement and graduation leaves as per company policy
Christmas bonuses as per local law
Work from home allowance as per company policy
Punctuality and attendance bonuses as per company policy
Food tickets as per company policy
Direct deposit of payroll.
Paid professional certifications

#Li-Remote

\n</description_text></item><item><id>1687377359</id><date_posted>2025-05-22T00:00:00</date_posted><date_created>2025-05-22T17:44:39.507895</date_created><title>Senior Software Engineer</title><organization>Capital One</organization><organization_url></organization_url><date_validthrough></date_validthrough><locations_raw><item><key name="@type">Place</key><address><key name="@type">PostalAddress</key><addressCountry>Mexico</addressCountry><addressLocality>Ciudad de Mexico</addressLocality></address></item></locations_raw><locations_alt_raw><item>Mexico City, Mexico</item></locations_alt_raw><location_type></location_type><location_requirements_raw></location_requirements_raw><salary_raw></salary_raw><employment_type><item>FULL_TIME</item></employment_type><url>https://capitalone.wd12.myworkdayjobs.com/Capital_One/job/Mexico-City-Mexico/Senior-Software-Engineer_R200159</url><source_type>ats</source_type><source>workday</source><source_domain>capitalone.wd12.myworkdayjobs.com</source_domain><organization_logo></organization_logo><cities_derived><item>Mexico City</item></cities_derived><regions_derived><item>Ciudad de México</item></regions_derived><countries_derived><item>Mexico</item></countries_derived><locations_derived><item>Mexico City, Ciudad de México, Mexico</item></locations_derived><timezones_derived><item>America/Mexico_City</item></timezones_derived><lats_derived><item>19.4333</item></lats_derived><lngs_derived><item>-99.1333</item></lngs_derived><remote_derived>false</remote_derived><description_text>WeWork Reforma Latino (97001), Mexico, Ciudad de Mexico, Ciudad de Mexico Senior Software Engineer Do you love building and pioneering in the technology space? Do you enjoy solving complex business problems in a fast-paced, collaborative, inclusive, and iterative delivery environment? At Capital One, you&apos;ll be part of a big group of makers, breakers, doers and disruptors, who solve real problems and meet real customer needs. We are seeking Full Stack Software Engineers who are passionate about marrying data with emerging technologies. As a Capital One Senior Software Engineer, you’ll have the opportunity to be on the forefront of driving a major transformation within Capital One. What You’ll Do: Collaborate with and across Agile teams to design, develop, test, implement, and support technical solutions in full-stack development tools and technologies Share your passion for staying on top of tech trends, experimenting with and learning new technologies, participating in internal &amp; external technology communities, mentoring other members of the engineering community Collaborate with digital product managers, and deliver robust cloud-based solutions that drive powerful experiences to help millions of Americans achieve financial empowerment Utilize programming languages like JavaScript, Java, HTML/CSS, TypeScript, SQL, Python, and Go, Open Source RDBMS and NoSQL databases, Container Orchestration services including Docker and Kubernetes, and a variety of AWS tools and services Basic Qualifications: Bachelor’s Degree At least 2 years of experience in software engineering (Internship experience does not apply) Preferred Qualifications: At least 5 years of experience in at least one of the following: JavaScript, Java, TypeScript, SQL, Python, or Go At least 1 year of experience with AWS, GCP, Microsoft Azure, or another cloud service At least 3 years of experience in open source frameworks At least 2 years of experience in Agile practices At this time, Capital One will not sponsor a new applicant for employment authorization for this position. At Capital One, we respect individual differences in culture, religion, and ethnicity. Likewise, we promote equal opportunities and development for all personnel. In the hiring process, we seek to provide equal employment opportunities to candidates, regardless of race, color, religion, gender, sexual orientation, marital or civil status, national origin, disability, or any other situation protected by federal, state, or local laws. For technical support or questions about Capital One&apos;s recruiting process, please send an email to Careers@capitalone.com Capital One does not provide, endorse nor guarantee and is not liable for third-party products, services, educational tools or other information available through this site. Capital One Financial is made up of several different entities. Please note that any position posted in Canada is for Capital One Canada, any position posted in the United Kingdom is for Capital One Europe, any position posted in the Philippines is for Capital One Service Corp (COPSSC), and any position posted in Mexico is for Capital One Technology Labs Mexico. At Capital One, we’re building a leading information-based technology company. Still founder-led by Chairman and Chief Executive Officer Richard Fairbank, Capital One is on a mission to help our customers succeed by bringing ingenuity, simplicity, and humanity to banking. We measure our efforts by the success our customers enjoy and the advocacy they exhibit.</description_text></item><item><id>1687240396</id><date_posted>2025-05-22T00:00:00</date_posted><date_created>2025-05-22T16:50:57.860178</date_created><title>Automation Software Engineer</title><organization>Flex</organization><organization_url></organization_url><date_validthrough></date_validthrough><locations_raw><item><key name="@type">Place</key><address><key name="@type">PostalAddress</key><addressCountry>Mexico</addressCountry><addressLocality>Guadalajara North, Mexico</addressLocality></address></item></locations_raw><locations_alt_raw><item>Mexico, Guadalajara</item></locations_alt_raw><location_type></location_type><location_requirements_raw></location_requirements_raw><salary_raw></salary_raw><employment_type><item>FULL_TIME</item></employment_type><url>https://flextronics.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/Careers/job/Mexico-Guadalajara/Automation-Software-Engineer_WD201282-1</url><source_type>ats</source_type><source>workday</source><source_domain>flextronics.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com</source_domain><organization_logo></organization_logo><cities_derived><item>Guadalajara</item></cities_derived><regions_derived><item>Jalisco</item></regions_derived><countries_derived><item>Mexico</item></countries_derived><locations_derived><item>Guadalajara, Jalisco, Mexico</item></locations_derived><timezones_derived><item>America/Mexico_City</item></timezones_derived><lats_derived><item>20.6767</item></lats_derived><lngs_derived><item>-103.3475</item></lngs_derived><remote_derived>false</remote_derived><description_text>Flex is the diversified manufacturing partner of choice that helps market-leading brands design, build and deliver innovative products that improve the world. A career at Flex offers the opportunity to make a difference and invest in your growth in a respectful, inclusive, and collaborative environment. If you are excited about a role but don&apos;t meet every bullet point, we encourage you to apply and join us to create the extraordinary. Job Summary To support our extraordinary teams who build great products and contribute to our growth, we’re looking to add a Automation Software Engineer located in Guadalajara, North one of our major manufacturing sites. Excellent opportunity to create an extraordinary career with a global company the size and scale of Flex. Reporting to the Director, Automation Engineering, Automation Software Engineer role will be responsible for architecting, designing, and implementing advanced software solutions that enable seamless integration between manufacturing equipment, databases, and enterprise systems. This senior-level position focuses on creating sophisticated connectivity solutions between production machines and business systems to drive data visibility, process automation, and manufacturing excellence. The engineer will architect and develop robust applications for data acquisition, machine monitoring, process control, and analytics using industrial communication protocols and modern software technologies. They will provide technical leadership on machine connectivity projects, mentor junior engineers, and collaborate with cross-functional teams to implement enterprise-grade IIoT solutions, develop software and secure APIs for system integration, create advanced data visualization dashboards, and optimize database performance for manufacturing applications. This position plays a strategic role in the company&apos;s digital transformation and smart manufacturing initiatives, helping to establish technical standards and best practices. What a typical day looks like: Architect and design software solutions that connect manufacturing equipment to enterprise systems using industrial communication protocols (OPC UA, Modbus, MQTT, Profinet, EtherNet/IP) Knowledge of IT infrastructure management for software development. Lead the development and optimization of database applications and stored procedures in MySQL and MSSQL to manage production data Design and implement scalable RESTful APIs to facilitate secure integration between manufacturing systems and business applications Develop advanced data acquisition strategies for PLCs and other automation controllers Create sophisticated data visualization dashboards using Tableau, PowerBi or similar tools to provide actionable insights into production metrics and KPIs Implement and optimize Elasticsearch for indexing, searching, and analyzing large volumes of manufacturing data Lead IIoT implementation projects for remote monitoring, predictive maintenance, and process control Design and optimize ETL processes and data pipelines for efficient data transformation and loading into enterprise systems Analyze and resolve complex connectivity issues between machines and systems Create comprehensive documentation for developments, interfaces, API specifications, and system architectures Lead technical discussions in cross-functional project meetings to shape technology initiatives Evaluate emerging technologies and methodologies in industrial connectivity and data management Lead the software team, using software development methodologies Provide technical mentorship to junior engineers on machine connectivity technologies and implementation approaches Establish technical standards and best practices for machine connectivity solutions. The experience we’re looking to add to our team: BA/BS or equivalent work experience. Solid experience in industrial software development with focus on machine data, connectivity and system integration. Expert proficiency in programming languages such as Python, C#, or Java with demonstrated experience in developing complex industrial applications. Advanced knowledge of database technologies including MySQL, MSSQL, and data management practices, including performance optimization and security. Comprehensive experience with industrial communication protocols (OPC UA, Modbus, MQTT, Profinet, EtherNet/IP, IPC-CFX). Strong understanding of PLC programming concepts and advanced data extraction techniques. Expertise in RESTful API development, implementation, and security best practices. Advanced knowledge of IIoT (Industrial Internet of Things) architectures, security, and implementation. Proficiency with visualization tools like Tableau, Power BI, or similar data visualization platforms, including advanced dashboard development. Advanced experience with Elasticsearch or similar data indexing and search technologies. Strong knowledge of development project management methodologies (Agile, Scrum, Kanban, Watterfall, etc.) Experience with Software versioning management (Github, Dev Azure, other). Experience with development software frameworks. Comprehensive understanding of MES (Manufacturing Execution Systems) concepts, architecture, and integration methods. Expert knowledge of data processing, ETL pipelines, and data transformation techniques. Strong understanding of cybersecurity principles as they relate to industrial systems and IIoT implementations. Proven ability to lead technical projects and mentor junior team members. Excellent problem-solving skills and ability to work in a fast-paced manufacturing environment. Strong communication skills with ability to explain complex technical concepts to stakeholders. Demonstrated capability in leading major initiatives that may impact multiple sites or customers. Experience with agile development methodologies and collaborative tools. Demonstrates Flex values and commitment to continuous improvement. ation tools (i.e., Git, Maven, SVN, TFS). Experience with Application Servers (i.e., Jboss, Payara, Glassfish, Tomcat) Rest Web Services Experience Intermediate English Experience with Databases is also a plus What you’ll receive for the great work you provide: Competitive Salary. Life &amp; Medical insurance. Christmas Bonus. Food Coupons. Saving Fund. MG61 Job Category Production Engineering Required Skills: Optional Skills: Flex is an Equal Opportunity Employer and employment selection decisions are based on merit, qualifications, and abilities. We do not discriminate based on: age, race, religion, color, sex, national origin, marital status, sexual orientation, gender identity, veteran status, disability, pregnancy status, or any other status protected by law. We&apos;re happy to provide reasonable accommodations to those with a disability for assistance in the application process. Please email accessibility@flex.com and we&apos;ll discuss your specific situation and next steps (NOTE: this email does not accept or consider resumes or applications. This is only for disability assistance. To be considered for a position at Flex, you must complete the application process first). Through the collective strength of 140,000 team members across 30 countries and responsible, sustainable operations, Flex is the diversified manufacturing partner of choice that helps market-leading brands design, build and deliver innovative products that improve the world. A career with Flex offers the opportunity to make a difference, invest in your growth, and build great products for our customers that improve people’s lives. Together, let’s create the extraordinary! Join our talent community to learn more about job opportunities, company news and events.</description_text></item><item><id>1687240391</id><date_posted>2025-05-22T00:00:00</date_posted><date_created>2025-05-22T16:50:57.622041</date_created><title>Automation Software Engineer</title><organization>Flex</organization><organization_url></organization_url><date_validthrough></date_validthrough><locations_raw><item><key name="@type">Place</key><address><key name="@type">PostalAddress</key><addressCountry>Mexico</addressCountry><addressLocality>Guadalajara North, Mexico</addressLocality></address></item></locations_raw><locations_alt_raw><item>Mexico, Guadalajara</item></locations_alt_raw><location_type></location_type><location_requirements_raw></location_requirements_raw><salary_raw></salary_raw><employment_type><item>FULL_TIME</item></employment_type><url>https://flextronics.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/Careers/job/Mexico-Guadalajara/Automation-Software-Engineer_WD201283-1</url><source_type>ats</source_type><source>workday</source><source_domain>flextronics.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com</source_domain><organization_logo></organization_logo><cities_derived><item>Guadalajara</item></cities_derived><regions_derived><item>Jalisco</item></regions_derived><countries_derived><item>Mexico</item></countries_derived><locations_derived><item>Guadalajara, Jalisco, Mexico</item></locations_derived><timezones_derived><item>America/Mexico_City</item></timezones_derived><lats_derived><item>20.6767</item></lats_derived><lngs_derived><item>-103.3475</item></lngs_derived><remote_derived>false</remote_derived><description_text>Flex is the diversified manufacturing partner of choice that helps market-leading brands design, build and deliver innovative products that improve the world. A career at Flex offers the opportunity to make a difference and invest in your growth in a respectful, inclusive, and collaborative environment. If you are excited about a role but don&apos;t meet every bullet point, we encourage you to apply and join us to create the extraordinary. Job Summary To support our extraordinary teams who build great products and contribute to our growth, we’re looking to add an Automation Software Engineer located in Guadalajara, North one of our major manufacturing sites in Guadalajara, Mexico. Excellent opportunity to create an extraordinary career with a global company the size and scale of Flex. Reporting to the Director, Automation Engineering, Automation Software Engineer role will be responsible for designing, developing, and implementing software solutions that enable seamless integration between manufacturing equipment, databases, and enterprise systems. This role focuses on creating robust connectivity between production machines and business systems to enhance data visibility, process automation, and manufacturing efficiency. The engineer will develop and maintain applications for data acquisition, machine monitoring, and process control using industrial communication protocols and modern software technologies. They will work closely with cross-functional teams to implement IIoT solutions, develop APIs for system integration, create data visualization dashboards, and optimize database performance for manufacturing applications. This position plays a critical role in the company&apos;s digital transformation and smart manufacturing initiatives. What a typical day looks like: Design and develop software applications that connect manufacturing equipment to enterprise systems using industrial communication protocols (OPC UA, AMQP, MQTT, Profinet, EtherNet/IP) Create and maintain database applications and stored procedures in MySQL and MSSQL to manage production data Develop and implement RESTful APIs to facilitate integration between manufacturing systems and business applications Configure and troubleshoot data acquisition from PLCs and other automation controllers Design and implement data visualization dashboards using Tableau, PowerBI or similars tools to provide real-time insights into production metrics Work with Elasticsearch to index and search large volumes of manufacturing data Collaborate with automation engineers to implement IIoT solutions for remote monitoring and control Develop and optimize ETL(Extract Load &amp; Transform) processes for data transformation and loading into enterprise systems Troubleshoot connectivity issues between machines and systems Document interfaces, API specifications, and system architectures Participate in cross-functional project meetings to ensure technology initiatives align with business requirements Stay current with emerging technologies and methodologies in industrial connectivity and data management Train and mentor junior team members on machine connectivity technologies and best practices. The experience we are looking to add to our team: BA/BS or equivalent work experience Mid seniority experience in industrial software development with focus on machine data, connectivity and system integration. Proficient in programming languages such as Python, C#, or Java with demonstrated experience in developing industrial applications. Strong knowledge of database technologies including MySQL, MSSQL, and data management practices. Experience with industrial communication protocols (OPC UA, Modbus, MQTT, Profinet, EtherNet/IP). Understanding of PLC programming concepts and data extraction techniques. Experience with RESTful API development and implementation. Knowledge of IIoT (Industrial Internet of Things) principles and implementation. Use of development project management methodologies (Agile, Scrum, Kanban, Watterfall, etc.) Software versioning management (Github, Dev Azure, other). Knowledge of development software frameworks. Familiarity with visualization tools like Tableau, Power BI, or similar data visualization platforms. Experience with Elasticsearch or similar data indexing and search technologies. Understanding of MES (Manufacturing Execution Systems) concepts and integration. Knowledge of data processing, ETL pipelines, and data transformation techniques. Understanding of cybersecurity principles as they relate to industrial systems. Strong problem-solving skills and ability to work in a fast-paced manufacturing environment. Excellent communication skills with ability to collaborate with technical and non-technical stakeholders. Demonstrates commitment to implement initiatives and contributes to team success. What you’ll receive for the great work you provide: Competitive Salary. Life &amp; Medical insurance. Christmas Bonus. Food Coupons. Saving Fund. MG61 Job Category Production Engineering Required Skills: Optional Skills: Flex is an Equal Opportunity Employer and employment selection decisions are based on merit, qualifications, and abilities. We do not discriminate based on: age, race, religion, color, sex, national origin, marital status, sexual orientation, gender identity, veteran status, disability, pregnancy status, or any other status protected by law. We&apos;re happy to provide reasonable accommodations to those with a disability for assistance in the application process. Please email accessibility@flex.com and we&apos;ll discuss your specific situation and next steps (NOTE: this email does not accept or consider resumes or applications. This is only for disability assistance. To be considered for a position at Flex, you must complete the application process first). Through the collective strength of 140,000 team members across 30 countries and responsible, sustainable operations, Flex is the diversified manufacturing partner of choice that helps market-leading brands design, build and deliver innovative products that improve the world. A career with Flex offers the opportunity to make a difference, invest in your growth, and build great products for our customers that improve people’s lives. Together, let’s create the extraordinary! Join our talent community to learn more about job opportunities, company news and events.</description_text></item><item><id>1686687252</id><date_posted>2025-05-22T00:00:00</date_posted><date_created>2025-05-22T11:16:23.233938</date_created><title>Software Engineer for Training AI Data in Mexican Spanish, Swift</title><organization>G2i Inc.</organization><organization_url>https://www.g2i.co/</organization_url><date_validthrough></date_validthrough><locations_raw><item><key name="@type">Place</key><address><key name="@type">PostalAddress</key><addressCountry>Remote</addressCountry></address></item></locations_raw><locations_alt_raw></locations_alt_raw><location_type>TELECOMMUTE</location_type><location_requirements_raw><item><key name="@type">Country</key><name>Mexico</name></item><item><key name="@type">Country</key><name>Remote</name></item></location_requirements_raw><salary_raw></salary_raw><employment_type><item>CONTRACTOR</item></employment_type><url>https://jobs.ashbyhq.com/g2i/50e7d7fd-8f4a-4aad-b4aa-438336c4adde</url><source_type>ats</source_type><source>ashby</source><source_domain>jobs.ashbyhq.com</source_domain><organization_logo>https://app.ashbyhq.com/api/images/org-theme-logo/24fc7a0d-00ff-4774-bed3-335f0fd2f6e1/61fda992-eb04-4983-9f1f-ada3baa884d8/af0882f7-1fe8-4a0b-94fc-0562a9f4d7f3.png</organization_logo><cities_derived></cities_derived><regions_derived></regions_derived><countries_derived><item>Mexico</item></countries_derived><locations_derived><item>Mexico</item></locations_derived><timezones_derived><item>America/Mexico_City</item></timezones_derived><lats_derived><item>19.4333</item></lats_derived><lngs_derived><item>-99.1333</item></lngs_derived><remote_derived>true</remote_derived><description_text>Accepted Locations
We accept applicants from the US, Canada, and most countries in LATAM and Europe. We are also accepting candidates from some countries in Africa and Asia. For the complete list of accepted locations, click here. This work is 100% remote.
Loom Video
We have created an Loom video that we highly recommend you watch! Check it out here: Loom Video
Overview
You’ll join an expert annotation team to create training data for the world&apos;s most advanced AI models. No previous AI experience is necessary. You&apos;ll get your foot in the door with one of the most prominent players in the AI/LLM space today. We seek software engineers with 3+ years of experience to train large AI language models, helping cutting-edge generative AI models write better code. Projects typically include discrete, highly variable problems that involve engaging with these models as they learn to code. We currently have 200+ roles open!
What Will I Be Doing?
Evaluating the quality of AI-generated code, including human-readable summaries of your rationale
Solve coding problems, writing functional and efficient code
Writing robust test cases to confirm code works efficiently and effectively
We asked the technical project manager to go into even more detail and this is how he answered: It is solving coding challenges, creating instructions to help others, reviewing the code before it goes into the model, and there&apos;s a ton of variety in the projects. We have everything from &quot;Which piece of Python code is better?&quot; to &quot;Make a full mobile application using this chatbot, and improve the chatbot&apos;s responses afterward to make it faster.&quot;
Pay Rates
Compensation rates average at $30/hr and can go up to $50+/hr. Expectations are 15+ hours per week; however, there is no upper limit. You can work as much as you want and will be paid weekly per hour of work done on the platform.
Contract Length
Long term, there is no end date. They expect to have work for the next 2 years.
You can end the contract at any time. We hope you will commit to 12 months of work, but if you start and it&apos;s not a fit for you, we totally understand. 
Flexible Schedules
Developers can set their own hours—ideal candidates will be interested in spending 40 hours a week. They will be with teams, so strong performers will adapt to the urgency of projects and stay engaged, but they will also be incredibly flexible on working hours. 
You can take a 3-hour lunch, no problem. Instead of tracking your hours, you are paid according to time spent on the platform, calculated in the coding exercises. 
Interview Process
Apply using this Ashby form.
If you seem like a good fit, we&apos;ll send an async RLHF code review that will take 35 minutes and must be finished within 72 hours of us sending it.
You&apos;ll receive credentials to the RLHF platform. We&apos;ll then set up a group call to answer any further questions about onboarding with the company.
You&apos;ll perform a simulated production-level task (RLHF task) on the platform. This will be your final interview, which will ultimately determine your employment and leveling. Successful completion of this process provides you with an opportunity to work on projects as they become available.
Tech Stack Priorities
The current priority for this team is engineers with either a Data Science background who know Swift well or software engineers who are well-versed in Swift.
Required Qualifications:
3+ years of experience in a software engineering/software development role.
Complete fluency in the English language.
Ability to articulate complex scientific concepts clearly and engagingly.
Excellent attention to detail and ability to maintain consistency in writing.
Solid understanding of grammar, punctuation, and style guidelines.
Proficiency with Swift
Nice To Haves:
Bachelor&apos;s or Master’s degree in Computer Science
Proficiency in working with one or more of the following: Java, JavaScript, TypeScript, C++. SQL, Swift, Ruby, Rust, Go, NET, Matlab, PHP, HTML, DART, R, Apex, and Shell, C, C#
Recognized accomplishments or contributions to the coding community or in projects.
Proven analytical skills with an ability to approach problems creatively.
Adept communication skills, especially when understanding and discussing project requirements.
A commitment to continuous learning and staying updated with the latest coding advancements and best practices.
Enthusiasm for teaching AI models and experience with technical writing!</description_text></item><item><id>1685520953</id><date_posted>2025-05-21T21:14:02</date_posted><date_created>2025-05-22T01:51:20.958812</date_created><title>Recent Graduated - Software Engineer</title><organization>Amdocs</organization><organization_url>amdocs.com</organization_url><date_validthrough>2025-06-20T21:14:02</date_validthrough><locations_raw><item><key name="@type">Place</key><address><key name="@type">PostalAddress</key><addressLocality>Guadalajara</addressLocality><addressRegion>Jal.,MX</addressRegion><addressCountry><key name="@type">Country</key><name>MX</name></addressCountry></address></item></locations_raw><locations_alt_raw></locations_alt_raw><location_type></location_type><location_requirements_raw></location_requirements_raw><salary_raw></salary_raw><employment_type><item>FULL_TIME</item></employment_type><url>https://jobs.amdocs.com/careers/job/563431002870954-recent-graduated-software-engineer-guadalajara-mexico</url><source_type>ats</source_type><source>eightfold</source><source_domain>jobs.amdocs.com</source_domain><organization_logo></organization_logo><cities_derived><item>Guadalajara</item></cities_derived><regions_derived><item>Jalisco</item></regions_derived><countries_derived><item>Mexico</item></countries_derived><locations_derived><item>Guadalajara, Jalisco, Mexico</item></locations_derived><timezones_derived><item>America/Mexico_City</item></timezones_derived><lats_derived><item>20.6767</item></lats_derived><lngs_derived><item>-103.3475</item></lngs_derived><remote_derived>false</remote_derived><description_text>Job ID: 199474 
Required Travel :Minimal 

Location: [[reqLocation]] 
Who are we?
Amdocs helps those who build the future to make it amazing. With our market-leading portfolio of software products and services, we unlock our customers’ innovative potential, empowering them to provide next-generation communication and media experiences for both the individual end user and enterprise customers. Our employees around the globe are here to accelerate service providers’ migration to the cloud, enable them to differentiate in the 5G era, and digitalize and automate their operations. Listed on the NASDAQ Global Select Market, Amdocs had revenue of $5.00 billion in fiscal 2024. For more information, visit www.amdocs.com
In one sentence
Responsible for design, development, modification, debug and/or maintenance of software systems
What will your job look like?
• You will design, develop, modify, debug and/or maintain software code according to functional, non-functional and technical design specifications.
• You will follow Amdocs software engineering standards, applicable software development methodology and release processes, to ensure code is maintainable, scalable, and supportable, and demo the software products to stakeholders.
• You will investigate issues by reviewing/debugging code, provide fixes and workarounds, and review changes for operability to maintain existing software solutions.
• You will work within a team, collaborate and add value through participation in peer code reviews, provide comments and suggestions, and work with cross functional teams to achieve goals.
• You will assume technical accountability for your specific work products within an application and provide technical support during solution design for new requirements.
• You will be encouraged to actively look for innovation, continuous improvement, and efficiency in all assigned tasks.
All you need is...
• Bachelor&apos;s degree in Science/IT/Computer Science or equivalent
• 3+ years Java experience (server side) on Linux/Unix/Windows
• Demonstrable experience with the Spring framework components - Spring Boot, MVC, Integration, Security, etc.
• Strong understanding of RESTful APIs and open systems
Why you will love this job:
• You will be challenged to design and develop new software applications.
• You will have the opportunity to work in a growing organization, with ever growing opportunities for personal growth.
Amdocs is an equal opportunity employer. We welcome applicants from all backgrounds and are committed to fostering a diverse and inclusive workforce</description_text></item><item><id>1684778917</id><date_posted>2025-05-21T20:01:03.112</date_posted><date_created>2025-05-21T20:25:32.30807</date_created><title>Software Engineer, Java and Kotlin Ecosystem</title><organization>Google</organization><organization_url>https://www.google.com</organization_url><date_validthrough></date_validthrough><locations_raw><item><key name="@type">Place</key><address><key name="@type">PostalAddress</key><addressCountry>MX</addressCountry><addressLocality>Mexico City</addressLocality><addressRegion>CDMX</addressRegion></address></item></locations_raw><locations_alt_raw></locations_alt_raw><location_type></location_type><location_requirements_raw></location_requirements_raw><salary_raw></salary_raw><employment_type></employment_type><url>https://www.google.com/about/careers/applications/jobs/results/143223195195843270</url><source_type>ats</source_type><source>in-house</source><source_domain>google.com</source_domain><organization_logo></organization_logo><cities_derived><item>Mexico City</item></cities_derived><regions_derived><item>Ciudad de México</item></regions_derived><countries_derived><item>Mexico</item></countries_derived><locations_derived><item>Mexico City, Ciudad de México, Mexico</item></locations_derived><timezones_derived><item>America/Mexico_City</item></timezones_derived><lats_derived><item>19.4333</item></lats_derived><lngs_derived><item>-99.1333</item></lngs_derived><remote_derived>false</remote_derived><description_text>MINIMUM QUALIFICATIONS:

 * Bachelor&apos;s degree or equivalent practical experience
 * 2 years of experience with software development in one or more programming
   languages, or 1 year of experience with an advanced degree
   
 * 2 years of experience with developing infrastructure, distributed systems or
   networks, or experience with compute technologies, storage or hardware
   architecture
   
 * Experience with Kotlin, Java, Java Libraries, Bazel
   



PREFERRED QUALIFICATIONS:

 * Experience building reusable, performant and reliable software
   
 * Experience in one of the following: library development, compilers, static
   analysis, programming languages, IDE plug-ins, or build systems
   
 * Experience working in Open Source
   
 * Experience with Android, iOS, or Web development
 * Interest in infrastructure, API design, or code health


ABOUT THE JOB:

Google&apos;s software engineers develop the next-generation technologies that change
how billions of users connect, explore, and interact with information and one
another. Our products need to handle information at massive scale, and extend
well beyond web search. We&apos;re looking for engineers who bring fresh ideas from
all areas, including information retrieval, distributed computing, large-scale
system design, networking and data storage, security, artificial intelligence,
natural language processing, UI design and mobile; the list goes on and is
growing every day. As a software engineer, you will work on a specific project
critical to Google’s needs with opportunities to switch teams and projects as
you and our fast-paced business grow and evolve. We need our engineers to be
versatile, display leadership qualities and be enthusiastic to take on new
problems across the full-stack as we continue to push technology forward.

In this role, you will have an opportunity to develop the Kotlin Multiplatform
Ecosystem. You will get the opportunity to partner with developers of many
popular Java Open Source libraries such as Guava, Truth, and Flogger to have an
impact both internally at Google and in Open Source. You will help improve the
developer experience at Google by improving the toolchain, developing libraries
and static analysis to prevent bugs before they are written, suggesting better
code patterns, and making large-scale changes to a huge codebase.

The Core team builds the technical foundation behind Google’s flagship products.
We are owners and advocates for the underlying design elements, developer
platforms, product components, and infrastructure at Google. These are the
essential building blocks for excellent, safe, and coherent experiences for our
users and drive the pace of innovation for every developer. We look across
Google’s products to build central solutions, break down technical barriers and
strengthen existing systems. As the Core team, we have a mandate and a unique
opportunity to impact important technical decisions across the company.


RESPONSIBILITIES:

 * Develop and test code for KMP developer tools, libraries, and static
   analysis.
   
 * Help Google engineers build, debug, test, profile, and run their KMP code on
   all supported platforms.
   
 * Participate in and lead design reviews with peers and stakeholders to decide
   amongst available technologies.
   
 * Review code developed by other developers and provide feedback to ensure best
   practices (e.g., style guidelines, checking code in, accuracy, testability,
   and efficiency).
   
 * Contribute to documentation or educational content and adapt content based on
   program updates and user feedback. Triage, debug, track, and resolve issues.
   </description_text></item><item><id>1684609212</id><date_posted>2025-05-21T18:51:47</date_posted><date_created>2025-05-21T19:09:07.617878</date_created><title>Software Engineer III, in Test</title><organization>Mitratech</organization><organization_url></organization_url><date_validthrough></date_validthrough><locations_raw><item><key name="@type">Place</key><name>Remote Mexico</name><address><key name="@type">PostalAddress</key><name>Remote Mexico</name><addressCountry></addressCountry><addressLocality>Remote Mexico</addressLocality></address></item></locations_raw><locations_alt_raw></locations_alt_raw><location_type></location_type><location_requirements_raw></location_requirements_raw><salary_raw></salary_raw><employment_type></employment_type><url>https://job-boards.greenhouse.io/mitratech/jobs/6871949</url><source_type>ats</source_type><source>greenhouse</source><source_domain>job-boards.greenhouse.io</source_domain><organization_logo></organization_logo><cities_derived></cities_derived><regions_derived></regions_derived><countries_derived><item>Mexico</item></countries_derived><locations_derived><item>Mexico</item></locations_derived><timezones_derived><item>America/Mexico_City</item></timezones_derived><lats_derived><item>19.4333</item></lats_derived><lngs_derived><item>-99.1333</item></lngs_derived><remote_derived>true</remote_derived><description_text>At Mitratech, we are a team of technocrats focused on building world-class products that simplify operations in the Legal, Risk, Compliance, and HR functions. We are a close-knit, globally dispersed team that thrives in an ecosystem that supports individual excellence and takes pride in its diverse and inclusive work culture centered around great people practices, learning opportunities, and having fun! Our culture is the ideal blend of entrepreneurial spirit and enterprise investment, enabling the chance to move at a rapid pace with some of the most complex, leading-edge technologies available.
For over 35 years, the experts at Mitratech have been focused on solving the complex needs. Today, we serve 20,000 client companies of all sizes globally, representing 30% of the Fortune 500 and over 500,000 users in over 160 countries.
As we continue to grow, we’re always looking for resourceful, enthusiastic, and fresh perspectives. Join our global team and see what makes Mitratech a truly exceptional place to work!
Job Description
The Software Engineer III, In Test is responsible for developing and establishing quality assurance standards and measures for the information technology services within the organization. This will include writing test plans and scripts for tracking defects and fixes in product development. This individual will apply proven analytical and problem-solving skills to help validate, verify, communicate, and resolve system/software application issues through careful testing in order to ensure high quality in our SaaS applications.
Essential Duties &amp; Responsibilities:
Develop and execute manual tests and plans for software changes in the company&apos;s software products
Develop and execute test scripts and plans for software changes in the company’s software products
Perform integrated software testing, which includes but is not limited to, ensuring the accuracy of new product features or corrections to current software functions per the business requirements prior to release of software
Track and report work completed on a daily basis
Work closely with software developers to clearly convey issues found and to ensure timely resolution
Document, track, retest and communicate test results
Ensure tasks assigned are completed as scheduled
Review product Release Notes and other documentation for accuracy
Enhance existing and recommend new methodologies to improve company efficiency and quality
Writes and maintains test automation scripts
Pursue continuing education, addressing analysis and upgrading of technical and testing skills
Requirements &amp; Skills:
5+ years experience with software development life cycle, testing methodologies, quality control, and quality assurance
Experience in systems integration and user acceptance testing
Experience developing and executing manual test suites
Familiarity with test tools and techniques, bug tracking systems, test design and execution (Testrail, Jmeter, Jira, etc)
Comfortable using and moving around in a Linux-based environment
Experienced in utilizing SQL queries to perform job duties
Experience in Java, JavaScript utilizing the Selenium framework. With hands on experience writing and running automated tests.
Experience with modern source control systems (Git, Gradle, etc.)
Problem-Solving Skills: Analytical mindset with the ability to troubleshoot technical issues and propose creative solutions. 
Communication and Collaboration: Highly effective communication skills, comfortable leading within a team, and driving development discussions.
Education:
Bachelor’s Degree or Equivalent Experience: Emphasis in engineering, data science, computer science or information systems is preferred. 
We are an equal-opportunity employer that values diversity at all levels. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, gender, national origin, age, sexual orientation, gender identity, disability, or veteran status.</description_text></item><item><id>1688376852</id><date_posted>2025-05-21T08:50:02</date_posted><date_created>2025-05-23T01:45:33.972909</date_created><title>Software Engineer - Intern</title><organization>Amdocs</organization><organization_url>amdocs.com</organization_url><date_validthrough>2025-06-20T08:50:02</date_validthrough><locations_raw><item><key name="@type">Place</key><address><key name="@type">PostalAddress</key><addressLocality>Guadalajara</addressLocality><addressRegion>Jal.,MX</addressRegion><addressCountry><key name="@type">Country</key><name>MX</name></addressCountry></address></item></locations_raw><locations_alt_raw></locations_alt_raw><location_type></location_type><location_requirements_raw></location_requirements_raw><salary_raw></salary_raw><employment_type><item>FULL_TIME</item></employment_type><url>https://jobs.amdocs.com/careers/job/563431002632131-software-engineer-intern-mexico-guadalajara-amdocs-site-</url><source_type>ats</source_type><source>eightfold</source><source_domain>jobs.amdocs.com</source_domain><organization_logo></organization_logo><cities_derived><item>Guadalajara</item></cities_derived><regions_derived><item>Jalisco</item></regions_derived><countries_derived><item>Mexico</item></countries_derived><locations_derived><item>Guadalajara, Jalisco, Mexico</item></locations_derived><timezones_derived><item>America/Mexico_City</item></timezones_derived><lats_derived><item>20.6767</item></lats_derived><lngs_derived><item>-103.3475</item></lngs_derived><remote_derived>false</remote_derived><description_text>Job ID: 198974 
Required Travel :Minimal 
Managerial - No 
Location: :Mexico-Guadalajara (AM) 
Who are we?
Amdocs helps those who build the future to make it amazing. With our market-leading portfolio of software products and services, we unlock our customers’ innovative potential, empowering them to provide next-generation communication and media experiences for both the individual end user and enterprise customers. Our employees around the globe are here to accelerate service providers’ migration to the cloud, enable them to differentiate in the 5G era, and digitalize and automate their operations. Listed on the NASDAQ Global Select Market, Amdocs had revenue of $5.00 billion in fiscal 2024. For more information, visit www.amdocs.com
In one sentence
Responsible for design, development, modification, debug and/or maintenance of software systems
What will your job look like?
• You will design, develop, modify, debug and/or maintain software code according to functional, non-functional and technical design specifications.
• You will follow Amdocs software engineering standards, applicable software development methodology and release processes, to ensure code is maintainable, scalable, and supportable, and demo the software products to stakeholders.
• You will investigate issues by reviewing/debugging code, provide fixes and workarounds, and review changes for operability to maintain existing software solutions.
• You will work within a team, collaborate and add value through participation in peer code reviews, provide comments and suggestions, and work with cross functional teams to achieve goals.
• You will assume technical accountability for your specific work products within an application and provide technical support during solution design for new requirements.
• You will be encouraged to actively look for innovation, continuous improvement, and efficiency in all assigned tasks.
All you need is...
• Bachelor&apos;s degree in Science/IT/Computer Science or equivalent
• 3+ years Java experience (server side) on Linux/Unix/Windows
• Demonstrable experience with the Spring framework components - Spring Boot, MVC, Integration, Security, etc.
• Strong understanding of RESTful APIs and open systems
Why you will love this job:
• You will be challenged to design and develop new software applications.
• You will have the opportunity to work in a growing organization, with ever growing opportunities for personal growth.
Amdocs is an equal opportunity employer. We welcome applicants from all backgrounds and are committed to fostering a diverse and inclusive workforce</description_text></item><item><id>1685520924</id><date_posted>2025-05-21T08:50:02</date_posted><date_created>2025-05-22T01:51:19.564585</date_created><title>Software Engineer - Intern</title><organization>Amdocs</organization><organization_url>amdocs.com</organization_url><date_validthrough>2025-06-20T08:50:02</date_validthrough><locations_raw><item><key name="@type">Place</key><address><key name="@type">PostalAddress</key><addressLocality>Guadalajara</addressLocality><addressRegion>Jal.,MX</addressRegion><addressCountry><key name="@type">Country</key><name>MX</name></addressCountry></address></item></locations_raw><locations_alt_raw></locations_alt_raw><location_type></location_type><location_requirements_raw></location_requirements_raw><salary_raw></salary_raw><employment_type><item>FULL_TIME</item></employment_type><url>https://jobs.amdocs.com/careers/job/563431002632131-software-engineer-intern-mexico-guadalajara-am-</url><source_type>ats</source_type><source>eightfold</source><source_domain>jobs.amdocs.com</source_domain><organization_logo></organization_logo><cities_derived><item>Guadalajara</item></cities_derived><regions_derived><item>Jalisco</item></regions_derived><countries_derived><item>Mexico</item></countries_derived><locations_derived><item>Guadalajara, Jalisco, Mexico</item></locations_derived><timezones_derived><item>America/Mexico_City</item></timezones_derived><lats_derived><item>20.6767</item></lats_derived><lngs_derived><item>-103.3475</item></lngs_derived><remote_derived>false</remote_derived><description_text>Job ID: 198974 
Required Travel :Minimal 
Managerial - No 
Location: :Mexico-Guadalajara (AM) 
Who are we?
Amdocs helps those who build the future to make it amazing. With our market-leading portfolio of software products and services, we unlock our customers’ innovative potential, empowering them to provide next-generation communication and media experiences for both the individual end user and enterprise customers. Our employees around the globe are here to accelerate service providers’ migration to the cloud, enable them to differentiate in the 5G era, and digitalize and automate their operations. Listed on the NASDAQ Global Select Market, Amdocs had revenue of $5.00 billion in fiscal 2024. For more information, visit www.amdocs.com
In one sentence
Responsible for design, development, modification, debug and/or maintenance of software systems
What will your job look like?
• You will design, develop, modify, debug and/or maintain software code according to functional, non-functional and technical design specifications.
• You will follow Amdocs software engineering standards, applicable software development methodology and release processes, to ensure code is maintainable, scalable, and supportable, and demo the software products to stakeholders.
• You will investigate issues by reviewing/debugging code, provide fixes and workarounds, and review changes for operability to maintain existing software solutions.
• You will work within a team, collaborate and add value through participation in peer code reviews, provide comments and suggestions, and work with cross functional teams to achieve goals.
• You will assume technical accountability for your specific work products within an application and provide technical support during solution design for new requirements.
• You will be encouraged to actively look for innovation, continuous improvement, and efficiency in all assigned tasks.
All you need is...
• Bachelor&apos;s degree in Science/IT/Computer Science or equivalent
• 3+ years Java experience (server side) on Linux/Unix/Windows
• Demonstrable experience with the Spring framework components - Spring Boot, MVC, Integration, Security, etc.
• Strong understanding of RESTful APIs and open systems
Why you will love this job:
• You will be challenged to design and develop new software applications.
• You will have the opportunity to work in a growing organization, with ever growing opportunities for personal growth.
Amdocs is an equal opportunity employer. We welcome applicants from all backgrounds and are committed to fostering a diverse and inclusive workforce</description_text></item><item><id>1684944080</id><date_posted>2025-05-21T00:00:00</date_posted><date_created>2025-05-21T21:37:25.345065</date_created><title>AI Software Engineer - MEX</title><organization>Platzi</organization><organization_url>https://jobs.workable.com/company/adzVYKBbnfRJGXifywZLgL/jobs-at-platzi</organization_url><date_validthrough></date_validthrough><locations_raw><item><key name="@type">Place</key><address><key name="@type">PostalAddress</key><addressLocality>Mexico City</addressLocality><addressRegion>Mexico City</addressRegion><addressCountry>Mexico</addressCountry></address></item></locations_raw><locations_alt_raw><item>Mexico City, Mexico City, Mexico</item></locations_alt_raw><location_type>TELECOMMUTE</location_type><location_requirements_raw><item><key name="@type">Country</key><name>Mexico</name></item></location_requirements_raw><salary_raw></salary_raw><employment_type><item>FULL_TIME</item></employment_type><url>https://jobs.workable.com/view/vKEhcRQZnVVDheB9ThnKaX/hybrid-ai-software-engineer---mex-in-mexico-city-at-platzi</url><source_type>ats</source_type><source>workable</source><source_domain>jobs.workable.com</source_domain><organization_logo>https://workablehr.s3.amazonaws.com/uploads/account/logo/665047/logo</organization_logo><cities_derived><item>Mexico City</item></cities_derived><regions_derived><item>Ciudad de México</item></regions_derived><countries_derived><item>Mexico</item></countries_derived><locations_derived><item>Mexico City, Ciudad de México, Mexico</item></locations_derived><timezones_derived><item>America/Mexico_City</item></timezones_derived><lats_derived><item>19.4333</item></lats_derived><lngs_derived><item>-99.1333</item></lngs_derived><remote_derived>true</remote_derived><description_text>At Platzi, we’re building AI-powered products that are changing the way people learn. We’re looking for an AI Software Engineer with a strong technical background—someone who knows how to integrate language models, embeddings, and agents into real-world systems that are scalable and maintainable.
This role is for someone who doesn’t just use LLMs, but understands how they work, how to optimize and deploy them, and most importantly, how to turn them into real products.
What you’ll do
Design and build AI-driven solutions using LLMs, agents, embeddings, and techniques like RAG and fine-tuning to improve model accuracy and personalization. 
Work with multiple LLM providers: OpenAI, Anthropic, Gemini/Vertex AI, Mistral AI. 
Integrate frameworks like LangChain, LlamaIndex, and similar tools into real data pipelines and products. 
Process unstructured data (PDFs, images, videos) and extract meaningful information. 
Build robust backend services with Python, FastAPI, and Django (bonus points if you also know TypeScript and have worked with Cloudflare Workers or Hono). 
Stay up to date with the latest AI advancements and bring those improvements to our stack. 
Read, understand, and apply insights from technical papers and research reports.</description_text></item><item><id>1681211802</id><date_posted>2025-05-20T19:05:16.234</date_posted><date_created>2025-05-20T19:13:05.421796</date_created><title>Software Engineer II - Android</title><organization>McDonald&apos;s Corporation</organization><organization_url></organization_url><date_validthrough></date_validthrough><locations_raw><item><address><streetAddress>Calz. Gral. Mariano Escobedo 595 Rincón del Bosque, Bosque de Chapultepec I Secc, Miguel Hidalgo</streetAddress><addressLocality>Ciudad de México</addressLocality><postalCode>11580</postalCode><addressCountry>Mexico</addressCountry></address></item></locations_raw><locations_alt_raw><item>Calz. Gral. Mariano Escobedo 595 Rincón del Bosque, Bosque de Chapultepec I Secc, Miguel Hidalgo, Ciudad de México, Mexico</item></locations_alt_raw><location_type></location_type><location_requirements_raw></location_requirements_raw><salary_raw></salary_raw><employment_type><item>Full-time</item></employment_type><url>https://jobs.smartrecruiters.com/McDonaldsCorporation/744000060625805-software-engineer-ii-android</url><source_type>ats</source_type><source>smartrecruiters</source><source_domain>jobs.smartrecruiters.com</source_domain><organization_logo></organization_logo><cities_derived><item>Mexico City</item></cities_derived><regions_derived><item>Ciudad de México</item></regions_derived><countries_derived><item>Mexico</item></countries_derived><locations_derived><item>Mexico City, Ciudad de México, Mexico</item></locations_derived><timezones_derived><item>America/Mexico_City</item></timezones_derived><lats_derived><item>19.4333</item></lats_derived><lngs_derived><item>-99.1333</item></lngs_derived><remote_derived>false</remote_derived><description_text>Company DescriptionMcDonald’s growth strategy, Accelerating the Arches, encompasses all aspects of our business as the leading global omni-channel restaurant brand. As the consumer landscape shifts we are using our competitive advantages to further strengthen our brand. One of our core growth strategies is to Double Down on the 3Ds (Delivery, Digital and Drive Thru). McDonald’s will accelerate technology innovation so 65M+ customers a day will experience a fast, easy experience, whether at one of our 25,000 and growing Drive Thrus, through McDelivery, dine-in or takeaway.  McDonald’s Global Technology is here to power tomorrow’s feel-good moments.  That’s why you’ll find us at the forefront of transformative technology, exploring new and innovative ways to serve our millions of customers and spread happiness one delicious Hot Fudge Sundae-dipped fry at a time. Using AI, robotics and emerging tech, we’re digitizing the Golden Arches. Combine that with our unparalleled global scale, and we’re reshaping all areas of the business, industry and every community that is home to a McDonald’s restaurant. We face complex tech challenges every day. But that’s where our diverse and talented teams come in. They’re made up of the best and brightest from all over the globe, and they thrive in the space where feel-good meets fast-paced.  We’re recruiting engineers to join our Global Technology team in Mexico City as we open our McDonald&apos;s in Mexico office. Our Mexico City office will be a hub for technology innovation and operational support to help us build the solutions that will improve our customer, crew and employee experience each and every day. Check out the McDonald’s  Global Technology Technical Blog to learn how technology and our global team are directly enabling the Accelerating the Arches strategy. Job DescriptionContribute to all aspects of the agile development life cycle including design, development, documentation, testing and operations.As a software development engineer on a team, you will play a pivotal role in shaping the definition, vision, design, road map and development of product features from beginning to end.Design, implement, test, deploy and maintain innovative software solutions to transform service performance, durability, cost, and security.Use software engineering best practices to ensure a high standard of quality for all team deliverables.Work in an agile, startup-like development environment, where you are always working on the most important priorities.Qualifications2+ years of non-internship professional software development experience.Extensive programming experience with Kotlin, Java, and Android platform technologies and APIs.Bachelor’s Degree in Computer Science or related field or equivalent years of experience.Solid knowledge of Computer Science fundamentals (object-oriented design, data structures and algorithm.Strong verbal and written communication skills.Solution-oriented attitude and ability to solve tough problems in a collaborative, cross-functional, and fast-paced environment.Demonstrated leadership abilities in an engineering environment in driving operational excellence and best practices.Highly quantitative with great judgment and passion for building a great customer experience.Uncompromising attention to detail and drive to continuously improve the product.Ability to take a project from scoping requirements to launch to delivery.#LI-Hybrid</description_text></item><item><id>1682166232</id><date_posted>2025-05-20T16:17:34</date_posted><date_created>2025-05-21T01:42:55.481555</date_created><title>Software Engineer - Intern</title><organization>Amdocs</organization><organization_url>amdocs.com</organization_url><date_validthrough>2025-06-19T16:17:34</date_validthrough><locations_raw><item><key name="@type">Place</key><address><key name="@type">PostalAddress</key><addressLocality>Guadalajara</addressLocality><addressRegion>Jal.,MX</addressRegion><addressCountry><key name="@type">Country</key><name>MX</name></addressCountry></address></item></locations_raw><locations_alt_raw></locations_alt_raw><location_type></location_type><location_requirements_raw></location_requirements_raw><salary_raw></salary_raw><employment_type><item>FULL_TIME</item></employment_type><url>https://jobs.amdocs.com/careers/job/563431002632117-software-engineer-intern-mexico-guadalajara-am-</url><source_type>ats</source_type><source>eightfold</source><source_domain>jobs.amdocs.com</source_domain><organization_logo></organization_logo><cities_derived><item>Guadalajara</item></cities_derived><regions_derived><item>Jalisco</item></regions_derived><countries_derived><item>Mexico</item></countries_derived><locations_derived><item>Guadalajara, Jalisco, Mexico</item></locations_derived><timezones_derived><item>America/Mexico_City</item></timezones_derived><lats_derived><item>20.6767</item></lats_derived><lngs_derived><item>-103.3475</item></lngs_derived><remote_derived>false</remote_derived><description_text>Job ID: 198973 
Required Travel :Minimal 
Managerial - No 
Location: :Mexico-Guadalajara (AM) 
Who are we?
Amdocs helps those who build the future to make it amazing. With our market-leading portfolio of software products and services, we unlock our customers’ innovative potential, empowering them to provide next-generation communication and media experiences for both the individual end user and enterprise customers. Our employees around the globe are here to accelerate service providers’ migration to the cloud, enable them to differentiate in the 5G era, and digitalize and automate their operations. Listed on the NASDAQ Global Select Market, Amdocs had revenue of $5.00 billion in fiscal 2024. For more information, visit www.amdocs.com
In one sentence
Responsible for design, development, modification, debug and/or maintenance of software systems
What will your job look like?
• You will design, develop, modify, debug and/or maintain software code according to functional, non-functional and technical design specifications.
• You will follow Amdocs software engineering standards, applicable software development methodology and release processes, to ensure code is maintainable, scalable, and supportable, and demo the software products to stakeholders.
• You will investigate issues by reviewing/debugging code, provide fixes and workarounds, and review changes for operability to maintain existing software solutions.
• You will work within a team, collaborate and add value through participation in peer code reviews, provide comments and suggestions, and work with cross functional teams to achieve goals.
• You will assume technical accountability for your specific work products within an application and provide technical support during solution design for new requirements.
• You will be encouraged to actively look for innovation, continuous improvement, and efficiency in all assigned tasks.
All you need is...
• Bachelor&apos;s degree in Science/IT/Computer Science or equivalent
• 3+ years Java experience (server side) on Linux/Unix/Windows
• Demonstrable experience with the Spring framework components - Spring Boot, MVC, Integration, Security, etc.
• Strong understanding of RESTful APIs and open systems
Why you will love this job:
• You will be challenged to design and develop new software applications.
• You will have the opportunity to work in a growing organization, with ever growing opportunities for personal growth.
Amdocs is an equal opportunity employer. We welcome applicants from all backgrounds and are committed to fostering a diverse and inclusive workforce</description_text></item><item><id>1682443648</id><date_posted>2025-05-20T00:00:00</date_posted><date_created>2025-05-21T03:37:55.959579</date_created><title>Software Engineer Senior Consultant II</title><organization>Allstate</organization><organization_url></organization_url><date_validthrough></date_validthrough><locations_raw><item><key name="@type">Place</key><address><key name="@type">PostalAddress</key><addressCountry>Mexico</addressCountry><addressLocality>Mexico (Remote)</addressLocality></address></item></locations_raw><locations_alt_raw><item>Mexico (Remote)</item></locations_alt_raw><location_type>TELECOMMUTE</location_type><location_requirements_raw><item><key name="@type">Country</key><name>Mexico</name></item></location_requirements_raw><salary_raw></salary_raw><employment_type><item>FULL_TIME</item></employment_type><url>https://allstate.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/allstate_careers/job/Mexico-Remote/Software-Engineer-Senior-Consultant-II_R17383</url><source_type>ats</source_type><source>workday</source><source_domain>allstate.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com</source_domain><organization_logo></organization_logo><cities_derived></cities_derived><regions_derived></regions_derived><countries_derived><item>Mexico</item></countries_derived><locations_derived><item>Mexico</item></locations_derived><timezones_derived><item>America/Mexico_City</item></timezones_derived><lats_derived><item>19.4333</item></lats_derived><lngs_derived><item>-99.1333</item></lngs_derived><remote_derived>true</remote_derived><description_text>Integon is a part of The Allstate Corporation, which means we have the same innovative drive that keeps us a step ahead of our customers’ evolving needs. It’s how we’ve become industry leaders in property and casualty insurance servicing. We support our insurance company affiliates by offering property and casualty insurance products inclusive of personal auto, homeowners, RV, motorcycle, small business auto insurance and more. Job Description Software Engineer Senior Consultant II implements applications following 12-factor principles to build out the product and iterative enhancements. They own the full stack of software products, developing and implementing frontends (web or mobile), and backend services. They leverage test driven development and continuous integration to ensure agility and quality of products. They actively participate in the decision-making process of the team ensuring that the simplest appropriate technology and design is chosen to meet user needs. Key Responsibilities • Provides input into the architecture and design of the product; collaborating with the team in solving problems the right way • Practices daily paired programming and test-driven development in writing software and building product • Participates in executing the strategy, keeping the customer needs and wants in mind • Serves as an expert on a specific business domain and demonstrates leadership and accountability on at least one technology stack • Coaches more junior team members around different technologies and XP practices • Establishes continuous integration, continuous delivery, and continuous deployment pipelines and practices • Provides support for software products in user environments • Leads and participates in daily site, cross-site, and product team standups • Participates in retrospectives to gather feedback and derive actionable items to improve the team and the product • Participates in iteration planning meetings ensuring that the team has a common understanding of each story and chores in a team’s backlog Education • 4 year Bachelors Degree (Preferred) Experience • 3 or more years of experience (Preferred) Supervisory Responsibilities • This job does not have supervisory duties. Education &amp; Experience (in lieu) • In lieu of the above education requirements, an equivalent combination of education and experience may be considered. At Integon, great things happen when our people work together. That’s why when you join our team, we make sure it isn’t just a job — it’s an opportunity. One that takes your skills and pushes them to the next level. One that encourages you to challenge the status quo. And one where you can impact the future for the greater good. You’ll do all this in a flexible environment that embraces connection and belonging. And with the recognition of several inclusivity and diversity awards, we’ve proven that Allstate empowers everyone to lead, drive change and give back where they work and live. Good Hands. Greater Together. In the event you need assistance or accommodation in completing your online application, please contact Integon via WhatsApp at 664.203.4492 Direct General Auto &amp; Life, Personal Express Insurance, Century-National Insurance, ABC Insurance Agencies, NatGen Preferred, NatGen Premier, Seattle Specialty, National General Lender Services, ARS, RAC Insurance Partners, Mountain Valley Indemnity, New Jersey Skylands, Adirondack Insurance Exchange, VelaPoint, Quotit, HealthCompare, AHCP, NHIC, Healthcare Solutions Team, North Star Marketing, Euro Accident. At Allstate, we work hard to help people live a good life every day. Allstaters are dedicated to serving clients, customers, and communities, which allows employees to find meaning and value in their work. Allstate offers an environment that fosters innovative thinking where you’ll be able to explore your ideas and feel proud of the work you do. Allstate helps protect nearly 16 million households with auto, home, life, and retirement products. We want every professional connected to Allstate to be committed to giving our customers the best and that means finding the best talent. We want you to be our next great addition. It’s easy to search and apply for a new opportunity with Allstate. Simply use the links below to identify the openings that interest you. About Us</description_text></item><item><id>1681435033</id><date_posted>2025-05-20T00:00:00</date_posted><date_created>2025-05-20T20:52:00.409317</date_created><title>.Net Software Engineer V</title><organization>Global Payments Inc.</organization><organization_url></organization_url><date_validthrough></date_validthrough><locations_raw><item><key name="@type">Place</key><address><key name="@type">PostalAddress</key><addressCountry>Mexico</addressCountry><addressLocality>EVO Lomas de Memelta, Mexico Office</addressLocality></address></item></locations_raw><locations_alt_raw><item>Cuajimalpa, Mexico City, Mexico</item></locations_alt_raw><location_type></location_type><location_requirements_raw></location_requirements_raw><salary_raw></salary_raw><employment_type><item>FULL_TIME</item></employment_type><url>https://tsys.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/TSYS/job/Cuajimalpa-Mexico-City-Mexico/XMLNAME-Net-Software-Engineer-V_R0062224</url><source_type>ats</source_type><source>workday</source><source_domain>tsys.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com</source_domain><organization_logo></organization_logo><cities_derived></cities_derived><regions_derived></regions_derived><countries_derived><item>Mexico</item></countries_derived><locations_derived><item>Mexico</item></locations_derived><timezones_derived><item>America/Mexico_City</item></timezones_derived><lats_derived><item>19.4333</item></lats_derived><lngs_derived><item>-99.1333</item></lngs_derived><remote_derived>false</remote_derived><description_text>Every day, Global Payments makes it possible for millions of people to move money between buyers and sellers using our payments solutions for credit, debit, prepaid and merchant services. Our worldwide team helps over 3 million companies, more than 1,300 financial institutions and over 600 million cardholders grow with confidence and achieve amazing results. We are driven by our passion for success and we are proud to deliver best-in-class payment technology and software solutions. Join our dynamic team and make your mark on the payments technology landscape of tomorrow. Global Payments is a market leading, fast-growing, global financial technology company that needs motivated and talented individuals to assist with delivering exceptional results that create great solutions! Our engineering teams utilize industry leading technologies to solve interesting and complicated challenges for our rapidly expanding global payments market. We are relentless in maximizing each individual’s career goals and aspirations, fostering interactions with like-minded people who share the same drive and passion, and allowing the freedom to create your own success. If you are looking for a culture based on engineering excellence, in which your contributions and ideas really make a difference, come join Global Payments! CORE QUALIFICATIONS Candidates who possess most of the following characteristics are encouraged to apply: • Can quickly consume and understand business strategy and operating models; can apply gap analysis techniques to create long-term technical product strategy. o Can ensure technical product and social capabilities match business needs and goals. • Can effectively communicate goals, metrics, and value propositions across the organization. • Can facilitate design, development, and support of existing and new products between business stakeholders. • Collaborate with Product Management and Engineering in the planning, execution, and delivery of existing, and new product offerings. • Assist domain and technical teams with problem-solving complex use cases and systems; while leading technical change and transformation in parallel. • Must have knowledge of .NET system services, communication protocols, and industry technologies. • Must have exposure around Object Oriented Design &amp; Analysis principles in C#; as well as WCF, API, ORM, Cloud, SOA, SaaS, and SQL data store technologies. • Must be able to deep-dive into various data stores to produce meaningful insights, operational intelligence, customer experience visualizations, and proactive trend analyses. • Must be passionate about creating solutions, and solving problems – in the right way, at the right time, and for the right reasons. • Must be teachable, give and receive feedback, and demonstrate success in their discipline on a consistent and transparent basis. EDUCATION • Minimum of 6 years of experience in a product, engineering, development, or technical delivery position. • Bachelor of Science Degree in Computer Science, Business, IT or related discipline; commensurate experience is also accepted. Global Payments Inc. is an equal opportunity employer. Global Payments provides equal employment opportunities to all employees and applicants for employment without regard to race, color, religion, sex (including pregnancy), national origin, ancestry, age, marital status, sexual orientation, gender identity or expression, disability, veteran status, genetic information or any other basis protected by law. If you wish to request reasonable accommodations related to applying for employment or provide feedback about the accessibility of this website, please contact jobs@globalpay.com. Join Our Talent Community Global Payments Inc. (NYSE: GPN) is a leading pure play payments technology company delivering innovative software and services to our customers globally. Our technologies, services and employee expertise enable us to provide a broad range of solutions that allow our customers to operate their businesses more efficiently across a variety of channels around the world. Headquartered in Georgia with nearly 24,000 employees worldwide, Global Payments is a member of the S&amp;P 500 with worldwide reach spanning over 100 countries throughout North America, Europe, Asia Pacific and Latin America. For more information, visit www.globalpaymentsinc.com and follow Global Payments on Twitter (@globalpayinc), LinkedIn and Facebook.</description_text></item><item><id>1681417356</id><date_posted>2025-05-20T00:00:00</date_posted><date_created>2025-05-20T20:44:41.003335</date_created><title>Senior Software Engineer, Cloud Build and Release</title><organization>Calix</organization><organization_url></organization_url><date_validthrough></date_validthrough><locations_raw><item><key name="@type">Place</key><address><key name="@type">PostalAddress</key><addressCountry>Mexico</addressCountry><addressLocality>Remote - Mexico</addressLocality></address></item></locations_raw><locations_alt_raw><item>Remote - Mexico</item></locations_alt_raw><location_type></location_type><location_requirements_raw></location_requirements_raw><salary_raw></salary_raw><employment_type><item>FULL_TIME</item></employment_type><url>https://calix.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/External/job/Remote---Mexico/Senior-Software-Engineer--Cloud-Build-and-Release_R-10605-1</url><source_type>ats</source_type><source>workday</source><source_domain>calix.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com</source_domain><organization_logo></organization_logo><cities_derived></cities_derived><regions_derived></regions_derived><countries_derived><item>Mexico</item></countries_derived><locations_derived><item>Mexico</item></locations_derived><timezones_derived><item>America/Mexico_City</item></timezones_derived><lats_derived><item>19.4333</item></lats_derived><lngs_derived><item>-99.1333</item></lngs_derived><remote_derived>true</remote_derived><description_text>This is a remote-based position in Mexico located in Mexico City or Monterrey. Calix delivers a broadband platform and managed services that enable our customers to improve life one community at a time. We’re at the forefront of a once in a generational change in the broadband industry. Join us as we innovate, help our customers reach their potential, and connect underserved communities with unrivaled digital experiences. Please submit your resume in English - we can only consider applications submitted in this language. We are seeking a highly skilled Cloud Build and Release Engineer with a strong focus on Cloud Platforms – primarily Google, AWS, Azure, etc. to join our dynamic team. The ideal candidate will have extensive experience with continuous integration (CI) and continuous deployment (CD) processes and be well-versed in modern tools and methodologies. The Build and Release Engineer is proficient in SCM methodologies and capable of performing tasks required for release engineering, whether operational, process-oriented, or project-based. The candidate is expected to continually strive to improve tools and processes and foster relationships with other areas by building strong networks. They will support the entire Cloud Products team in managing multiple complex releases throughout the product lifecycle, including code submission, branching, merging, conflict resolution, source code control and health, build, compile, release, and sustaining. A successful candidate will have experience in a fast-paced, multiple product environment and be motivated to deliver quality in everything they do. This position carries tremendous responsibility and high visibility within the Cloud team and the overall company. The ideal candidate should be passionate about the build process and operations, enjoy repeatable and scripted work, manage their time and commitments effectively, excel at executing detailed and complex run lists, quickly learn and internalize a repeatable SCM process, and be a clear and thorough communicator. Responsibilities and Duties: Build configuration, administration, and troubleshooting of highly complex products using cloud microservice architecture. Ad hoc troubleshooting of merge and release blockers (configurations, code, quality checks) and support triaging efforts related to code management and release. Execute branch management and code promotion throughout the development and release cycle. Design, Implement, and manage cloud-native microservices using modern DevOps practices. Automate plan creations and update multiple build plans using REST API and YAML. Automate the promotion and deployment of artifacts using tools such as Argo CD. Utilize Maven for build automation and dependency management in a microservices environment. Implement and manage containerization and orchestration technologies such as Docker and Kubernetes. Manage and optimize CI/CD pipelines using tools like Bitbucket, Bamboo/Jenkins, along with artifact management tools such as Google Artifactory Repository (GAR) and Sonatype Nexus, or JFrog. Responsible for artifact lifecycle from creation to promotion across different environment (dev, stage, prod). Collaborate with cross-functional teams to ensure seamless integration and deployment of applications. Document process workflows, FAQs, and technical documentation, and provide training to various stakeholders. Champion best practices in DevOps, including infrastructure as code, version control, and automated testing, to improve efficiency and maintainability. Work closely with the Release and Deployment team to provide SCM and build support. Qualifications: 10+ years of Build/Release experience using Cloud Platform. Bachelor’s Degree in Computer Science or equivalent experience. Strong technical skills in programming/scripting. Hands-on experience with any of the following programming languages: Python, Java, C++, Go. Proficiency with using Python, REST API, and YAML. Proficiency in container management and orchestration technologies (Kubernetes, Mesos, Docker, Swarm). Experience with package managers (Helm). Experience with Repository Management (Google Artifactory Repository, Nexus, or JFrog). Strong experience with Jira, Bitbucket/GitHub, Bamboo/Jenkins as an administrator. Strong Linux and GIT skills. Basic JQL an SQL query knowledge and experience. Excellent problem-solving skills and the ability to work in a fast-paced environment. Strong communication and collaboration skills. Knowledge of IT security practices such as encryption, certificates, key management, security mechanisms, and compliance. Excellent verbal and written English communication skills Preferred Skills: Experience with other cloud platforms such as GCP and AWS. Familiarity with additional CI/CD tools and practices. Knowledge of security best practices in a cloud environment. ITIL knowledge. Location: This is a remote-based position in Mexico located in Mexico City or Monterrey. #-LI-Remote PLEASE NOTE: All emails from Calix will come from a &apos;@calix.com&apos; email address. Please verify and confirm any communication from Calix prior to disclosing any personal or financial information. If you receive a communication that you think may not be from Calix, please report it to us at talentandculture@calix.com. Calix delivers a broadband platform and managed services that enable our customers to improve life one community at a time. We’re at the forefront of a once in a generational change in the broadband industry. Join us as we innovate, help our customers reach their potential, and connect underserved communities with unrivaled digital experiences. This is the Calix mission - to enable CSPs of all sizes to Simplify. Innovate. Grow. To learn more, visit the Calix web site at www.calix.com To learn more about our international job opportunities, please visit our International Careers Page If you are a person with a disability needing assistance with the application process please: Email us at calix.interview@calix.com; or Call us at +1 (408) 514-3000. Calix is a Drug Free Workplace. You may access a copy of Calix Candidate Privacy Policy HERE and other Calix Privacy Policies HERE.</description_text></item><item><id>1681132103</id><date_posted>2025-05-20T00:00:00</date_posted><date_created>2025-05-20T18:43:18.883653</date_created><title>Staff Software Engineer - Application Stack</title><organization>Calix</organization><organization_url></organization_url><date_validthrough></date_validthrough><locations_raw><item><key name="@type">Place</key><address><key name="@type">PostalAddress</key><addressCountry>Mexico</addressCountry><addressLocality>Remote - Mexico</addressLocality></address></item></locations_raw><locations_alt_raw><item>Remote - Mexico</item></locations_alt_raw><location_type></location_type><location_requirements_raw></location_requirements_raw><salary_raw></salary_raw><employment_type><item>FULL_TIME</item></employment_type><url>https://calix.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/External/job/Remote---Mexico/Staff-Software-Engineer---Application-Stack_R-10610-2</url><source_type>ats</source_type><source>workday</source><source_domain>calix.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com</source_domain><organization_logo></organization_logo><cities_derived></cities_derived><regions_derived></regions_derived><countries_derived><item>Mexico</item></countries_derived><locations_derived><item>Mexico</item></locations_derived><timezones_derived><item>America/Mexico_City</item></timezones_derived><lats_derived><item>19.4333</item></lats_derived><lngs_derived><item>-99.1333</item></lngs_derived><remote_derived>true</remote_derived><description_text>This is a remote-based position in Mexico located in Mexico City or Monterrey. Calix provides the cloud, software platforms, systems and services required for communications service providers to simplify their businesses, excite their subscribers and grow their value. Our team is growing and we&apos;re looking for a Staff Software Engineer - Application Stack. Please submit your resume in English - we can only consider applications submitted in this language. Responsibilities and Duties: Scale distributed applications, make architectural trade-offs applying synchronous and asynchronous design patterns, write code, and deliver with speediness and quality. Develop multi-tier scalable, high-volume performing, and reliable user-centric applications that operate 24x7. Provide technical leadership, driving and performing best engineering practices to initiate, plan, and execute large-scale, cross functional, and company-wide critical programs. Identify, leverage, and successfully evangelize opportunities to improve engineering productivity. Work closely with product owners to understand, analyze product requirements, provide feedback, and deliver a complete solution. Technical leadership of software design in meeting requirements of service stability, reliability, scalability, and security Produce high quality software that is unit tested, code reviewed, and checked in regularly for continuous integration. Qualifications: Bachelor&apos;s Degree in Computer Science, Engineering, or Mathematics or equivalent experience. 10+ years of highly technical, hands-on software engineering experience. Practical understanding and usage of GCP (or AWS) Cloud platform and services. Expert in Java. Proficiency in other languages like Rust, Go, Python, NodeJS is a plus. Experience in designing and building infrastructure and web services at large scale. Expert knowledge of computer science, with strong competencies in data structures, algorithms, and software design. Strong, creative problem-solving skills and ability to abstract and share details to create meaningful articulation. Proficient in design and implementation of microservices-based, API/Endpoint architectures Strong background in designing and developing event-based / pub-sub workflows &amp; data ingestion solutions. Proficiency and hands on experience with Kafka at scale (or similar) desired. Strong background in transactional databases and good understanding and experience with no-SQL datastores. Organized and goal-focused, ability to deliver in a fast-paced environment Excellent verbal and written English communication skills Location: This is a remote-based position in Mexico located in Mexico City or Monterrey. #LI-Remote PLEASE NOTE: All emails from Calix will come from a &apos;@calix.com&apos; email address. Please verify and confirm any communication from Calix prior to disclosing any personal or financial information. If you receive a communication that you think may not be from Calix, please report it to us at talentandculture@calix.com. Calix delivers a broadband platform and managed services that enable our customers to improve life one community at a time. We’re at the forefront of a once in a generational change in the broadband industry. Join us as we innovate, help our customers reach their potential, and connect underserved communities with unrivaled digital experiences. This is the Calix mission - to enable CSPs of all sizes to Simplify. Innovate. Grow. To learn more, visit the Calix web site at www.calix.com To learn more about our international job opportunities, please visit our International Careers Page If you are a person with a disability needing assistance with the application process please: Email us at calix.interview@calix.com; or Call us at +1 (408) 514-3000. Calix is a Drug Free Workplace. You may access a copy of Calix Candidate Privacy Policy HERE and other Calix Privacy Policies HERE.</description_text></item><item><id>1680834389</id><date_posted>2025-05-20T00:00:00</date_posted><date_created>2025-05-20T16:48:08.174598</date_created><title>Software Engineer</title><organization>Thomson Reuters</organization><organization_url></organization_url><date_validthrough></date_validthrough><locations_raw><item><key name="@type">Place</key><address><key name="@type">PostalAddress</key><addressCountry>Mexico</addressCountry><addressLocality>MEX-Distrito Federal-Reforma 26</addressLocality></address></item></locations_raw><locations_alt_raw><item>MEX-Distrito Federal-Reforma 26</item></locations_alt_raw><location_type>TELECOMMUTE</location_type><location_requirements_raw><item><key name="@type">Country</key><name>Mexico</name></item></location_requirements_raw><salary_raw></salary_raw><employment_type><item>FULL_TIME</item></employment_type><url>https://thomsonreuters.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com/External_Career_Site/job/MEX-Distrito-Federal-Reforma-26/Software-Engineer_JREQ191056</url><source_type>ats</source_type><source>workday</source><source_domain>thomsonreuters.wd5.myworkdayjobs.com</source_domain><organization_logo></organization_logo><cities_derived></cities_derived><regions_derived></regions_derived><countries_derived><item>Mexico</item></countries_derived><locations_derived><item>Mexico</item></locations_derived><timezones_derived><item>America/Mexico_City</item></timezones_derived><lats_derived><item>19.4333</item></lats_derived><lngs_derived><item>-99.1333</item></lngs_derived><remote_derived>false</remote_derived><description_text>Senior Software Engineer Are you passionate about the chance to bring your experience to a world-class company that is market-leading for both content and technology? If yes, we are looking for you! As a Software Engineer at Thomson Reuters, you will play a crucial role in our technology team, driving the design, development, and delivery of cutting-edge software solutions. Your primary purpose will be to enhance customer experience by creating robust, scalable, and efficient software systems. Software Development Engineers are mid-level professionals that design, build, develop and deploy software applications, tools, platforms and services that enable current and future needs of our customers. Software Development Engineers interact with internal and external teams. They work on projects independently and collaborate with cross-functional teams to manage project priorities, deadlines, and deliverables. In this role, you will assist colleagues, Business Analysts, and other team members by solving problems, providing technical guidance, training and helping them. Exceptional attention to detail, strong analytical skills, excellent communication skills, an innovative mindset, the ability to solve complex problems and deep technical ability in software development programming within an agile environment will be key for success. As an SE you should have some experience working with AI technologies Trust is a key value for Thomson Reuters, and your trustworthiness will be essential for the success of our hybrid model of work. About the Role In this opportunity as a Software Engineer, you will be responsible for: Development: Participate in the development of software applications using C++, ensuring they meet business requirements and are secure, scalable, maintainable, and efficient. Develop new features for existing applications as well as create new applications to help meet business needs in areas such as Taxes, Sales, Marketing, Human Resources, Finance, Operations, Procurement, and Supply Chain Management. Customer Obsession: Engage with customers to understand their needs deeply, using feedback and data to drive product enhancements that exceed their expectations. Continuously seek opportunities to simplify and improve the customer journey through process, product, or business model changes. Agile Methodologies: Apply agile methodologies to deliver software solutions swiftly and efficiently. Utilize metrics and data to measure outcomes and iterate on solutions to achieve optimal results. Actively participate in Agile/Scrum team activities such as daily standups, retrospectives, and sprint planning sessions. Co-Creation: Collaborate closely with customers and stakeholders to co-create solutions, building strong, trusted relationships through passion, curiosity, and empathy. Challenge &amp; Commit: Encourage respectful dialogue and debate within the team, seeking diverse viewpoints to drive optimal solutions. Commit to delivering results beyond expectations by maintaining a clear focus on outcomes. Ownership and Accountability: Take ownership of projects beyond your immediate responsibilities, ensuring personal accountability for actions and accelerating results. Growth Mindset: Embrace change and tackle complex challenges head-on. Seek and incorporate external learnings, proactively seek diverse perspectives, and continuously drive innovation through rapid experimentation and learning from failure. Testing and Quality Assurance: Implement feature requests through automated testing, unit testing, integration testing, system testing, user acceptance testing, and quality inspections. Collaboration: Work closely with product owners and other stakeholders on project prioritization and release planning. Participate in sprint or team ceremonies. Best Practices: Apply software engineering best practices such as continuous integration and continuous deployment, pair programming, test-driven development, and domain-driven design. Technology Adoption: Stay abreast of new technologies and their potential adoption within the organization. Help maintain and improve existing codebases by fixing bugs and optimizing performance. Production Support: Support production systems by responding to incidents and implementing hotfixes. About You Experience: 3 years of programming experience in C++. Desirable experience in software engineering and knowledge of other programming languages and technologies, including XML, JSON, XSLT, C#, .Net, JavaScript, and Python. Artificial Intelligence: Experience with LLMs, AI Solutions, and evaluation. Understanding of agentic systems and workflows. Desirable Technical Expertise: Knowledge of GitHub, GitHub actions, XMLSpy, static code analysis with SNYK (or other static code software), JFrog, and Code Coverage (Report) from Microsoft.TestPlatform NuGet. Familiarity with GoogleTest for unit testing (or other unit testing frameworks). Proficient in the use of IDE, VisualStudio preferred. Azure DevOps knowledge is desirable, including ADO Pipelines, dashboards, and boards. Customer Obsessed: Relentlessly curious about customers, consistently demonstrating a deep understanding of their needs and using feedback and data to serve them beyond their expectations. Agile in approach, confident in applying methodologies for fast delivery, and sophisticated in the use of metrics. Challenge &amp; Commit: Skilled at engaging in respectful dialogue and debate, seeking and contributing diverse viewpoints to drive optimal solutions. Clear focus on outcomes and results, taking ownership and accountability for projects and personal actions. Growth Mindset: Embraces change and challenges, seeking out tough and ambiguous problems to solve. Proactively seeks diverse perspectives, offers and seeks candid feedback, and learns quickly from failure to drive innovation. Trustworthiness: Demonstrates a high level of trustworthiness, essential for the success of our hybrid model of work. Able to work independently and responsibly, maintaining integrity and reliability in all tasks. Communication Skills: Excellent communication skills, written and verbal, able to convey complex technical concepts to both technical and non-technical stakeholders effectively. Documents and demonstrates solutions by developing documentation, flowcharts, layouts, diagrams, charts, code comments, and clear code. Excellent active and passive listening skills. Excellent reading comprehension. Collaboration: Strong team player, able to work collaboratively in a fast-paced, dynamic environment, building strong relationships with team members and customers alike. Continuous Learning: Demonstrates a commitment to continuous learning and improvement, staying updated with the latest industry trends and technologies. Strong problem solving and analytical thinking. Ability to understand code and solve problems based on existing good practices and standards #LI-LJ1 What’s in it For You? Hybrid Work Model: We’ve adopted a flexible hybrid working environment (2-3 days a week in the office depending on the role) for our office-based roles while delivering a seamless experience that is digitally and physically connected. Flexibility &amp; Work-Life Balance: Flex My Way is a set of supportive workplace policies designed to help manage personal and professional responsibilities, whether caring for family, giving back to the community, or finding time to refresh and reset. This builds upon our flexible work arrangements, including work from anywhere for up to 8 weeks per year, empowering employees to achieve a better work-life balance. Career Development and Growth: By fostering a culture of continuous learning and skill development, we prepare our talent to tackle tomorrow’s challenges and deliver real-world solutions. Our Grow My Way programming and skills-first approach ensures you have the tools and knowledge to grow, lead, and thrive in an AI-enabled future. Industry Competitive Benefits: We offer comprehensive benefit plans to include flexible vacation, two company-wide Mental Health Days off, access to the Headspace app, retirement savings, tuition reimbursement, employee incentive programs, and resources for mental, physical, and financial wellbeing. Culture: Globally recognized, award-winning reputation for inclusion and belonging, flexibility, work-life balance, and more. We live by our values: Obsess over our Customers, Compete to Win, Challenge (Y)our Thinking, Act Fast / Learn Fast, and Stronger Together. Social Impact: Make an impact in your community with our Social Impact Institute. We offer employees two paid volunteer days off annually and opportunities to get involved with pro-bono consulting projects and Environmental, Social, and Governance (ESG) initiatives. Making a Real-World Impact: We are one of the few companies globally that helps its customers pursue justice, truth, and transparency. Together, with the professionals and institutions we serve, we help uphold the rule of law, turn the wheels of commerce, catch bad actors, report the facts, and provide trusted, unbiased information to people all over the world. About Us Thomson Reuters informs the way forward by bringing together the trusted content and technology that people and organizations need to make the right decisions. We serve professionals across legal, tax, accounting, compliance, government, and media. Our products combine highly specialized software and insights to empower professionals with the data, intelligence, and solutions needed to make informed decisions, and to help institutions in their pursuit of justice, truth, and transparency. Reuters, part of Thomson Reuters, is a world leading provider of trusted journalism and news. We are powered by the talents of 26,000 employees across more than 70 countries, where everyone has a chance to contribute and grow professionally in flexible work environments. At a time when objectivity, accuracy, fairness, and transparency are under attack, we consider it our duty to pursue them. Sound exciting? Join us and help shape the industries that move society forward. As a global business, we rely on the unique backgrounds, perspectives, and experiences of all employees to deliver on our business goals. To ensure we can do that, we seek talented, qualified employees in all our operations around the world regardless of race, color, sex/gender, including pregnancy, gender identity and expression, national origin, religion, sexual orientation, disability, age, marital status, citizen status, veteran status, or any other protected classification under applicable law. Thomson Reuters is proud to be an Equal Employment Opportunity Employer providing a drug-free workplace. We also make reasonable accommodations for qualified individuals with disabilities and for sincerely held religious beliefs in accordance with applicable law. More information on requesting an accommodation here. Learn more on how to protect yourself from fraudulent job postings here. More information about Thomson Reuters can be found on thomsonreuters.com. Thomson Reuters informs the way forward by delivering trusted content and technology that professionals and institutions need to make the right decisions. We are modernizing the pillars of society through the digitalization of the tax and legal professions, the free press, commerce, and the rule of law, and elevating the way professionals and institutions work. Discover how Thomson Reuters approaches AI innovation as Chief Product Officer David Wong breaks down the essential components.</description_text></item><item><id>1680659582</id><date_posted>2025-05-20T00:00:00</date_posted><date_created>2025-05-20T15:40:33.938463</date_created><title>Senior Software Engineer - Full Stack</title><organization>Capital One</organization><organization_url></organization_url><date_validthrough></date_validthrough><locations_raw><item><key name="@type">Place</key><address><key name="@type">PostalAddress</key><addressCountry>Mexico</addressCountry><addressLocality>Ciudad de Mexico</addressLocality></address></item></locations_raw><locations_alt_raw><item>Mexico City, Mexico</item></locations_alt_raw><location_type></location_type><location_requirements_raw></location_requirements_raw><salary_raw></salary_raw><employment_type><item>FULL_TIME</item></employment_type><url>https://capitalone.wd12.myworkdayjobs.com/Capital_One/job/Mexico-City-Mexico/Senior-Software-Engineer---Full-Stack_R193662</url><source_type>ats</source_type><source>workday</source><source_domain>capitalone.wd12.myworkdayjobs.com</source_domain><organization_logo></organization_logo><cities_derived><item>Mexico City</item></cities_derived><regions_derived><item>Ciudad de México</item></regions_derived><countries_derived><item>Mexico</item></countries_derived><locations_derived><item>Mexico City, Ciudad de México, Mexico</item></locations_derived><timezones_derived><item>America/Mexico_City</item></timezones_derived><lats_derived><item>19.4333</item></lats_derived><lngs_derived><item>-99.1333</item></lngs_derived><remote_derived>false</remote_derived><description_text>WeWork Reforma Latino (97001), Mexico, Ciudad de Mexico, Ciudad de Mexico Senior Software Engineer - Full Stack Do you love building and pioneering in the technology space? Do you enjoy solving complex business problems in a fast-paced, collaborative, inclusive, and iterative delivery environment? At Capital One, you&apos;ll be part of a big group of makers, breakers, doers and disruptors, who solve real problems and meet real customer needs. We are seeking Full Stack Software Engineers who are passionate about marrying data with emerging technologies. As a Capital One Senior Software Engineer, you’ll have the opportunity to be on the forefront of driving a major transformation within Capital One. What You’ll Do: Collaborate with and across Agile teams to design, develop, test, implement, and support technical solutions in full-stack development tools and technologies Share your passion for staying on top of tech trends, experimenting with and learning new technologies, participating in internal &amp; external technology communities, mentoring other members of the engineering community Collaborate with digital product managers, and deliver robust cloud-based solutions that drive powerful experiences to help millions of Americans achieve financial empowerment Utilize programming languages like JavaScript, Java, HTML/CSS, TypeScript, SQL, Python, and Go, Open Source RDBMS and NoSQL databases, Container Orchestration services including Docker and Kubernetes, and a variety of AWS tools and services Basic Qualifications: Intermediate-Advanced English fluency Bachelor’s Degree At least 4 years of experience in software engineering (Internship experience does not apply) Preferred Qualifications: At least 5 years of experience in at least one of the following: JavaScript, Java, TypeScript, SQL, Python, C#/.Net or Go At least 1 year of experience with AWS, Serverless, or another cloud service At least 3 years of experience in open source frameworks At least 2 years of experience in Agile practices Capital One will only consider candidates that are Mexico citizens or permanent residents. At Capital One, we respect individual differences in culture, religion, and ethnicity. Likewise, we promote equal opportunities and development for all personnel. In the hiring process, we seek to provide equal employment opportunities to candidates, regardless of race, color, religion, gender, sexual orientation, marital or civil status, national origin, disability, or any other situation protected by federal, state, or local laws. For technical support or questions about Capital One&apos;s recruiting process, please send an email to Careers@capitalone.com Capital One does not provide, endorse nor guarantee and is not liable for third-party products, services, educational tools or other information available through this site. Capital One Financial is made up of several different entities. Please note that any position posted in Canada is for Capital One Canada, any position posted in the United Kingdom is for Capital One Europe, any position posted in the Philippines is for Capital One Service Corp (COPSSC), and any position posted in Mexico is for Capital One Technology Labs Mexico. At Capital One, we’re building a leading information-based technology company. Still founder-led by Chairman and Chief Executive Officer Richard Fairbank, Capital One is on a mission to help our customers succeed by bringing ingenuity, simplicity, and humanity to banking. We measure our efforts by the success our customers enjoy and the advocacy they exhibit.</description_text></item><item><id>1680523519</id><date_posted>2025-05-20T00:00:00</date_posted><date_created>2025-05-20T14:49:52.980122</date_created><title>Staff Software Engineer - Application Stack</title><organization>Calix</organization><organization_url></organization_url><date_validthrough></date_validthrough><locations_raw><item><key name="@type">Place</key><address><key name="@type">PostalAddress</key><addressCountry>Mexico</addressCountry><addressLocality>Remote - Mexico</addressLocality></address></item></locations_raw><locations_alt_raw><item>Remote - Mexico</item></locations_alt_raw><location_type></location_type><location_requirements_raw></location_requirements_raw><salary_raw></salary_raw><employment_type><item>FULL_TIME</item></employment_type><url>https://calix.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/ExternalInternational/job/Remote---Mexico/Staff-Software-Engineer---Application-Stack_R-10610</url><source_type>ats</source_type><source>workday</source><source_domain>calix.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com</source_domain><organization_logo></organization_logo><cities_derived></cities_derived><regions_derived></regions_derived><countries_derived><item>Mexico</item></countries_derived><locations_derived><item>Mexico</item></locations_derived><timezones_derived><item>America/Mexico_City</item></timezones_derived><lats_derived><item>19.4333</item></lats_derived><lngs_derived><item>-99.1333</item></lngs_derived><remote_derived>true</remote_derived><description_text>This is a remote-based position in Mexico located in Mexico City or Monterrey. Calix provides the cloud, software platforms, systems and services required for communications service providers to simplify their businesses, excite their subscribers and grow their value. Our team is growing and we&apos;re looking for a Staff Software Engineer - Application Stack. Please submit your resume in English - we can only consider applications submitted in this language. Responsibilities and Duties: Scale distributed applications, make architectural trade-offs applying synchronous and asynchronous design patterns, write code, and deliver with speediness and quality. Develop multi-tier scalable, high-volume performing, and reliable user-centric applications that operate 24x7. Provide technical leadership, driving and performing best engineering practices to initiate, plan, and execute large-scale, cross functional, and company-wide critical programs. Identify, leverage, and successfully evangelize opportunities to improve engineering productivity. Work closely with product owners to understand, analyze product requirements, provide feedback, and deliver a complete solution. Technical leadership of software design in meeting requirements of service stability, reliability, scalability, and security Produce high quality software that is unit tested, code reviewed, and checked in regularly for continuous integration. Qualifications: Bachelor&apos;s Degree in Computer Science, Engineering, or Mathematics or equivalent experience. 10+ years of highly technical, hands-on software engineering experience. Practical understanding and usage of GCP (or AWS) Cloud platform and services. Expert in Java. Proficiency in other languages like Rust, Go, Python, NodeJS is a plus. Experience in designing and building infrastructure and web services at large scale. Expert knowledge of computer science, with strong competencies in data structures, algorithms, and software design. Strong, creative problem-solving skills and ability to abstract and share details to create meaningful articulation. Proficient in design and implementation of microservices-based, API/Endpoint architectures Strong background in designing and developing event-based / pub-sub workflows &amp; data ingestion solutions. Proficiency and hands on experience with Kafka at scale (or similar) desired. Strong background in transactional databases and good understanding and experience with no-SQL datastores. Organized and goal-focused, ability to deliver in a fast-paced environment Excellent verbal and written English communication skills Location: This is a remote-based position in Mexico located in Mexico City or Monterrey. #LI-Remote PLEASE NOTE: All emails from Calix will come from a &apos;@calix.com&apos; email address. Please verify and confirm any communication from Calix prior to disclosing any personal or financial information. If you receive a communication that you think may not be from Calix, please report it to us at talentandculture@calix.com. Calix delivers a broadband platform and managed services that enable our customers to improve life one community at a time. We’re at the forefront of a once in a generational change in the broadband industry. Join us as we innovate, help our customers reach their potential, and connect underserved communities with unrivaled digital experiences. This is the Calix mission - to enable CSPs of all sizes to Simplify. Innovate. Grow. To learn more, visit the Calix web site at www.calix.com If you are a person with a disability needing assistance with the application process please: Email us at calix.interview@calix.com; or Call us at +1 (408) 514-3000. Calix is a Drug Free Workplace. You may access a copy of Calix Candidate Privacy Policy HERE and other Calix Privacy Policies HERE.</description_text></item></jobs>