<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><jobs><item><id>1689101107</id><date_posted>2025-05-23T07:31:09.58</date_posted><date_created>2025-05-23T08:25:29.020271</date_created><title>Software Engineer III, Chrome</title><organization>Google</organization><organization_url>https://www.google.com</organization_url><date_validthrough></date_validthrough><locations_raw><item><key name="@type">Place</key><address><key name="@type">PostalAddress</key><addressCountry>MX</addressCountry><addressLocality>Mexico City</addressLocality><addressRegion>CDMX</addressRegion></address></item></locations_raw><locations_alt_raw></locations_alt_raw><location_type></location_type><location_requirements_raw></location_requirements_raw><salary_raw></salary_raw><employment_type></employment_type><url>https://www.google.com/about/careers/applications/jobs/results/139898173249200838</url><source_type>ats</source_type><source>in-house</source><source_domain>google.com</source_domain><organization_logo></organization_logo><cities_derived><item>Mexico City</item></cities_derived><regions_derived><item>Ciudad de México</item></regions_derived><countries_derived><item>Mexico</item></countries_derived><locations_derived><item>Mexico City, Ciudad de México, Mexico</item></locations_derived><timezones_derived><item>America/Mexico_City</item></timezones_derived><lats_derived><item>19.4333</item></lats_derived><lngs_derived><item>-99.1333</item></lngs_derived><remote_derived>false</remote_derived><description_text>MINIMUM QUALIFICATIONS:

 * Bachelor’s degree or equivalent practical experience.
 * 2 years of experience with software development in one or more programming
   languages, or 1 year of experience with an advanced degree in an industry
   setting.
 * 2 years of experience with data structures or algorithms in either an
   academic or industry setting.



PREFERRED QUALIFICATIONS:

 * Experience with open source software and infrastructure development.
 * Experience in software development in one or more of the following languages:
   Python, C/C++, Java, Rust.
 * Experience with fuzzing and vulnerability research.
 * Knowledge of security engineering (e.g., memory safety issues).


ABOUT THE JOB:

Google&apos;s software engineers develop the next-generation technologies that change
how billions of users connect, explore, and interact with information and one
another. Our products need to handle information at massive scale, and extend
well beyond web search. We&apos;re looking for engineers who bring fresh ideas from
all areas, including information retrieval, distributed computing, large-scale
system design, networking and data storage, security, artificial intelligence,
natural language processing, UI design and mobile; the list goes on and is
growing every day. As a software engineer, you will work on a specific project
critical to Google’s needs with opportunities to switch teams and projects as
you and our fast-paced business grow and evolve. We need our engineers to be
versatile, display leadership qualities and be enthusiastic to take on new
problems across the full-stack as we continue to push technology forward.

In this role, with your technical expertise, you will manage project priorities,
deadlines, and deliverables. You will design, develop, test, deploy, maintain,
and enhance software solutions.Chrome is dedicated to building a better, more
open web. We’re focused on making a better browser (on both desktop and mobile)
to help users take advantage of all the web has to offer in a safe and secure
way.Chrome is available across all major platforms — iOS, Android, Windows, Mac,
Linux and Chrome OS. We also built Chrome as an open source project so the
entire web ecosystem could benefit from the latest innovations in speed,
simplicity and security.


RESPONSIBILITIES:

 * Write product or system development code.
 * Participate in, or lead design reviews with peers and stakeholders to decide
   amongst available technologies.
 * Review code developed by other developers and provide feedback to ensure best
   practices (e.g., style guidelines, checking code in, accuracy, testability,
   and efficiency).
 * Contribute to existing documentation or educational content and adapt content
   based on product/program updates and user feedback.
 * Triage product or system issues and debug/track/resolve by analyzing the
   sources of issues and the impact on hardware, network, or service operations
   and quality.</description_text></item><item><id>1688227055</id><date_posted>2025-05-22T23:24:27</date_posted><date_created>2025-05-23T00:25:54.089573</date_created><title>Platform Software Engineer (Full Stack) - Contract</title><organization>Tech Holding</organization><organization_url></organization_url><date_validthrough></date_validthrough><locations_raw><item><key name="@type">Place</key><name>Mexico, Remote</name><address><key name="@type">PostalAddress</key><name>Mexico, Remote</name><addressCountry></addressCountry><addressLocality>Mexico, Remote</addressLocality></address></item></locations_raw><locations_alt_raw></locations_alt_raw><location_type></location_type><location_requirements_raw></location_requirements_raw><salary_raw></salary_raw><employment_type></employment_type><url>https://job-boards.greenhouse.io/techholding/jobs/4568690005</url><source_type>ats</source_type><source>greenhouse</source><source_domain>job-boards.greenhouse.io</source_domain><organization_logo></organization_logo><cities_derived></cities_derived><regions_derived></regions_derived><countries_derived><item>Mexico</item></countries_derived><locations_derived><item>Mexico</item></locations_derived><timezones_derived><item>America/Mexico_City</item></timezones_derived><lats_derived><item>19.4333</item></lats_derived><lngs_derived><item>-99.1333</item></lngs_derived><remote_derived>true</remote_derived><description_text>About us:
Working at Tech Holding isn&apos;t just a job, it&apos;s an opportunity to be a part of something bigger. We are a full-service consulting firm that was founded on the premise of delivering predictable outcomes and high-quality solutions to our clients. Our founders and team members have industry experience and have held senior positions in a wide variety of companies – from emerging startups to large Fortune 50 firms – and we have taken our combined experiences and developed a unique approach that is supported by the principles of deep expertise, integrity, transparency, and dependability.
The Role
As a Platform Software Engineer, you will work with a team of talented software developers to expand and mature a kitchen automation system and cloud-connected infrastructure. You will perform hard-core coding, debugging, testing, and troubleshooting throughout the development process. You will use your expertise in software engineering to own the design, prototype, and commercialization of core software. You will collaborate closely with robotics specialists in controls, machine learning, and computer vision.
What You’ll Do
Code, debug, test and troubleshoot software throughout the development process.
Develop sophisticated state machines that efficiently manage and optimize various cooking 
workflows.
Engineer streamlined, user-friendly procedures for robotic system installations ensuring a smooth 
user experience.
Design and implement robust monitoring solutions to continuously track and ensure the health of 
our robotic systems in various environments.
Use best engineering judgment to iterate on code and refactoring repeatedly to improve our 
software generality and quality.
Read our code and documentation to understand our existing architecture and practices.
Adhere to and help improve our software development lifecycle (SDLC) processes.
Take ownership when developing, maintaining, improving, testing and releasing software.
Create unit tests and system-level tests to verify code functionality.
Create architectural diagrams that demonstrate flow of data through the system.
Requirements
BS or higher in Computer Science (or related field) and 2+ years of relevant industry experience
Experience in system software, network stacks, state machines, and SQL databases for robotic 
systems
Python programming expertise and familiarity with C++
Proficiency in developing applications in the Robot Operating System (ROS)
Proficiency with working in development environments that comprise of Linux, Docker, and Git
Self-motivated, responsible, and excellent written and verbal interpersonal skills
Ability to collaborate effectively as a remote team member
Strong attention to detail, analytical skills, and ability to learn quickly
Collaborative team player with a drive to take initiative and ownership
Must be available to work in Pacific Time (PT) zone
Preferred Qualifications
Experience with cloud and edge computing
Experience developing platforms that serve multiple robotic products
What We Offer
Remote opportunity with collaborative team culture
Exposure to cloud-first environments and modern DevOps tooling
Opportunities for growth and cross-functional impact
Dynamic and fast-paced engineering environment
Tech Holding is proud to be an Equal Opportunity Employer and is committed to fostering a diverse and inclusive workplace. We welcome applicants from all backgrounds and experiences, and we consider qualified applicants without regard to race, color, religion, gender, sexual orientation, gender identity, national origin, disability, veteran status, or any other legally protected characteristic. If you require accommodation in the application process, please contact our HR</description_text></item><item><id>1687606707</id><date_posted>2025-05-22T19:09:03</date_posted><date_created>2025-05-22T19:17:33.769764</date_created><title>Senior Data &amp; Software Engineer</title><organization>Kunai</organization><organization_url></organization_url><date_validthrough></date_validthrough><locations_raw><item><key name="@type">Place</key><name>Remote - Mexico</name><address><key name="@type">PostalAddress</key><name>Remote - Mexico</name><addressCountry></addressCountry><addressLocality>Remote - Mexico</addressLocality></address></item></locations_raw><locations_alt_raw></locations_alt_raw><location_type></location_type><location_requirements_raw></location_requirements_raw><salary_raw></salary_raw><employment_type></employment_type><url>https://job-boards.greenhouse.io/kunai/jobs/4742672007</url><source_type>ats</source_type><source>greenhouse</source><source_domain>job-boards.greenhouse.io</source_domain><organization_logo></organization_logo><cities_derived></cities_derived><regions_derived></regions_derived><countries_derived><item>Mexico</item></countries_derived><locations_derived><item>Mexico</item></locations_derived><timezones_derived><item>America/Mexico_City</item></timezones_derived><lats_derived><item>19.4333</item></lats_derived><lngs_derived><item>-99.1333</item></lngs_derived><remote_derived>true</remote_derived><description_text>Kunai builds full-stack technology solutions for banks, credit and payment networks, infrastructure providers, and their customers. Together, we are changing the world’s relationship with financial services. At Kunai, we help our clients modernize, capitalize on emerging trends, and evolve their business for the coming decades by remaining tech-agnostic and human-centered.
Kunai is working with a major credit card organization in Mexico City, to build the platform that companies use to manage their corporate card program. This includes everything from applying for a card, to upgrades, payments, statements, reward points - the whole thing end to end. We will build on a modern tech stack, pushing to the cloud, and have a lot of fun while we get there.
In this role, you will oversee all technical aspects of the databases for a Global Corporate Client Platform, that powers not only the global work suite of applications, but over 75 mission critical applications. This role requires a deep understanding of database architectures and hands-on experience with database technologies, preferably PostgreSQL as that is our target technology in the modernization initiatives. Successful candidates will ensure strong control management, proactive risk management, optimal database performance, security, resiliency, integrity, and availability, along with implementing innovative solutions such as the Point of Arrival (POA) system for the data layer.
Experience
6+ years of software development experience in a professional environment and/or comparable experience including: 
A wide breadth of engineering experience
Proven experience working with teams of engineers
Hands-on expertise with application design, software development, and automated testing
Experience with distributed (multi-tiered) systems, algorithms, and relational databases
Experience in database development, tuning, and administration
Qualifications
Bachelor’s degree in computer science, computer science engineering, or related experience required; advanced degree preferred
3+ years of hands-on Java development
3+ years working with PostgreSQL
Experience in API design and Architecture, SOAP and REST
Experience in Database modernization or Migration
Nice to have
Hands-on knowledge of Spark
Experience in Scala development
Experience with Systems of Record (SOR)
Prior experience migrating from legacy (the current environment is DB2) data environments 
This is a primarily a remote role, but will require going a couple of days a month to the CDMX office
Our success over the past 20 years is rooted in our exceptional team, which thrives in a culture of collaboration, creativity, and continuous learning. 

We are proud to offer our employees a range of benefits, including competitive compensation, professional development opportunities, and flexible work arrangements, all designed to help them thrive. As we continue to expand, we remain committed to cultivating an environment where people feel valued, have a voice, and are given the tools to grow—both personally and professionally—while pushing the boundaries of innovation in the fintech industry.</description_text></item><item><id>1687477088</id><date_posted>2025-05-22T17:31:01.15</date_posted><date_created>2025-05-22T18:25:30.426983</date_created><title>Software Engineer, Chrome Accessibility</title><organization>Google</organization><organization_url>https://www.google.com</organization_url><date_validthrough></date_validthrough><locations_raw><item><key name="@type">Place</key><address><key name="@type">PostalAddress</key><addressCountry>MX</addressCountry><addressLocality>Mexico City</addressLocality><addressRegion>CDMX</addressRegion></address></item></locations_raw><locations_alt_raw></locations_alt_raw><location_type></location_type><location_requirements_raw></location_requirements_raw><salary_raw></salary_raw><employment_type></employment_type><url>https://www.google.com/about/careers/applications/jobs/results/109029229680566982</url><source_type>ats</source_type><source>in-house</source><source_domain>google.com</source_domain><organization_logo></organization_logo><cities_derived><item>Mexico City</item></cities_derived><regions_derived><item>Ciudad de México</item></regions_derived><countries_derived><item>Mexico</item></countries_derived><locations_derived><item>Mexico City, Ciudad de México, Mexico</item></locations_derived><timezones_derived><item>America/Mexico_City</item></timezones_derived><lats_derived><item>19.4333</item></lats_derived><lngs_derived><item>-99.1333</item></lngs_derived><remote_derived>false</remote_derived><description_text>MINIMUM QUALIFICATIONS:

 * Bachelor’s degree or equivalent practical experience.
 * 2 years of experience with data structures/algorithms and software
   development in one or more programming languages.



PREFERRED QUALIFICATIONS:

 * Master&apos;s degree or PhD in Computer Science or related technical fields.
 * Experience developing accessible technologies.
 * Experience with C++, JavaScript and Web Applications.
 * Experience with Chrome and Chrome OS.


ABOUT THE JOB:

Google&apos;s software engineers develop the next-generation technologies that change
how billions of users connect, explore, and interact with information and one
another. Our products need to handle information at massive scale, and extend
well beyond web search. We&apos;re looking for engineers who bring fresh ideas from
all areas, including information retrieval, distributed computing, large-scale
system design, networking and data storage, security, artificial intelligence,
natural language processing, UI design and mobile; the list goes on and is
growing every day. As a software engineer, you will work on a specific project
critical to Google’s needs with opportunities to switch teams and projects as
you and our fast-paced business grow and evolve. We need our engineers to be
versatile, display leadership qualities and be enthusiastic to take on new
problems across the full-stack as we continue to push technology forward.

As a Software Engineer working with the Chrome Accessibility team, you will help
us make Chrome universally accessible and useful. Without the things we build,
some users wouldn’t be able to use Chrome at all. We are focused on opening new
possibilities for these users and making new experiences possible for them.
Going beyond just enabling people to use our products and services, we want to
find new ways to become a companion in people’s lives. Your projects will have
crucial impact on these users as you address hard technical problems and
coordinate with many teams at Google to find solutions that make Chrome an
amazing platform for everyone.

Chrome is dedicated to building a better, more open web. We’re focused on making
a better browser (on both desktop and mobile) to help users take advantage of
all the web has to offer in a safe and secure way.Chrome is available across all
major platforms — iOS, Android, Windows, Mac, Linux and Chrome OS. We also built
Chrome as an open source project so the entire web ecosystem could benefit from
the latest innovations in speed, simplicity and security.


RESPONSIBILITIES:

 * Work closely with UX designers, Product Managers, and other engineers to
   define, design, and implement accessibility and immersive reading features.
 * Work on Chrome browser features to improve the experience for users with
   disabilities, including those who rely on third-party assistive technology.
 * Build and improve Chrome OS platform features for users with disabilities,
   including screen reading, braille support, magnification, color enhancement,
   and more.
 * Improve the web platform with tools and APIs to help developers make their
   web apps accessible to everyone.
 * Stay up-to-date with the latest accessibility standards and best practices.</description_text></item><item><id>1687120227</id><date_posted>2025-05-22T15:21:18.685</date_posted><date_created>2025-05-22T15:25:06.825038</date_created><title>Software Engineer II - Android</title><organization>McDonald&apos;s Corporation</organization><organization_url></organization_url><date_validthrough></date_validthrough><locations_raw><item><address><streetAddress>Calz. Gral. Mariano Escobedo 595 Rincón del Bosque, Bosque de Chapultepec I Secc, Miguel Hidalgo</streetAddress><addressLocality>Ciudad de México</addressLocality><postalCode>11580</postalCode><addressCountry>Mexico</addressCountry></address></item></locations_raw><locations_alt_raw><item>Calz. Gral. Mariano Escobedo 595 Rincón del Bosque, Bosque de Chapultepec I Secc, Miguel Hidalgo, Ciudad de México, Mexico</item></locations_alt_raw><location_type></location_type><location_requirements_raw></location_requirements_raw><salary_raw></salary_raw><employment_type><item>Full-time</item></employment_type><url>https://jobs.smartrecruiters.com/McDonaldsCorporation/744000061017575-software-engineer-ii-android</url><source_type>ats</source_type><source>smartrecruiters</source><source_domain>jobs.smartrecruiters.com</source_domain><organization_logo></organization_logo><cities_derived><item>Mexico City</item></cities_derived><regions_derived><item>Ciudad de México</item></regions_derived><countries_derived><item>Mexico</item></countries_derived><locations_derived><item>Mexico City, Ciudad de México, Mexico</item></locations_derived><timezones_derived><item>America/Mexico_City</item></timezones_derived><lats_derived><item>19.4333</item></lats_derived><lngs_derived><item>-99.1333</item></lngs_derived><remote_derived>false</remote_derived><description_text>Company DescriptionMcDonald’s growth strategy, Accelerating the Arches, encompasses all aspects of our business as the leading global omni-channel restaurant brand. As the consumer landscape shifts we are using our competitive advantages to further strengthen our brand. One of our core growth strategies is to Double Down on the 3Ds (Delivery, Digital and Drive Thru). McDonald’s will accelerate technology innovation so 65M+ customers a day will experience a fast, easy experience, whether at one of our 25,000 and growing Drive Thrus, through McDelivery, dine-in or takeaway.  McDonald’s Global Technology is here to power tomorrow’s feel-good moments.  That’s why you’ll find us at the forefront of transformative technology, exploring new and innovative ways to serve our millions of customers and spread happiness one delicious Hot Fudge Sundae-dipped fry at a time. Using AI, robotics and emerging tech, we’re digitizing the Golden Arches. Combine that with our unparalleled global scale, and we’re reshaping all areas of the business, industry and every community that is home to a McDonald’s restaurant. We face complex tech challenges every day. But that’s where our diverse and talented teams come in. They’re made up of the best and brightest from all over the globe, and they thrive in the space where feel-good meets fast-paced.  We’re recruiting engineers to join our Global Technology team in Mexico City as we open our McDonald&apos;s in Mexico office. Our Mexico City office will be a hub for technology innovation and operational support to help us build the solutions that will improve our customer, crew and employee experience each and every day. Check out the McDonald’s  Global Technology Technical Blog to learn how technology and our global team are directly enabling the Accelerating the Arches strategy. Job DescriptionContribute to all aspects of the agile development life cycle including design, development, documentation, testing and operations.As a software development engineer on a team, you will play a pivotal role in shaping the definition, vision, design, road map and development of product features from beginning to end.Design, implement, test, deploy and maintain innovative software solutions to transform service performance, durability, cost, and security.Use software engineering best practices to ensure a high standard of quality for all team deliverables.Work in an agile, startup-like development environment, where you are always working on the most important priorities.Qualifications2+ years of non-internship professional software development experience.Extensive programming experience with Kotlin, Java, and Android platform technologies and APIs.Bachelor’s Degree in Computer Science or related field or equivalent years of experience.Solid knowledge of Computer Science fundamentals (object-oriented design, data structures and algorithm.Strong verbal and written communication skills.Solution-oriented attitude and ability to solve tough problems in a collaborative, cross-functional, and fast-paced environment.Demonstrated leadership abilities in an engineering environment in driving operational excellence and best practices.Highly quantitative with great judgment and passion for building a great customer experience.Uncompromising attention to detail and drive to continuously improve the product.Ability to take a project from scoping requirements to launch to delivery.#LI-Hybrid</description_text></item><item><id>1687809345</id><date_posted>2025-05-22T00:00:00</date_posted><date_created>2025-05-22T20:49:31.6896</date_created><title>Senior Software Engineer</title><organization>TigerConnect</organization><organization_url></organization_url><date_validthrough></date_validthrough><locations_raw><item><key name="@type">Place</key><address><key name="@type">PostalAddress</key><addressCountry>Mexico</addressCountry><addressLocality>Mexico City</addressLocality></address></item></locations_raw><locations_alt_raw><item>Hybrid - Mexico City, Mexico</item></locations_alt_raw><location_type></location_type><location_requirements_raw></location_requirements_raw><salary_raw></salary_raw><employment_type><item>FULL_TIME</item></employment_type><url>https://tigerconnect.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/TC/job/Hybrid---Mexico-City-Mexico/Senior-Software-Engineer_R003053</url><source_type>ats</source_type><source>workday</source><source_domain>tigerconnect.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com</source_domain><organization_logo></organization_logo><cities_derived><item>Mexico City</item></cities_derived><regions_derived><item>Ciudad de México</item></regions_derived><countries_derived><item>Mexico</item></countries_derived><locations_derived><item>Mexico City, Ciudad de México, Mexico</item></locations_derived><timezones_derived><item>America/Mexico_City</item></timezones_derived><lats_derived><item>19.4333</item></lats_derived><lngs_derived><item>-99.1333</item></lngs_derived><remote_derived>false</remote_derived><description_text>TigerConnect transforms healthcare with the industry’s most widely adopted clinical collaboration platform – uniquely modernizing the way doctors, nurses, care teams, patients, and data connect. With solutions spanning care team communication, scheduling automation, alarm management and event notifications, nurse call, patient engagement and more, we accelerate productivity, reduce costs, and improve patient outcomes, safely and securely. More than 8,000 healthcare organizations trust us to deliver enterprise-ready solutions, making this possible with the right group of dedicated, thoughtful trailblazers. Today, private practice doctor’s offices, small and large hospice centers, and some of the largest healthcare organizations in the United States rely on TigerConnect. We’re a fun, hungry, smart, innovative group of eclectic people who are passionate about transforming the way clinical care teams work and communicate. TigerConnect transforms healthcare with the industry’s most widely adopted clinical collaboration platform – uniquely modernizing the way doctors, nurses, care teams, patients, and data connect. With solutions spanning care team communication, scheduling automation, alarm management and event notifications, nurse call, patient engagement and more, we accelerate productivity, reduce costs, and improve patient outcomes, safely and securely. More than 8,000 healthcare organizations trust us to deliver enterprise-ready solutions, making this possible with the right group of dedicated, thoughtful trailblazers. Today, private practice doctor’s offices, small and large hospice centers, and some of the largest healthcare organizations in the United States rely on TigerConnect. We’re a fun, hungry, smart, innovative group of eclectic people who are passionate about transforming the way clinical care teams work and communicate. TigerConnect is looking for an experienced Senior JavaScript Engineer to join our team and help build a platform used by thousands of first responders, nurses, and doctors. You will play a leading role in all aspects of our platform development including REST API, MongoDB configuration, AWS DevOps, Android and iOS development. Above all, your work will impact the way hospitals save lives during an emergency. What You’ll Be Doing: Lead the design and development of scalable backend services using Node.js and TypeScript Architect and implement RESTful APIs to support mobile and web applications Configure and manage MongoDB databases, ensuring optimal performance and data integrity Collaborate with cross-functional teams to integrate cloud infrastructure solutions, particularly within AWS environments Develop and maintain front-end components using modern JavaScript frameworks such as Vue or React Participate in test-driven development practices, including pair programming and mobbing sessions Utilize AI tools to enhance development workflows and code quality Mentor team members, fostering a culture of continuous learning and knowledge sharing What You Bring: 8+ years professional experience with JavaScript and Typescript, with minimum of 4 years professional experience with enterprise scale platform development using Node.js Experience configuring and maintaining cloud infrastructure (preferably with AWS) Experience with front end JavaScript development in any of the following JS frameworks (Vue, React) Experience with App development in any of the following JS frameworks (iOS, Android, Flutter) All development is done with pairing and mobbing with TDD. You MUST have experience in this type of environment Experience using AI to augment development and coding You&apos;re a team player who actively teaches the team in areas where you are skilled while showing an eagerness to step out of your comfort zone and learn completely unfamiliar things by engaging with the team and asking for help in the areas where you&apos;re not as skilled Perks &amp; Benefits We Offer: Join us in our prime office space in the heart of Mexico City&apos;s Reforma area; Our hybrid teams unite top talent from Mexico, the US, and beyond, offering flexibility and collaboration Enjoy our comprehensive benefits with excellent private medical, dental, vision, and life insurance coverage for you and your family Focus on your well-being through our wellness reimbursement program and company-wide wellness days (extra days off to rest and recharge) Take advantage of extra perks and benefits, including a savings fund, monthly teleworking allowance, grocery vouchers, and travel insurance In addition to the minimum days off required by law, our Flexible Time Off program gives you extra time to enjoy the things you love Join a mission-driven team committed to making a real impact in the world of healthcare Our mission is to provide a healthcare communication solution that radically improves the way care is delivered. We’ve been recognized as one of the Best Places to Work in Los Angeles (2022), as well as on the list of Best Paying Companies (2022) with the Best Perks &amp; Benefits (2022). We were also honored to be named to Inc. 5000’s list of Fastest Growing Companies. TigerConnect is an equal opportunity employer and values diversity at our company! We do not discriminate on the basis of race, religion, color, national origin, sex, gender, gender expression, sexual orientation, age, marital status, veteran status, or disability status. We will ensure that individuals with disabilities are provided reasonable accommodation to participate in the job application or interview process, to perform essential job functions, and to receive other benefits and privileges of employment. Please contact us to request accommodation. TigerConnect is on a mission to transform and improve communication and workflows in hospitals and the healthcare industry overall. This is without a doubt a tall task, but one that we’ve been solving since 2010 and will continue to tackle with the right group of dedicated, thoughtful trailblazers. Headquartered in Santa Monica, California, and with team members across seven countries, TigerConnect believes that the people building and supporting our products are the core to our success. From our outstanding benefits package to our focus on mental health &amp; wellbeing to our life-saving products — working at TigerConnect allows you to build partnerships and truly make an impact on how healthcare communication is delivered.</description_text></item><item><id>1687687973</id><date_posted>2025-05-22T00:00:00</date_posted><date_created>2025-05-22T19:54:37.972119</date_created><title>Senior Software Engineer - Java, Fullstack</title><organization>3Pillar</organization><organization_url></organization_url><date_validthrough></date_validthrough><locations_raw><item><key name="@type">Place</key><address><key name="@type">PostalAddress</key><addressLocality>Mexico</addressLocality><addressRegion></addressRegion><addressCountry></addressCountry><postalCode></postalCode></address></item></locations_raw><locations_alt_raw></locations_alt_raw><location_type></location_type><location_requirements_raw></location_requirements_raw><salary_raw></salary_raw><employment_type><item>Full-time</item></employment_type><url>https://jobs.lever.co/3pillarglobal/7e92a873-7052-4958-9e0c-dcb3fead285c</url><source_type>ats</source_type><source>lever.co</source><source_domain>jobs.lever.co</source_domain><organization_logo>https://lever-client-logos.s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/ac642534-49c7-4e52-9580-2c59423836cb-1723212200858.png</organization_logo><cities_derived></cities_derived><regions_derived></regions_derived><countries_derived><item>Mexico</item></countries_derived><locations_derived><item>Mexico</item></locations_derived><timezones_derived><item>America/Mexico_City</item></timezones_derived><lats_derived><item>19.4333</item></lats_derived><lngs_derived><item>-99.1333</item></lngs_derived><remote_derived>false</remote_derived><description_text>👋 Greetings, future tech savant: 

Embark on an exciting journey into the realm of software development with 3Pillar! We extend an invitation for you to join our team and gear up for a thrilling adventure. At 3Pillar, our focus is on crafting cutting-edge technologies that revolutionize industries. As a DevOps Engineer, you&apos;ll play a vital role in our dynamic team, contributing to exciting projects that redefine urban living, establish new media channels for enterprise companies, or drive innovation in healthcare. This opportunity goes beyond code – it&apos;s about creating epic solutions that leave a lasting impression in the market. If your passion for programming fuels your drive to make a real-world impact, consider this your pass to the captivating world of Product Development! 🚀💻

WE ARE 3PILLAR GLOBAL

At 3Pillar, culture is more than a buzzword. The power of culture, teamwork, and open collaboration drives our commitment to building breakthrough software solutions that power digital businesses. Our passion for software development has gained us recognition in some of the industry’s most innovative spaces, including a spot on the Inc. 5000 list ten years in a row, a three time winner of the Washington Post Top Workplaces Award, and notable features in Forbes, Fortune, and the Washington Business Journal. 

We are an innovative software development partner whose solutions drive rapid revenue, market share, customer growth and employee efficiency for industry leaders in Media and Publishing, Information Services, Banking and Financial Services, Insurance and Healthcare.
Our key differentiator is our Product Mindset. Our development teams focus on building for outcomes and all of our team members around the globe are trained on the Product Mindset’s core values – Minimize Time to Value, Solve For Need, and Excel at Change. Our business-minded approach to agile development ensures that we align to client goals from the earliest conceptual stages through launch and beyond. 

WHAT WE BELIEVE

At 3Pillar, our core values – Intrinsic Dignity, Outsized Impact, Open Collaboration, and Continuous Improvement – drive our commitment to providing best-in-class software development services to high-growth businesses across the globe. We’ve spent more than fifteen years building innovative software solutions. Our executive team has always held our values to the highest standard which has led to active participation on the Forbes Tech Council, a winner of the Ernst &amp; Young Entrepreneur of the Year Award, and a spot on the Washington Business Journal’s Women Who Mean Business list.
\n

Key Responsibilities:
Craft client code that is not just efficient but also performant, testable, scalable, secure, and of the highest quality.
Provide accurate status tracking, reporting, and estimation using project methods and tools.
Gather requirements, validate their understanding amongst the team, and create and maintain relevant documentation.
Execute activities within the current methodology and uphold the highest quality standards.
Foster collaboration with fellow engineers, designers, and managers to comprehend user pain points and iterate on solutions that drive client success.
Take ownership of projects, from technical design to a successful launch.


Key Responsibilities:
Demonstrated expertise with a minimum of 2+ years of experience in at least one of the specified technologies.
Java 17+
Spring boot, JPA
AWS
DB2
Aurora
Azure
Microservices
Reactive Programming
Ideally with knowledge of mobile development (Mobile First / Flutter)
Beginner- to intermediate-level design proficiency following UML/C4/ArchiMate.
Experience in engineering software systems of medium-to-large scope and complexity.
Familiarity with Agile software development methodologies.
Proficiency with relational databases and SQL.
Experience in building frontend/backend applications at scale.
Proficiency in the English language.


Benefits:
Medical Insurance benefits as per company policy. 
Life Insurance as per company policy
15 days of paid vacation plus additional days based on tenure
Vacation bonus as per local law
Sick leave and paid holidays as per local law
Profit sharing as per local law
Paternity and maternity leave as per as per local law
Marriage, bereavement and graduation leaves as per company policy
Christmas bonuses as per local law
Work from home allowance as per company policy
Punctuality and attendance bonuses as per company policy
Food tickets as per company policy
Direct deposit of payroll.
Paid professional certifications

#Li-Remote

\n</description_text></item><item><id>1687377359</id><date_posted>2025-05-22T00:00:00</date_posted><date_created>2025-05-22T17:44:39.507895</date_created><title>Senior Software Engineer</title><organization>Capital One</organization><organization_url></organization_url><date_validthrough></date_validthrough><locations_raw><item><key name="@type">Place</key><address><key name="@type">PostalAddress</key><addressCountry>Mexico</addressCountry><addressLocality>Ciudad de Mexico</addressLocality></address></item></locations_raw><locations_alt_raw><item>Mexico City, Mexico</item></locations_alt_raw><location_type></location_type><location_requirements_raw></location_requirements_raw><salary_raw></salary_raw><employment_type><item>FULL_TIME</item></employment_type><url>https://capitalone.wd12.myworkdayjobs.com/Capital_One/job/Mexico-City-Mexico/Senior-Software-Engineer_R200159</url><source_type>ats</source_type><source>workday</source><source_domain>capitalone.wd12.myworkdayjobs.com</source_domain><organization_logo></organization_logo><cities_derived><item>Mexico City</item></cities_derived><regions_derived><item>Ciudad de México</item></regions_derived><countries_derived><item>Mexico</item></countries_derived><locations_derived><item>Mexico City, Ciudad de México, Mexico</item></locations_derived><timezones_derived><item>America/Mexico_City</item></timezones_derived><lats_derived><item>19.4333</item></lats_derived><lngs_derived><item>-99.1333</item></lngs_derived><remote_derived>false</remote_derived><description_text>WeWork Reforma Latino (97001), Mexico, Ciudad de Mexico, Ciudad de Mexico Senior Software Engineer Do you love building and pioneering in the technology space? Do you enjoy solving complex business problems in a fast-paced, collaborative, inclusive, and iterative delivery environment? At Capital One, you&apos;ll be part of a big group of makers, breakers, doers and disruptors, who solve real problems and meet real customer needs. We are seeking Full Stack Software Engineers who are passionate about marrying data with emerging technologies. As a Capital One Senior Software Engineer, you’ll have the opportunity to be on the forefront of driving a major transformation within Capital One. What You’ll Do: Collaborate with and across Agile teams to design, develop, test, implement, and support technical solutions in full-stack development tools and technologies Share your passion for staying on top of tech trends, experimenting with and learning new technologies, participating in internal &amp; external technology communities, mentoring other members of the engineering community Collaborate with digital product managers, and deliver robust cloud-based solutions that drive powerful experiences to help millions of Americans achieve financial empowerment Utilize programming languages like JavaScript, Java, HTML/CSS, TypeScript, SQL, Python, and Go, Open Source RDBMS and NoSQL databases, Container Orchestration services including Docker and Kubernetes, and a variety of AWS tools and services Basic Qualifications: Bachelor’s Degree At least 2 years of experience in software engineering (Internship experience does not apply) Preferred Qualifications: At least 5 years of experience in at least one of the following: JavaScript, Java, TypeScript, SQL, Python, or Go At least 1 year of experience with AWS, GCP, Microsoft Azure, or another cloud service At least 3 years of experience in open source frameworks At least 2 years of experience in Agile practices At this time, Capital One will not sponsor a new applicant for employment authorization for this position. At Capital One, we respect individual differences in culture, religion, and ethnicity. Likewise, we promote equal opportunities and development for all personnel. In the hiring process, we seek to provide equal employment opportunities to candidates, regardless of race, color, religion, gender, sexual orientation, marital or civil status, national origin, disability, or any other situation protected by federal, state, or local laws. For technical support or questions about Capital One&apos;s recruiting process, please send an email to Careers@capitalone.com Capital One does not provide, endorse nor guarantee and is not liable for third-party products, services, educational tools or other information available through this site. Capital One Financial is made up of several different entities. Please note that any position posted in Canada is for Capital One Canada, any position posted in the United Kingdom is for Capital One Europe, any position posted in the Philippines is for Capital One Service Corp (COPSSC), and any position posted in Mexico is for Capital One Technology Labs Mexico. At Capital One, we’re building a leading information-based technology company. Still founder-led by Chairman and Chief Executive Officer Richard Fairbank, Capital One is on a mission to help our customers succeed by bringing ingenuity, simplicity, and humanity to banking. We measure our efforts by the success our customers enjoy and the advocacy they exhibit.</description_text></item><item><id>1687240396</id><date_posted>2025-05-22T00:00:00</date_posted><date_created>2025-05-22T16:50:57.860178</date_created><title>Automation Software Engineer</title><organization>Flex</organization><organization_url></organization_url><date_validthrough></date_validthrough><locations_raw><item><key name="@type">Place</key><address><key name="@type">PostalAddress</key><addressCountry>Mexico</addressCountry><addressLocality>Guadalajara North, Mexico</addressLocality></address></item></locations_raw><locations_alt_raw><item>Mexico, Guadalajara</item></locations_alt_raw><location_type></location_type><location_requirements_raw></location_requirements_raw><salary_raw></salary_raw><employment_type><item>FULL_TIME</item></employment_type><url>https://flextronics.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/Careers/job/Mexico-Guadalajara/Automation-Software-Engineer_WD201282-1</url><source_type>ats</source_type><source>workday</source><source_domain>flextronics.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com</source_domain><organization_logo></organization_logo><cities_derived><item>Guadalajara</item></cities_derived><regions_derived><item>Jalisco</item></regions_derived><countries_derived><item>Mexico</item></countries_derived><locations_derived><item>Guadalajara, Jalisco, Mexico</item></locations_derived><timezones_derived><item>America/Mexico_City</item></timezones_derived><lats_derived><item>20.6767</item></lats_derived><lngs_derived><item>-103.3475</item></lngs_derived><remote_derived>false</remote_derived><description_text>Flex is the diversified manufacturing partner of choice that helps market-leading brands design, build and deliver innovative products that improve the world. A career at Flex offers the opportunity to make a difference and invest in your growth in a respectful, inclusive, and collaborative environment. If you are excited about a role but don&apos;t meet every bullet point, we encourage you to apply and join us to create the extraordinary. Job Summary To support our extraordinary teams who build great products and contribute to our growth, we’re looking to add a Automation Software Engineer located in Guadalajara, North one of our major manufacturing sites. Excellent opportunity to create an extraordinary career with a global company the size and scale of Flex. Reporting to the Director, Automation Engineering, Automation Software Engineer role will be responsible for architecting, designing, and implementing advanced software solutions that enable seamless integration between manufacturing equipment, databases, and enterprise systems. This senior-level position focuses on creating sophisticated connectivity solutions between production machines and business systems to drive data visibility, process automation, and manufacturing excellence. The engineer will architect and develop robust applications for data acquisition, machine monitoring, process control, and analytics using industrial communication protocols and modern software technologies. They will provide technical leadership on machine connectivity projects, mentor junior engineers, and collaborate with cross-functional teams to implement enterprise-grade IIoT solutions, develop software and secure APIs for system integration, create advanced data visualization dashboards, and optimize database performance for manufacturing applications. This position plays a strategic role in the company&apos;s digital transformation and smart manufacturing initiatives, helping to establish technical standards and best practices. What a typical day looks like: Architect and design software solutions that connect manufacturing equipment to enterprise systems using industrial communication protocols (OPC UA, Modbus, MQTT, Profinet, EtherNet/IP) Knowledge of IT infrastructure management for software development. Lead the development and optimization of database applications and stored procedures in MySQL and MSSQL to manage production data Design and implement scalable RESTful APIs to facilitate secure integration between manufacturing systems and business applications Develop advanced data acquisition strategies for PLCs and other automation controllers Create sophisticated data visualization dashboards using Tableau, PowerBi or similar tools to provide actionable insights into production metrics and KPIs Implement and optimize Elasticsearch for indexing, searching, and analyzing large volumes of manufacturing data Lead IIoT implementation projects for remote monitoring, predictive maintenance, and process control Design and optimize ETL processes and data pipelines for efficient data transformation and loading into enterprise systems Analyze and resolve complex connectivity issues between machines and systems Create comprehensive documentation for developments, interfaces, API specifications, and system architectures Lead technical discussions in cross-functional project meetings to shape technology initiatives Evaluate emerging technologies and methodologies in industrial connectivity and data management Lead the software team, using software development methodologies Provide technical mentorship to junior engineers on machine connectivity technologies and implementation approaches Establish technical standards and best practices for machine connectivity solutions. The experience we’re looking to add to our team: BA/BS or equivalent work experience. Solid experience in industrial software development with focus on machine data, connectivity and system integration. Expert proficiency in programming languages such as Python, C#, or Java with demonstrated experience in developing complex industrial applications. Advanced knowledge of database technologies including MySQL, MSSQL, and data management practices, including performance optimization and security. Comprehensive experience with industrial communication protocols (OPC UA, Modbus, MQTT, Profinet, EtherNet/IP, IPC-CFX). Strong understanding of PLC programming concepts and advanced data extraction techniques. Expertise in RESTful API development, implementation, and security best practices. Advanced knowledge of IIoT (Industrial Internet of Things) architectures, security, and implementation. Proficiency with visualization tools like Tableau, Power BI, or similar data visualization platforms, including advanced dashboard development. Advanced experience with Elasticsearch or similar data indexing and search technologies. Strong knowledge of development project management methodologies (Agile, Scrum, Kanban, Watterfall, etc.) Experience with Software versioning management (Github, Dev Azure, other). Experience with development software frameworks. Comprehensive understanding of MES (Manufacturing Execution Systems) concepts, architecture, and integration methods. Expert knowledge of data processing, ETL pipelines, and data transformation techniques. Strong understanding of cybersecurity principles as they relate to industrial systems and IIoT implementations. Proven ability to lead technical projects and mentor junior team members. Excellent problem-solving skills and ability to work in a fast-paced manufacturing environment. Strong communication skills with ability to explain complex technical concepts to stakeholders. Demonstrated capability in leading major initiatives that may impact multiple sites or customers. Experience with agile development methodologies and collaborative tools. Demonstrates Flex values and commitment to continuous improvement. ation tools (i.e., Git, Maven, SVN, TFS). Experience with Application Servers (i.e., Jboss, Payara, Glassfish, Tomcat) Rest Web Services Experience Intermediate English Experience with Databases is also a plus What you’ll receive for the great work you provide: Competitive Salary. Life &amp; Medical insurance. Christmas Bonus. Food Coupons. Saving Fund. MG61 Job Category Production Engineering Required Skills: Optional Skills: Flex is an Equal Opportunity Employer and employment selection decisions are based on merit, qualifications, and abilities. We do not discriminate based on: age, race, religion, color, sex, national origin, marital status, sexual orientation, gender identity, veteran status, disability, pregnancy status, or any other status protected by law. We&apos;re happy to provide reasonable accommodations to those with a disability for assistance in the application process. Please email accessibility@flex.com and we&apos;ll discuss your specific situation and next steps (NOTE: this email does not accept or consider resumes or applications. This is only for disability assistance. To be considered for a position at Flex, you must complete the application process first). Through the collective strength of 140,000 team members across 30 countries and responsible, sustainable operations, Flex is the diversified manufacturing partner of choice that helps market-leading brands design, build and deliver innovative products that improve the world. A career with Flex offers the opportunity to make a difference, invest in your growth, and build great products for our customers that improve people’s lives. Together, let’s create the extraordinary! Join our talent community to learn more about job opportunities, company news and events.</description_text></item><item><id>1687240391</id><date_posted>2025-05-22T00:00:00</date_posted><date_created>2025-05-22T16:50:57.622041</date_created><title>Automation Software Engineer</title><organization>Flex</organization><organization_url></organization_url><date_validthrough></date_validthrough><locations_raw><item><key name="@type">Place</key><address><key name="@type">PostalAddress</key><addressCountry>Mexico</addressCountry><addressLocality>Guadalajara North, Mexico</addressLocality></address></item></locations_raw><locations_alt_raw><item>Mexico, Guadalajara</item></locations_alt_raw><location_type></location_type><location_requirements_raw></location_requirements_raw><salary_raw></salary_raw><employment_type><item>FULL_TIME</item></employment_type><url>https://flextronics.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/Careers/job/Mexico-Guadalajara/Automation-Software-Engineer_WD201283-1</url><source_type>ats</source_type><source>workday</source><source_domain>flextronics.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com</source_domain><organization_logo></organization_logo><cities_derived><item>Guadalajara</item></cities_derived><regions_derived><item>Jalisco</item></regions_derived><countries_derived><item>Mexico</item></countries_derived><locations_derived><item>Guadalajara, Jalisco, Mexico</item></locations_derived><timezones_derived><item>America/Mexico_City</item></timezones_derived><lats_derived><item>20.6767</item></lats_derived><lngs_derived><item>-103.3475</item></lngs_derived><remote_derived>false</remote_derived><description_text>Flex is the diversified manufacturing partner of choice that helps market-leading brands design, build and deliver innovative products that improve the world. A career at Flex offers the opportunity to make a difference and invest in your growth in a respectful, inclusive, and collaborative environment. If you are excited about a role but don&apos;t meet every bullet point, we encourage you to apply and join us to create the extraordinary. Job Summary To support our extraordinary teams who build great products and contribute to our growth, we’re looking to add an Automation Software Engineer located in Guadalajara, North one of our major manufacturing sites in Guadalajara, Mexico. Excellent opportunity to create an extraordinary career with a global company the size and scale of Flex. Reporting to the Director, Automation Engineering, Automation Software Engineer role will be responsible for designing, developing, and implementing software solutions that enable seamless integration between manufacturing equipment, databases, and enterprise systems. This role focuses on creating robust connectivity between production machines and business systems to enhance data visibility, process automation, and manufacturing efficiency. The engineer will develop and maintain applications for data acquisition, machine monitoring, and process control using industrial communication protocols and modern software technologies. They will work closely with cross-functional teams to implement IIoT solutions, develop APIs for system integration, create data visualization dashboards, and optimize database performance for manufacturing applications. This position plays a critical role in the company&apos;s digital transformation and smart manufacturing initiatives. What a typical day looks like: Design and develop software applications that connect manufacturing equipment to enterprise systems using industrial communication protocols (OPC UA, AMQP, MQTT, Profinet, EtherNet/IP) Create and maintain database applications and stored procedures in MySQL and MSSQL to manage production data Develop and implement RESTful APIs to facilitate integration between manufacturing systems and business applications Configure and troubleshoot data acquisition from PLCs and other automation controllers Design and implement data visualization dashboards using Tableau, PowerBI or similars tools to provide real-time insights into production metrics Work with Elasticsearch to index and search large volumes of manufacturing data Collaborate with automation engineers to implement IIoT solutions for remote monitoring and control Develop and optimize ETL(Extract Load &amp; Transform) processes for data transformation and loading into enterprise systems Troubleshoot connectivity issues between machines and systems Document interfaces, API specifications, and system architectures Participate in cross-functional project meetings to ensure technology initiatives align with business requirements Stay current with emerging technologies and methodologies in industrial connectivity and data management Train and mentor junior team members on machine connectivity technologies and best practices. The experience we are looking to add to our team: BA/BS or equivalent work experience Mid seniority experience in industrial software development with focus on machine data, connectivity and system integration. Proficient in programming languages such as Python, C#, or Java with demonstrated experience in developing industrial applications. Strong knowledge of database technologies including MySQL, MSSQL, and data management practices. Experience with industrial communication protocols (OPC UA, Modbus, MQTT, Profinet, EtherNet/IP). Understanding of PLC programming concepts and data extraction techniques. Experience with RESTful API development and implementation. Knowledge of IIoT (Industrial Internet of Things) principles and implementation. Use of development project management methodologies (Agile, Scrum, Kanban, Watterfall, etc.) Software versioning management (Github, Dev Azure, other). Knowledge of development software frameworks. Familiarity with visualization tools like Tableau, Power BI, or similar data visualization platforms. Experience with Elasticsearch or similar data indexing and search technologies. Understanding of MES (Manufacturing Execution Systems) concepts and integration. Knowledge of data processing, ETL pipelines, and data transformation techniques. Understanding of cybersecurity principles as they relate to industrial systems. Strong problem-solving skills and ability to work in a fast-paced manufacturing environment. Excellent communication skills with ability to collaborate with technical and non-technical stakeholders. Demonstrates commitment to implement initiatives and contributes to team success. What you’ll receive for the great work you provide: Competitive Salary. Life &amp; Medical insurance. Christmas Bonus. Food Coupons. Saving Fund. MG61 Job Category Production Engineering Required Skills: Optional Skills: Flex is an Equal Opportunity Employer and employment selection decisions are based on merit, qualifications, and abilities. We do not discriminate based on: age, race, religion, color, sex, national origin, marital status, sexual orientation, gender identity, veteran status, disability, pregnancy status, or any other status protected by law. We&apos;re happy to provide reasonable accommodations to those with a disability for assistance in the application process. Please email accessibility@flex.com and we&apos;ll discuss your specific situation and next steps (NOTE: this email does not accept or consider resumes or applications. This is only for disability assistance. To be considered for a position at Flex, you must complete the application process first). Through the collective strength of 140,000 team members across 30 countries and responsible, sustainable operations, Flex is the diversified manufacturing partner of choice that helps market-leading brands design, build and deliver innovative products that improve the world. A career with Flex offers the opportunity to make a difference, invest in your growth, and build great products for our customers that improve people’s lives. Together, let’s create the extraordinary! Join our talent community to learn more about job opportunities, company news and events.</description_text></item></jobs>